<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10107032</Id><Name>Radisson Blu Hotel Batumi</Name><Region><Id>5233783</Id><Name>Batumi</Name><CityId>5233783</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 Ninoshvili Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Batumi</City><State /><Zip>6000</Zip><Country>Georgia</Country><Tel>00995 (0)422255555</Tel><Fax>00995 (0)422228888</Fax><Email>reservations.batumi@radissonblu.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/E85front.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/E85thumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1788</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/E85bed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/E85thumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1641</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/E85map.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/E85thumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1510</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Radisson Blu Hotel Batumi is a stylish 5-star property offering modern accommodation in the heart of Batumi. Highlights include fine dining, free Wi-Fi, an excellent location just off Batumi beach and a luxury spa featuring a gym, indoor and outdoor swimming pools and private treatment rooms. Batumi beach is a vibrant and popular retreat offering golden sand, beautiful views of the Black Sea and plenty of shops and entertainment, notably an array of beachfront clubs. Nearby places of interest include Batumi Zoo, Batumi Botanical Garden and the Adjara State Museum. Local bus services provide fast and easy access to other popular Batumi destinations. The hotel is housed in a contemporary high-rise building with a geometric design. Facilities include a luxury spa with indoor and outdoor swimming pools, a gym, sauna, steam room and private treatment rooms. Free Wi-Fi is available throughout the premises. Standard rooms are decorated in a modern style with blue and green tones, striped carpets and floor-to-ceiling windows. They feature views of the city and the Black Sea and a sitting area with an armchair and a foot stool. Amenities include air-conditioning, a flat-screen cable/satellite TV, mini-bar, safe and a Nespresso coffee machine. The en-suite bathrooms feature a bathrobe, slippers and a walk-in shower or bathtub with integrated shower. Clouds Restaurant &amp; Bar Batumi offers international cuisine in a contemporary dining room with a light wood floor, floor-to-ceiling windows and spectacular views over the city and the Black Sea, courtesy of its 19th-floor location. Medea Restaurant Batumi offers local cuisine with international influences in a sophisticated setting with earth tones. Guests can also enjoy a range of cocktails, wines and international beers at the stylish Medea Bar Batumi situated in the lobby. A buffet breakfast is provided every morning and there are plenty of dining opportunities in the vicinity. Free parking is possible onsite. The hotel has a 24-hour reception.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>11</Rank></HotelElement>