<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10121373</Id><Name>Quality Spa &amp; Resort Norefjell</Name><Region><Id>7657461</Id><Name>Noresund </Name><CityId>7657461</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Boeseter</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Noresund</City><State /><Zip>3536</Zip><Country>Norway</Country><Tel>0047 (0)32148200</Tel><Fax>0047 (0)32148211</Fax><Email>booking.norefjell@choice.no</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/5QSfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/5QSthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2192</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/5QSbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/5QSthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1912</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/5QSmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/5QSthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1306</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Nestled in breathtaking mountainous surroundings, the Quality Spa &amp; Resort Norefjell is a beautiful resort within a 1.5 hour drive of both Oslo and Gardermoen International Airport. Primarily a superb ski destination with unobstructed access to mile upon mile of freshly prepared slopes for both adults and children of all abilities, not to mention doorstep ski lifts that link up to the entire Norefjell mountain landscape, the resort is also blessed with beautiful outdoor trails for leisurely walks, running, hiking and mountain biking to guarantee a fun-filled holiday all throughout the year. Nearby lookout points promise beautiful uninterrupted views of Norway, while there are also great possibilities to see reindeer and other wild animals. Within driving distance lies the idyllic 18-hole Norefjell Golf Course complete with an additional driving range, pitching green, and putting green to suited to both beginners and experienced golfers alike. At over 800 metres above sea level, guests can relax in the resort’s spa overlooking the spectacular mountain landscape and indulge in a wide variety of sumptuous massage and beauty treatments. Utilizing both indoor and outdoor areas, the spa comprises swimming pools, whirlpools, saunas, steam rooms and private treatment rooms to soothe the mind, body and spirit. The resort is also home to a 16 metre-high international standard indoor climbing wall, a year-round ice skating rink, a children’s ballgames area, an indoor swimming pool and a gym with state-of-the-art cardiovascular and weight-training equipment. If that isn’t enough, the onsite restaurants strive to provide an unforgettable dining experience, offering extensive dishes using organic, locally sourced ingredients to cater for even the most discerning palate. The Boeseter serves a delightful buffet breakfast with everything from cereals, fresh fruit and coffee, to traditional Norwegian selections and freshly-baked bread, as well as a three course evening menu inspired by local and international cuisine. The Pizzeria offers tantalizing Italian delicacies and classic pizza recipes, while Bar 52 and the adjoining furnished sun terrace are great places to enjoy hot and cold drinks, refreshing cocktails and other alcoholic beverages with friends or family. Standard guestrooms boast a contemporary chalet-style decor with comfortable furnishings and modern amenities, including a flat-screen television and complimentary wireless internet access, to guarantee an enjoyable and memorable stay. There is free parking onsite.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>