<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10368895</Id><Name>Vogue Hotel Bodrum</Name><Region><Id>18833</Id><Name>Bodrum</Name><CityId>18833</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Kaynar Mevkii, Torba</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bodrum</City><State /><Zip>48400</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>0090 (0)2523371070</Tel><Fax>0090 (0)2523371073</Fax><Email>reservation@voguebodrum.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/Y6Qfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/Y6Qthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1997</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/Y6Qbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/Y6Qthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1615</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/Y6Qmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/Y6Qthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1441</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Vogue Hotel Bodrum is a luxury 5-star superior property offering beachfront accommodation northeast of Bodrum. Highlights include fine dining, outdoor swimming pools, tennis courts, a gym, amusement park and a waterpark. Torba is a peaceful fishing village surrounded by hills and pine forests and situated northeast of Bodrum. Nearby places of interest include Torba Bay, the day boat Jetty and the Lelegian Tomb. The hotel occupies a collection of modern mid-rise buildings with elegant facades featuring decorative stonework and terraces or balconies on each floor. Facilities include outdoor swimming pools, tennis courts, a private beach, football field, theatre, library, the 9,000sqm Aquapark and the 12,000sqm Wonder Vogue entertainment park. There is also a luxury spa with saunas, a steam room, Jacuzzi, plunge pool, beauty salon, indoor swimming pool, gym and private treatment rooms. Chargeable Wi-Fi is available in public areas. Superior rooms are decorated in an elegant style with classic Turkish influences, wood floors and earth tones. They feature a balcony and a large sitting area with a sofa and a coffee table. Amenities include air-conditioning, tea and coffee equipment, free Wi-Fi, a flat-screen satellite TV, DVD player and mini-bar with free soft drinks. Nespresso coffee machines are available on request. The en-suite bathrooms feature a bathtub and separate walk-in shower, bathrobes and slippers. Main Restaurant offers buffet style international cuisine in an elegant setting. La Casita Mexicana offers delicious Mexican dishes in a relaxed environment, while Feng serves Chinese and Teppanyaki dishes in a sophisticated space. Ela Ela serves Turkish and Greek cuisine in a traditional Greek tavern. Guests can also enjoy a range of drinks at the stylish hotel bars. Free parking is possible onsite. The hotel provides 24-hour reception and room service and offers a chargeable airport shuttle service.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>