<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10546385</Id><Name>Boulan South Beach</Name><Region><Id>21648</Id><Name>Miami Beach - South Beach</Name><CityId>19741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2000 Collins Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Miami</City><State /><Zip>33139</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>(305) 878-6176</Tel><Fax>+1 (305) 7638836</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located on Collins Avenue between the W South Beach and The Setai South Beach, the all Suite 52 Room Luxury Boutique Property offers oversized one and two bedroom units and penthouse units with roof-top access. Amenities include 24-hour valet, concierge, boutique lobby and common areas, a meditation garden and courtyard, fitness center, landscaped roof-top oasis with pool, Jacuzzi and cabana beds, private beach. The Rooms have a minimalist ultra chic design that is every bit as alluring as the mesmerizing city and ocean views. And the lavish luxuries in every kitchen and bath may give you little reason to ever leave. 
&lt;strong&gt; The hotel has no smoking policy. Valet Parking is $35.00 per night. Internet Access is available throughout the property at a charge of $12.99 for 24 hrs&lt;/strong&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Within walking distance of Boulan South Beach are jet-setter hot spots like the W Hotel, the Gansevoort, the Setai, the Shore Club and the Delano. Celebrated restaurants including Nobu, Mr. Chow, STK, Philippe, Prime One Twelve, the Forge and Joe's Stone Crab. World-class shopping at the open-aired Lincoln Road Mall, the chic boutiques on and off Collins Avenue, the ultra-exclusive Bal Harbour Shops. Boulan South Beach is situated in the Cultural Arts Overlay District across from Collins Park, home to the Bass Museum of Art. Miami Beach's many cultural offerings can also be appreciated at the Miami City Ballet, New World Symphony, the Adrienne Arsht Center of Performing Arts and the Fillmore Theater. For more athletic pursuits, Miami Beach Golf Course and South Pointe Park are just a short drive away. And of course, the sandy beaches and sparkling waters across the way are simply irresistible anytime of the year.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Deluxe - Suite - Deluxe Suite offers one king bed or one queen bed and one sofa bed. Deluxe Ocean View Suites offer all the same luxury of the other accommodations, with the extra touch of exquisite ocean views. Want to take in the ocean with a breath of fresh air? Access your furnished balcony from your bedroom or living area for those sparkling ocean views. Whether you luxuriate in your oversized marble and glass rainfall shower or soak in your roomy oval tub, the blissful bathrooms evoke the ultimate spa experience. The Boulan's Deluxe Ocean View apartments will allow you to live in the lap of luxury. (900 - 1100 square feet).

Platinum - Suite - Platinum Suite offers one king bed or queen bed and one sofa bed. Standard 1 Bedroom Suite: Indulge your senses in this spacious one-bedroom apartment. Inspired by art-deco design, the Boulan's one-bedroom terrace line offers sleek, modern accommodations with a splash of whimsical sophistication. The modern layout makes the most of its generous space with an open plan living and kitchen area to create an expansive sanctuary in the heart of South Beach's trend-setting bustle. (950 -1050 square feet)

Premier - Suite - Premier Suite offers one king bed or queen bed and one sofa bed. The largest of the accommodations, the XL one bedroom will give you the room you need to unwind from Miami's vibrant energy. Enjoy this ample space whose clean, sleek lines will heighten the zen in your everyday life. This art-deco designed apartment captures the perfect blend of modern sophistication and playful elegance. Its glowing white walls and neutral tones are accented with splashes of color throughout this ultra-chic pad. (975 - 1175 Square Feet).

Penthouse - Suite - Penthouse Suite offers two king beds and one queen bed or one sofa bed. Premier Penthouse Suite.

Luxury 2 Bedroom Suite - Luxury Two bedroom Suite offers 2 King Size Beds, a sofa bed and 2 1/2 bathrooms. This Suite is 1323 sq. ft.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>