<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10552599</Id><Name>World Center Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21687</Id><Name>Lower Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>144 Washington Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York</City><State /><Zip>10006</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>212-577-2933</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The World Center Hotel is located in the heart of Lower Manhattan, on the south side of the World Trade Center, with unfettered views of what will become the United States most famous landmark, the 1776 foot Freedom Tower as well as the rising September 11th Memorial &amp; Museum. A newly constructed hotel that offers the latest in guestroom and hotel design in an unforgettable, unique location. This upscale, full service hotel provides a secure, quiet atmosphere including a 24 hour Guest Service Desk/Concierge, instant guest registration, free Internet access throughout the hotel (including guestrooms), free use of computer/printer workstations in the lounge and business center that also features coffee, tea, magazines and games for your pleasure. Guests also have complimentary use of an onsite fitness room. Sleek guestrooms are both comfortable and efficient and offer an alarm clock with iPod docking station, LCD TV with multi-media connectivity, custom designed, soft elm wood furnishings with luxury bedding and linens and a frosted glass-top desk that contributes to the airy ambiance of the room and features an ergonomically designed chair. Other amenities include Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries, hairdryer, coffee maker, earth-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic, touch screen temperature control device, which is programmed for energy efficiency and is located bedside for your convenience. Rounding out our guestroom amenities are in-room high-speed Internet access and chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on every floor  both complimentary. Each room has double paned, floor-to-ceiling windows allowing for tremendous views of downtown Manhattan while limiting the sounds from outdoors. Adding to the hotels special location and contemporary design, is its View of the World Terrace Club. This private club and restaurant is situated on the top floor of the hotel with breathtaking views and year-round indoor/outdoor dining. Multi-menu room service is also available from a variety of area restaurants. In the midst of downtown Manhattan,the World Center Hotel is minutes from world class shopping, restaurants, bars and entertainment. Wall Street, the Financial District, Tribeca, Soho, Battery Park Citys scenic waterfront, the World Financial Center as well as the ferry to the Statue of Liberty/Ellis Island are all nearby.

The World Center Hotel is targeting the LEED 'gold' certificate for environmentally sustainable design, construction &amp; operation.  World Center Hotel uses energy saving programs and electrical appliances, renewable materials in construction, eco-showerheads and dual flush toilets, low energy lighting throughout the hotel, automatic room occupancy sensors and management policies to turn off systems when not required along with various recycling programs.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in the heart of downtown Manhattan, the World Center Hotel is not only surrounded by some of the most powerful corporations and organizations in the world, it is situated directly across from the rising World Trade Center September 11 Memorial &amp; Museum and Freedom Tower. Those familiar with downtown NYC will recognize that Wall Street, the Financial District, the World Financial Center and Battery Park City are just steps away from the World Center Hotel. Guests can enjoy some of the neighborhood's best attractions including the Winter Garden Shops and Restaurants at the World Financial Center, Fraunces Tavern Museum, the waterfront of Battery Park City and locals' favorite department store, Century 21.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>City Studio with Kitchenette - Designed for one or two guests looking for the quintessential Manhattan studio apartment experience, our City Studio features one queen-sized pull-out sofa bed as the bed and an accessory-stocked kitchenette. Room amenities: alarm clock with iPod docking station, flat screen Cable television with premium channels, multi media connectivity, Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries, eco-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic bedside touch screen temperature control device. In-room high-speed Internet access and chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on every floor are complimentary.

Superior Room with Kitchenette and Terrace - The same features &amp; amenities of the Superior Room with Kitchenette, but with a unique indoor/outdoor feature, exterior terrace with seating &amp; partial views of the World Trade Center 9/11 Memorial site &amp; East River. This room offers a queen size bed or two twin beds (limited availability), accessory-stocked kitchenette (plates, mugs, utensils). Blonde elm furnishings include a custom-built headboard and frosted glass-top desk, which features an ergonomically designed chair. You'll enjoy modern conveniences like complimentary in-room high-speed Internet access &amp; chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on every floor. Alarm clock with iPod docking station and a state-of-the-art LCD TV with multi-media connectivity. To make you even more comfortable, our rooms offer Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries, eco-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic, touch screen temperature control device, programmed for energy efficiency &amp; is located bedside for your convenience.

Standard with World Trade Center 911 Memorial Site View - One queen size bed, contemporary wood furnishings including a state of the art desk/work station, Each room also features complimentary WiFi, iPod docking station, touch screen temperature. control system located bedside and LCD TV with multi-media connectivity. Completing your experience is a dramatic view of the World Trade Center 9/11 Memorial. The eight acre site plan includes two massive pools with 30 foot waterfalls  and nearly 400 trees to create a contemplative space separate from the sights and sounds of the surrounding city.

Superior with Kitchenette and World Trade Center 911 Memorial Site View - Queen bed, kitchenette complete with refrigerator and microwave, contemporary wood furnishings including state of the art desk/work station. , Each room also features complimentary WiFi, iPod docking station, touch screen temperature control system located bedside and LCD TV with multi-media connectivity. Completing your experience is a dramatic view of the World Trade Center 9/11 Memorial. The eight acre site plan includes two massive pools with 30 foot waterfalls  and nearly 400 trees to create a contemplative space separate from the sights and sounds of the surrounding city.

Standard Guestroom - Standard: A well-fitting retreat for two, our Standard is larger than our Single and features a queen size bed or two twin beds (limited availability). Custom blonde elm furnishings and thoughtful, state-of-the-art amenities evoke feelings of tranquility and resilience. Each room features an alarm clock with iPod docking station, a state-of-the-art LCD TV with multi-media connectivity and a frosted glass-top desk that contributes to the airy ambiance of the room and features an ergonomically designed chair. Other amenities include Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries, earth-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic, touch screen temperature control device, which is programmed for energy efficiency and is located bedside for your convenience. Rounding out our guestroom amenities are in-room high-speed Internet access and chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on every floor - both complimentary.

Superior with Kitchenette - Offering a queen size bed or two twin beds (limited availability), as well as an accessory-stocked kitchenette (plates, mugs, utensils), this urban-designed room is the perfect blend of comfort and style. Blonde elm furnishings include a custom-built headboard and frosted glass-top desk, which features an ergonomically designed chair. You'll enjoy modern conveniences like complimentary in-room high-speed Internet access and chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on every floor. Our Superior rooms also feature an alarm clock with iPod docking station and a state-of-the-art LCD TV with multi-media connectivity. To make you even more comfortable, our Superior Room offers Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries, eco-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic, touch screen temperature control device, which is programmed for energy efficiency and is located bedside for your convenience.

One Room - Suite with Kitchenette - When you need some more space, our One Room Suite offers a queen size bed, a pull out sofa bed in the living room area, and a kitchenette that's stocked with necessary accessories like plates, mugs and utensils. This airy, stylish room offers custom-designed furnishings that combine blonde elm, frosted glass and contemporary fabrics in a tasteful, understated way. Every One Room Suite offers an alarm clock with iPod docking station, a state-of-the-art LCD TV with multi-media connectivity and Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries. Other features include earth-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic, touch screen temperature control device, which is programmed for energy efficiency and is located bedside for your convenience. Rounding out our guestroom amenities are in-room high-speed Internet access and chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on 
every floor - both complimentary.

Single/Small Double - Perfect for guests traveling alone, or wanting a room to themselves, our Single/Small Double rooms are the utmost in stylish NYC efficiency with one queen size bed and modern, custom-designed furnishings.. Each room features an alarm clock with iPod docking station, a state-of-the-art LCD TV with multi-media connectivity and a frosted glass-top desk and an ergonomically designed chair. We've also incorporated Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries, eco-friendly bathroom fixtures and an electronic, touch screen temperature control device, which is programmed for energy efficiency and is located bedside for your convenience. In-room high-speed Internet access and chilled, filtered, bottled water stations on every floor are complimentary. Maximum Occupancy:2</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>