<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10573863</Id><Name>Georgetown Suites Harbour Building</Name><Region><Id>21950</Id><Name>Georgetown</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1000 29th St Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20007</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (202) 298-1600</Tel><Fax>+1 (202) 333-2019</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Georgetown Suites is an all suite hotel located in the heart of Historic Georgetown. The hotel is surrounded by the unique shops, boutiques and restaurants of Georgetown, Washingtons premiere neighborhood. Georgetown Suites consists of two buildings that are located just a half block from each other. Both buildings offer the same amenities and have similar decor. Many of our repeat guests have their favorite building, while others like to alternate which property they stay at each time.  Georgetown Suites Harbour features 80 suites and is located across the street from the offices and restaurants of the Washington Harbour Complex on the Georgetown waterfront. Two of our three conference rooms are located in the Harbour Building. All Rates include free continental breakfast, free wireless internet, and free local calls. This building is completely nonsmoking.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Tourist site</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Studio queen nonsmoking - Spacious studio suite with queen bed en-us !DEFAULT! and full kitchen nonsmoking en-us !DEFAULT!

1 Bedroom King Suite Nonsmoking - Spacious one bedroom suite with en-us !DEFAULT! separate bedroom and living room nonsmoking en-us !DEFAULT!

Penthouse - This 2 bedroom plus den suite has 3 1/2 baths en-us !DEFAULT! and sweeping views of Georgetown en-us !DEFAULT!

Studio king nonsmoking - Spacious studio suite with king bed with en-us !DEFAULT! kitchen and free wireless internet non smoking en-us !DEFAULT!

1 Bedroom Queen Nonsmoking - One bedroom suite with queen bed en-us !DEFAULT! and full kitchen. nonsmoking room en-us !DEFAULT!</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>