<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10574126</Id><Name>Club Quarters Washington</Name><Region><Id>21949</Id><Name>Foggy Bottom</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>839 17th Street N.w.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20006</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>202-463-6400</Tel><Fax>+1 (202) 4636401</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Club Quarters is a full service hotel that overlooks Farragut Square and is just two blocks from the White House and Lafayette Square.  A short walk to all the monuments and museums in downtown DC.  Free high-speed Internet access in all guest rooms, 24 hour Guest Service Desk/Concierge, Fitness Facility, Private Club Room with complimentary newspapers, magazine and games, as well as use of a computer/printer with free high-speed internet access.  Guestrooms are comfortable, elegantly styled and beautifully appointed with all modern conveniences and pillow top mattresses.  Other amenities include two-line speaker phone with private direct dial phone number, well lighted desk and work area.  The on-site restaruant, Cafe Soleil is a popular, casual bistro.  Room Service as well as multi-menu room delivery also available.  Club Quarters warm and friendly staff provides first class customer service.  The hotel is minutes to fine dining, shopping and entertainment.  Club Quarters is affiliated with Central Parking located on 18th Street between K and L Streets. The cost is $15 for 24 hours with validated parking ticket.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>White House, Constitution Gardens, Washington Monument, National Mall, Vietnam Veterans Memorial, Lafayette Square, National Archives, Foggy Bottom boutiques and restaurants, Korean War Veterans Building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>One Room Suite with Kitchenette - One queen bed with kitchenette, including microwave and refrigerator. Other features include premium mattress and premium linens,  contemporary  wood furnishings - latest design workstation with task lighting, ergonomic chair and complimentary high-speed Internet access with network printing, cable/satellite TV with On Demand movies, 2-line speaker and cordless phones with direct dial number and voicemail, MP3 alarm clock with iPod docking station, individual climate control, hair dryer, makeup/shaving mirror and tea/coffee making facilities. Some rooms may accommodate a chairbed or rollaway -available only upon request and subject to availability. Maximum Occupancy: 3

Superior with Kitchenette - Oversized room with one queen bed and kitchenette, including microwave and refrigerator. Other features include premium  mattress and premium linens, contemporary wood furnishings - latest design workstation with task lighting, ergonomic chair and complimentary high-speed Internet access with network printing, cable/satellite TV with On Demand movies, 2-line speaker and cordless phones with direct dial number and voicemail, MP3 alarm clock with iPod docking station, individual climate control, hair dryer, makeup/shaving mirror and tea/coffee making facilities. Some rooms may accommodate a rollaway - available only upon request and subject to availability. Maximum Occupancy: 3

Standard Room - One queen bed with premium mattress and premium linens. Other features include contemporary wood furnishings - latest design workstation with task lighting, ergonomic chair and complimentary high-speed Internet access with network printing, cable/satellite TV with On Demand movies, 2-line speaker and cordless phones with direct dial number and voicemail, MP3 alarm clock with iPod docking station, individual climate control, hair dryer, makeup/shaving mirror and tea/coffee making facilities. Maximum Occupancy: 2

Club Size Room - One full or queen bed with premium mattress and premium linens. Other features include contemporary wood furnishings - latest design workstation with task lighting, ergonomic chair and complimentary high-speed Internet access with network printing, cable/satellite TV with On Demand movies, 2-line speaker and cordless phones with direct dial number and voicemail, MP3 alarm clock radio with iPod docking station, individual climate control, hair dryer, makeup/shaving mirror and tea/coffee making facilities. Maximum Occupancy: 2</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>