<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>107850</Id><Name>Don Antonio</Name><Region><Id>21272</Id><Name>Peguera </Name><CityId>18419</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>BONAVIDA 8</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PAGUERA</City><State /><Zip>07160</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>971.033033</Tel><Fax>971.033000</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>39.5404064</Latitude><Longitude>2.4386041</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867main.jpg</Url><Width>180</Width><Height>144</Height><Bytes>6405</Bytes><Caption>main</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867mainthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2028</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867general.jpg</Url><Width>180</Width><Height>144</Height><Bytes>6150</Bytes><Caption>general</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867generalthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1883</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867reception.jpg</Url><Width>180</Width><Height>144</Height><Bytes>6102</Bytes><Caption>reception</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867receptionthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2066</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867room.jpg</Url><Width>180</Width><Height>144</Height><Bytes>5454</Bytes><Caption>room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867roomthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1867</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867xml.jpg</Url><Width>180</Width><Height>144</Height><Bytes>6405</Bytes><Caption>xml</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1024/48/67/4867xmlthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2028</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Hotel Don Antonio is situated in Peguera, one of the prettiest parts of the south-west coastal region of the island of Mallorca. Peguera is within easy reach (20 Kms) of the island’s capital city Palma. The Hotel is only 900m from Peguera centre and the same distance from the beaches. For golfers there is a choice of three splendid 18 hole golf courses within a 7 km radius.



SERVICES AVAILABLE VIA THE HOTEL’S RECEPTION: Money Exchange, Rent a Car, Fax and Internet, Laundry Service, Towels for the swimming pools, Baby Sitter, Free Mini Bus, Car Park, Medical Aid, Luggage Service.



The Hotel Don Antonio offers 151 rooms (from 25•5 sq.mts up to 32 sq.mts). In addition the hotel also has three specially equipped rooms for wheelchair users. All the rooms have a terrace and the majority offer sea views looking on to the Mediterranean Sea.

The comfortable rooms are equipped to a high standard  worthy of a hotel of this category. All the rooms have «en suite» bathrooms complete with hair dryer, a make up mirror, telephone, and for winter use, a radiator / towel dryer. Furthermore most rooms give you the choice between individual bath and shower.

Each room has a telephone with direct exterior line, mini bar, safe box, television with satellite channels, radio and air conditioning. There is also a number of rooms which have French Beds.



RESTAURANT: The HDA offers a Restaurant - Buffet Bar where guests can enjoy an extensive variety of meals and a wide choice of Mediterranean and international cuisine.

BAR SALÓN: In a quiet corner of the entrance Hall of the hotel you can find the magnificent Bar Salón where as well as a pleasing selection of snacks guests can enjoy their favourite drinks or seek adventure in one of our exquisite cocktails.

SNACK BAR: Located on the hotel´s terrace, between the two swimming pools is the hotel Snack Bar where refreshing drinks and tasty snacks are prepared throughout the summer months for guests´ enjoyment.



The Hotel has two open air swimming pools; one for children with a solarium, and a second one for adults with a small jacuzzi. Around each pool are deck chairs and loungers as well as parasols to give plenty of protection and shade against the midday sun. There is an on site snack bar for hotel clients. Just a few metres from the adult pool is a kids’ playground for the little ones.


The Hotel Don Antonio is the perfect place to keep in shape. The hotel boasts a fully equipped gym, along with sauna and Turkish baths, there’s also a Jacuzzi and air conditioned interior pool complete with its own incorporated Jacuzzi (open to the public out of season between November and April)



Around Peguera, the Hotel Don Antonio makes available to its clients a wide range of sports activities so that they might enjoy their holidays to the maximum -  sailing, diving, tennis and boat hire. 
Near to the hotel are three modern, well equipped golf courses which will delight even the most demanding of players. The Hotel is also ideally situated for lovers of hiking and trekking.


The Balearic Islands – the name only brings in mind instant images of warm sun and unspoilt nature – coupled with culture and history ave a  privileged their position in the Mediterranean Sea. The largest of the islands, Mallorca, is a land of 4000 years packed with hidden secrets and wonderful scenic routes through small inland villages - the island is quite simply a delight! And these few succinct words of Archduke Luis Salvador say it all «It's almost impossible to believe that the eyes are capable of taking in so much beauty of form and colour at any one time»</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>