<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10819078</Id><Name>Kensington Aparthotel</Name><Region><Id>52887</Id><Name>Kensington &amp; Earls Court</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>8 Knaresborough Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW5 0TG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (0) 20 73700003</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Kensington Apart'Hotel is a mix of standard and superior one and two bedroom serviced apartments sleeping up to four people. The hotel is just a few minutes walk from the renowned Cromwell Hospital. Cradled in the heart of Kensington and Chelsea, guests at the Kensington Apart'Hotel, will benefit from the convenience and services of a hotel whilst also enjoying the space and freedom of apartment living. The apartments are all available on a nightly basis, with no minimum stay, making them the ideal choice for both corporate clients and visitors to London. The hotel close to an excellent transport network with a choice between Earls Court and Gloucester Road stations or buses in or out of Central London. This makes the hotel an ideal spot from where guests can enjoy easy access to all that London has to offer. A haven of rest and relaxation, Kensington Apart'Hotel offers total short-stay solutions for the corporate as well as the leisure market. Earls Court and Olympia Exhibition Centre are both within walking distance of the hotel. The hotel is also within walking distance of the Natural History Museum, the Royal Albert Hall and the Victoria and Albert Museum. There are many historical attractions close by including High Street Kensington, Knightsbridge with Harrods. The functional yet tasteful layout, with a range of facilities such as WI-Fi, elevator, family room, in-room safety deposit boxes and 24 HR reception, ensures that all essential requirements are taken care of at the Kensington Apart'Hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in south Kensington, within a short walk of Earls Court or Gloucester Road Tube Stations (Piccadilly, District and Circle lines), the Apart'Hotel is ideally placed with good transport links to all major airports and transport interchanges. The closest mainline stations to the Kensington apartments are Victoria and Paddington, all accessible via London Underground Services or short taxi rides. South Kensington is culturally and historically one of the most vibrant districts in West London with numerous places of interest filled with many activities - boutiques, cinemas, theatres and restaurants. The National History Museum, the Victoria and Albert Museum and the Science Museum are all within easy reach of the apartments.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Apartment - Standard Apartment offers one double size bed with basic amenities. Functional and ideal for the lone traveller or a couple, the standard apartment has the added advantage of coming at a slightly more advantageous price without compromising on space and quality. Standard double bed, luxury duvets and bedding, flat screen television, tea and coffee making facilities, direct dial phone, in room safe, hair dryer and bathroom amenities. Most rooms of the standard one bed apartment offer a view.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>