<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10829926</Id><Name>Holly House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52928</Id><Name>Westminster &amp; Victoria </Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>18 - 34 Hugh Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW1V 1RP</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 834 5671</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>One thinks of London and two things come to mind. The many landmark sights...and the expense! However, even in the heart of the capital you can still find affordable accommodation in order for you to be able to take in all the sights, or alternatively, make in roads to the important business that are only conducted day to day in the country's number one city.

The source of this oasis in the wilderness is the Holly House Hotel on Hugh Street, just around the corner from Victoria Train Station, Underground and coach station, with St. Pancras Station also being close by for Eurostar trains.

We are situated in one of the main thoroughfares in Victoria, in the heart of London. Our warm, friendly hospitality is second to none, matching the stylish facilities and quality service to the perfect location. 

We do our utmost to ensure our clients have a pleasant and enjoyable stay with us and make their trip a memorable experience.

Very close to Bicycle hiring bay.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The source of this oasis in the wilderness is the Holly House Hotel on Hugh Street, just around the corner from Victoria Train Station, Underground and coach station, with St. Pancras Station also being close by for Eurostar trains.

We are situated in one of the main thoroughfares in Victoria, in the heart of London. Our warm, friendly hospitality is second to none, matching the stylish facilities and quality service to the perfect location.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single Room - Single room with colour television, free Wi-Fi Internet, tea/coffee making facilities. Fridge and Fan including continental breakfast. We provide hair dryer and iron on request.

Twin Room - Twin room with colour television, free Wi-Fi Internet, tea/coffee making facilities. Fridge and Fan including continental breakfast. We provide hair dryer and iron on request.

Double Room - Double room with colour television, free Wi-Fi Internet, tea/coffee making facilities. Fridge and Fan including continental breakfast. We provide hair dryer and iron on request.

Triple Room - Triple room with colour television, free Wi-Fi Internet, tea/coffee making facilities. Fridge and Fan including continental breakfast. We provide hair dryer and iron on request.

Family Room - Family room with colour television, free Wi-Fi Internet, tea/coffee making facilities. Fridge and Fan including continental breakfast. We provide hair dryer and iron on request.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>