<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10828979</Id><Name>Central Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>16 - 18 Argyle Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>WC1H 8EG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 837 9008</Tel><Fax>+44 (207) 8379008</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Dining-4.jpg</Url><Width>395</Width><Height>296</Height><Bytes>14425</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Central-Hotel-Dining-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Dining-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1699</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>30499</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Central-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2191</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3639</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Central-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2232</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>18162</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Central-Hotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1746</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>18941</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Central-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/50/26/1/2631759-Central-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>52</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1284</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Central hotel is a family run bed and breakfast conveniently located in the heart of central London offering superb value for money accommodation. The hotel is situated barely a minutes walk from Kings Cross Tube Station and offers easy access to all of London's tourist sights, shopping districts and theatres. The hotel has been run by the family for over forty years and during this period the hotel have established a wonderful reputation with the customers. The hotel always strive to achieve a warm friendly and well informed atmosphere, making your stay as homely and comfortable as possible. The hotel has 30 rooms which vary from comfortable budget rooms to well presented en-suite rooms and the price includes a hearty full English breakfast to help get you off to a good start each day!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Central Hotel is located in the heart of central London, barely a minutes walk from Kings Cross and st. Pancras tube and mainline train station giving you easy access to the whole of central and Greater London and also access to anywhere outside of this wonderful city. Buses and taxi ranks are also located at the same station. The hotel is situated close to many of the tourist attractions including Piccadilly Circus, Leicester Square, Soho, British Museum, British Library, Madame Tusauds, Rock Circus, London Zoo, London Dungeons, Tower Bridge, The London Eye, Buckingham Palace and many more are nearby and all are reachable within 5 to 30 minutes maximum by tube. The hotel is also very close to Tottenham Court Road and Oxford Street for those who like to shop.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Economy Room - Economy Room offers one double size bed with basic amenities. Economy rooms do not have private shower and toilet; shower and toilet are outside the room which is shared with other rooms. But also have TV, tea / coffee making facilities, central heating , sheets, towels, soap, daily chambermaid service, free WI-Fi internet in rooms, English breakfast and taxes. The hotel can also provide, wake up calls for those following a schedule. Iron and ironing boards, hair dryers are also available on request. The hotel make sure that all the rooms are cleaned daily for maximum cleanliness and customer satisfaction. Smoking is not permited in Central Hotel. Each morning a good English breakfast is served this is also included in the price.

Double En-suite - Double En-suite Room offers one double size bed with basic amenities. Ensuite rooms come with private toilet and shower, TV, hairdryer, tea/coffee making facilities, central heating, sheets, towels, soap, daily chambermaid service, free Wi-Fi internet in rooms, English breakfast and taxes.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Security24Hour</Code><Text>24-hour security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>