<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846468</Id><Name>Royal Norfolk Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52528</Id><Name>Folkestone</Name><CityId>52528</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>7  Sandgate High Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Folkestone</City><State /><Zip>CT20 3BD</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01303 248262</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Situated in the picturesque seaside town of Sandgate, this hotel offers a wide range of modern accommodation and great food in their Gees Bar, served from Mon- Sat 12 noon till 8pm and 12 noon till 4pm on Sun. Their bar serves a great selection of wines, spirits, draft lagers, real ales and cider, fresh cappuccino and latte coffee. On Fridays, the bar hosts great local entertainment including live music until 1am</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Sandgate is a beautiful antique and art village, with an interesting naval, military and social history. The village spreads across 2 kms of the Kent coastline, with Folkestone and Hythe on either side. Sandgate offers a range of leisurely walks along the coastal park, such as a stroll along the sea wall or a relaxing walk in the woodlands and country side with views across the Channel. It also offers cycling and water based leisure activities: rowing, fishing and bathing. The Royal Norfolk Hotel is close to the Port of Dover, the Channel Tunnel and the Ashford Eurostar service (just 39 minutes to London St Pancras). With Dover, Deal and Walmer Castles and also Leeds Castle plus Port Lympne Wild Animal Park and Canterbury Cathedral, there's much nearby to keep the whole family amused.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Double - Standard Double offers one double bed with standard amenities.

Superior Double - Superior Double offers one double bed with standard amenities.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>