<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859073</Id><Name>The Hope Anchor</Name><Region><Id>153616</Id><Name>Rye</Name><CityId>153616</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Watchbell Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Rye, East Sussex</City><State /><Zip>TN31 7HA</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01797 222216</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Dining-7.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>321</Height><Bytes>24677</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Dining-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Dining-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2554</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>252</Height><Bytes>29680</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>133</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3613</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>4381</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2718</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Property-Amenity-8.jpg</Url><Width>321</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>23075</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Property-Amenity-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Property-Amenity-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1566</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>321</Height><Bytes>21091</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2199</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>22440</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2057</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>20556</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2201</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>321</Height><Bytes>19259</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1972</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>23819</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/19/41/2631759-The-Hope-Anchor-Guest-Room-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>52</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1523</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Hope Anchor is a mid 18th Century Hotel built at the end of one of the most delightful streets in Rye. The building originally would have housed a Smugglers gang thought to have been "The Tenterden", a nasty motley crew! Pistols at the ready and regular fights for territory with other local smugglers gangs including the infamous Hawkhurst, legend has it that on one occasion the Tenterden gang famously out gunned the Hawkhurst gang and they scurried hurriedly back to their watering hole! Most of the secret passage ways and escape routes are now blocked in but once here, it doesn't take a lot of imagination to realize what it was like in those dark and exciting days! The Hope Anchor as its name suggests was built primarily for a watering hole for the sailors and ship builders as Rye was still surrounded by the sea up until the late 18th century. The hotel and all rooms are Non Smoking. Although famous for its past, the Hope Anchor is known locally for its stunning views across the Quayside, Romney Marshes, Camber Castle and beyond to the sea. Most of the rooms enjoy these panoramic views and to be honest they need to be seen to be believed. Although beautiful all year round the sunsets in summer bring locals young and old to enjoy alfresco dining accompanied of course with a glass or two of wine! The Hope Anchor features in Malcolm Saville's children's books and is described as the Gay Dolphin. It has also been identified as the Traders Arms in the map and Lucia books by E. F. Benson, a well known writer who lived in Lamb house. Rye was never built to cope with today's traffic or transport and parking is at a premium in Rye, the hotel is however lucky, although the outside of the building is controlled by local authorities, it has parking permits for its guests so your car is never far away. The Hope Anchor stands elegantly poised in this exquisite medieval town, one common trait is that once visited travelers and guests return time and time again.
The hotel also offers free breakfast to it's guests.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel in the Citadel of Rye and within an hours drive of the Chanel tunel, Leeds, Dover or Bodiam Castle, Historic houses and gardens, Eastbourne, Hastings and only a ten minute drive to the beach.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>The Sankey Suite (Rm3) - The Sankey Suite (Rm3) is a Four Poster Deluxe Double Bedroom with small separate lounge and en suite Bathroom and shower; it is positioned on the first floor over looking, Romney Marsh, and Camber Castle and to the horizon the sea. The Harbour View (Rm6) is a Four Poster Deluxe Double Bedroom with en suite Bathroom and shower attachment; it is positioned on the first floor over looking across the quayside, Romney Marsh, and Camber Castle and to the horizon the sea.

The Nook and Cranny (Rm21) - The Nook and Cranny (Rm21) is a Twin bedded Bedroom and has sloping ceilings and low beams with an en suite shower; it is positioned on the second floor over looking, Romney Marsh, and Camber Castle and to the horizon the sea.

The Roof Tops (Rm26) - The Roof Tops (Rm26) is a small Double Bedroom with en suite shower; it is positioned on the second floor over looking the Medieval roof tops of Rye and beyond. The Riverside (Rm2) is a small Double Bedroom with en suite shower; it is positioned on the first floor at the front of the hotel over looking the Quayside, Romney Marsh, and to the left Camber Castle and to the horizon the sea.

HONEYMOON - APARTMENT - A ground floor Apartment (A) with a large combined bedroom and lounge with En suite bathroom with separate shower and access to a large patio area. The Apartment (A) is equipped with free view TV and DVD recorder, WI-FI, mini bar and telephone, tea and coffee making facilities. There are two armchairs that convert into two single beds to Accommodate a family at an extra 30 per person bed and breakfast. The hotel and all rooms are Non Smoking. The Admirals Apartments are situated 10 metres away from the hotel and are of Watch Bell Street (a quiet cobbled street) with views across Romney Marshes, Camber Castle and the sea.

EXECUTIVE - APARTMENT - The first floor Apartment is accessed of the landing and comprises a large double bedroom with an en suite bathroom and shower with walk in dressing room, it is equipped with free view TV, WI-FI, telephone and tea and coffee making facilities. There is a separate lounge also with free view TV, mini bar and WI-FI connection. There are two armchairs in the lounge that convert into two single beds to accommodate a family at an extra 30 per person bed and breakfast.The hotel and all rooms are Non Smoking. The Admirals Apartments are situated 10 metres away from the hotel and are of Watch Bell Street (a quiet cobbled street) with views across Romney Marshes, Camber Castle and the sea.

COURTYARD - COTTAGE - The Hidden Treasure Cottage (Rm30)is a two hundred year old Fishermans Cottage recently refurbished situated to the side of the hotel. It has a small hallway and utility room, lounge with a two seater settee and two armchairs that convert into two single beds to Accommodate a family at an extra 30 per person bed and breakfast. Up stairs is a double bedroom with en suite bathroom and shower. As the cottage is situated to the side of the hotel, the views of Romney Marsh are obscructed on the ground floor. Every room has a direct dial telephone, clock radio, flat screen Digital Free view TV, hair dryer and hot drinks tray, plus a few little niceties that usually meet with its guests' approval. The Lounge, Bar, Restaurant and most of the bedrooms have WIFI connection for the internet.The hotel and all rooms are Non Smoking.

DELUXE - DOUBLE - Every room has a direct dial telephone, clock radio, flat screen Digital Free view TV, hair dryer and hot drinks tray, plus a few little niceties that usually meet with its guests' approval. The Lounge, Bar, Restaurant and most of the bedrooms have WIFI connection for the internet.The hotel and all rooms are Non Smoking.

The Jolly Sailor (Rm28) - The Jolly Sailor (Rm28) is a Deluxe King Size Double Bedroom with en suite Bathroom and separate shower; it is positioned on the first floor over looking Watch Bell Street, Romney Marsh, and Camber Castle and to the horizon the sea.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>