<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856228</Id><Name>The Old Bank Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52674</Id><Name>Oxford</Name><CityId>52674</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>92-94 High Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Oxford</City><State /><Zip>OX1 4BJ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0014-418-657-995-99</Tel><Fax>+44 (0) 1865 799598</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>32509</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2582</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3760</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2351</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Lobby-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>22361</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Lobby-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Lobby-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2327</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Other-9.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>40650</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Other-9</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Other-9.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2739</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Bathroom-7.jpg</Url><Width>272</Width><Height>394</Height><Bytes>14972</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Bathroom-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Bathroom-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>48</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1302</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>22385</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1935</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>20723</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2034</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>18888</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2168</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>19949</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2137</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Meeting-Room-8.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>25256</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Meeting-Room-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/55/46/2631759-The-Old-Bank-Hotel-Meeting-Room-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2340</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Situated in the heart of historical Oxford, The Old Bank offers luxury rooms with marble bathrooms and modern art. With free private parking, there is also a stylish brasserie and jazz bar. The spacious rooms are air conditioned and elegantly decorated. Rooms also offer a TV, tea and coffee facilities, and ample work space. Many have original period features and views of the city. The Quod Brasserie at The Old Bank Hotel serves a creative menu, and features a pleasant terrace and an impressive collection of contemporary art. Cooked breakfasts and daily specials are also available, and live jazz is a regular fixture. Just steps away from Merton, All Souls and Oriel Colleges, The Old Bank is a 5-minute walk from the Botanic Garden. Magdalen Bridge and the River Cher-well can also be reached in 5 minutes, and Oxford Rail Station is a 15-minute walk away.

PLEASE NOTE: If you wish to book 5 or more rooms, the Hotel's cancellation policy will vary from that displayed on this site. Please contact the Hotel directly to discuss the policy.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Please note between the hours of 7am and 6.30pm a traffic restriction on the High is enforced. From the city cent-re the hotel is situated half way down the High Street opposite St Marys Church (the University Church) and Catte Street. The hotel is the most centrally located in the city between famous colleges Merton, All Souls, University and Oriel and within minutes of the best of Oxfords shopping, theaters, galleries, libraries and gardens. The hotel has a large secure private car park which provides up to 40 spaces for hotel guests and is accessed via an automated barrier.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Superior Deluxe Double - Our Superior Deluxe Double Rooms, all at the front of the hotel, offer a contemporary and stylish decor with superior fixtures and fittings. Each of these spacious rooms boast a range of excellent facilities for discerning guests. These include complimentary high-speed Broadband access, flat screen TV, CD player, air-conditioning, safe and a hairdryer. The bathrooms have a bath and shower, most with a separate shower cubicle, bathrobes and toiletries. approx 270 sq ft. Twin Beds on request, subject to availability. Maximum Occupancy 4.

The Suite - Our Suite offers a contemporary and stylish decor with superior fixtures and fittings and a superb view of colleges and Oxford spires across the skyline. The suite boasts a range of excellent facilities for discerning guests, including complimentary high-speed Broadband access, flat screen TV, CD player, air-conditioning, safe and a hairdryer. The bathrooms have a bath and separate shower, bathrobes and toiletries. approx 305 sq ft. Maximum Occupancy 4.

Accessible Double Room - Adapted for the disabled with wheelchair access. Each room offers a contemporary and stylish decor with superior fixtures and fittings. Each of the rooms boasts lovely views and a range of excellent facilities for discerning guests. These include complimentary high-speed Broadband access, flat screen TV, CD player, air-conditioning, safe and a hairdryer. The bathrooms have shower/wet room facilities, bathrobes and toiletries. 14 m square. Maximum Occupancy 2

Double Room - Double Room with one double bed offer a contemporary and stylish decor with superior fixtures and fittings. Many of the rooms boast lovely views and all have a range of excellent facilities for discerning guests. These include complimentary high-speed Broadband access, flat screen TV, CD player, air-conditioning, safe and a hairdryer. The bathrooms have a bath and shower, bathrobes and toiletries. approx 150 sq ft.

Deluxe Double Room - Deluxe Double Room with one double bed offer a contemporary and stylish decor with superior fixtures and fittings. Each of these spacious rooms boasts a range of excellent facilities for discerning guests. These include complimentary high-speed Broadband access, flat screen TV, CD player, air-conditioning, safe and a hairdryer. The bathrooms have a bath and shower, most with a separate shower cubicle, bathrobes and toiletries. approx 205 sq ft.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>