<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856122</Id><Name>Waltons Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52666</Id><Name>Nottingham</Name><CityId>52666</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2 North Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nottingham</City><State /><Zip>NG7 1AG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01159475215</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Situated in the historic Park area of the city of Nottingham, Walton's Hotel provides the perfect retreat. Built as a hunting lodge in the early 1800's, this unique residence has retained many of its original features whilst offering all of the conveniences of modern living. This prestigious and secluded location is amazingly just 5 minutes walk from the vibrant cent-re of Nottingham. Here you'll find a superb range of shops, bars, pubs, restaurants, theaters and the city's historic castle. Beautifully decorated throughout, Walton's Hotel offers 17 stunning single, double and family rooms all with free WIFI, a lively bar and stylish restaurant serving a delicious menu. You can also relax in the spacious patio area overlooking a tranquil landscaped garden. Walton's Hotel is the perfect setting for private parties and weddings, all tailor-made to meet your requirements. Or you can simply sit back and enjoy one of regular special events such as summer barbecues and evenings of live music. Amenities - Free Breakfast.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Walton's Hotel is situated in the historic Park area of the city of Nottingham, this prestigious and secluded location is just 5 minutes walk from the vibrant cent-re of Nottingham. Here you'll find a superb range of shops, bars, pubs, restaurants, theaters and the city's historic castle.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Double Twin - Double Twin with one double or two twin beds includes an outstanding level of comfort with private bathrooms, direct dial telephones, colour television, DVD/Video, free WIFI and tea and coffee making facilities. Each one of 17 rooms has been carefully decorated and furnished in keeping with the atmosphere and ambience of a 19th century hunting lodge. Each room is unique, with its' own individual style.

Single Room - Single Room with one twin bed includes outstanding level of comfort with private bathrooms, direct dial telephones, colour television, DVD/Video, free WIFI and tea and coffee making facilities. Each one of 17 rooms has been carefully decorated and furnished in keeping with the atmosphere and ambience of a 19th century hunting lodge. Each room is unique, with its' own individual style.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>