<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10850117</Id><Name>Throstles Nest Hotel Liverpool</Name><Region><Id>52609</Id><Name>Liverpool</Name><CityId>52609</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>344 Scotland Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Liverpool</City><State /><Zip>L5 5AQ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-151-207-9797</Tel><Fax>44-151-207-9594</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>384</Height><Bytes>22847</Bytes><Caption>Throstles-Nest-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1915</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2925</Bytes><Caption>Throstles-Nest-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1955</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>384</Height><Bytes>24375</Bytes><Caption>Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1819</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>384</Height><Bytes>24832</Bytes><Caption>Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1813</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>384</Height><Bytes>26398</Bytes><Caption>Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/36/61/Throstles-Nest-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1975</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>A superb 18th century hotel recently refurbished, and one of the most famous pubs in Liverpool. Your stay at this Bed &amp; Breakfast Hotel is a real experience, providing you easy access to Liverpool City Centre - just a quarter of a mile away. Close to all major attractions, explore all that Liverpool has to offer, from its magical nightlife to the peace and tranquility of two, amazing Cathedrals and of course a visit to Liverpool would not be complete without seeing  world famous football clubs - Liverpool FC &amp; EVERTON FC - all a five minute ride away. Liverpool is steeped in history and a two minute bus ride from outside the hotel will allow you to explore this wonderful and vibrant city. From its world famous waterfront, historic docklands, the famous Albert Dock, with its Maritime Museum, TATE Gallery, designer shopping, superb restaurants, theaters and much more. The hotel itself has recently been refurbished to a very high standard and consists of 15 rooms on two floors. Rooms are furnished to a very high standard and are extremely comfortable and spacious. Each having shower-en-suite, central heating, flat screen co-lour TV and DVD, tea and coffee, trouser press, hairdryer, iron and board, direct dial telephone and of course FREE "hot spot" high speed internet access for the discerning traveler. A full English breakfast and a five star welcome await you. Each clean and cozy room at Throstles Nest Hotel has an en suite shower, flat-screen TV with satellite channels and a DVD player. Full English breakfast is available in the morning. Throstles Nest Pub is next door and has a pool table and wide-screen TV, plus a bar and lounge.
Amenities - No Smoking Policy.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Among the finest galleries and collections are those housed in the National Museums Liverpool. These include the Walker, the national gallery of the north, recently refurbished to the acclaim of international critics, and the Museum of Liverpool Life, tracing the growth of the city and its people. Also on the world-famous waterfront are the Mersey-side Maritime Museum and Tate Liverpool, set in the stunningly refurbished Albert Dock complex. These beautifully restored dockside warehouses are now home to a dazzling collection of bars, cafes, restaurants, shops and other unique visitor attractions including The Beatles Story museum. This refurbished, 18th-century hotel is a short walk from Liverpool city cent-re. It has free internet access and is a 15-minute walk to Liverpool FC and Everton FC's football grounds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Double Room - Double En Suite Shower Room one king bed includes all the basic amenities.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>