<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10858382</Id><Name>Abbey House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52699</Id><Name>Reading</Name><CityId>52699</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>118 Cannught Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Reading</City><State /><Zip>RG30 2UF</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 118 959 0549</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>17542</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1906</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2754</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1931</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>359</Height><Bytes>19898</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1751</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>322</Height><Bytes>22377</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/38/17/1/2631759-Abbey-House-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2169</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Abbey House Hotel is located a 10-minute walk to Reading town centre, in a quiet residential area. It offers free Wi-Fi and free parking to all guests. Reading has many restaurants, clubs, cafs and shops to offer, including The Oracle shopping centre. The hotel is 20 miles from Heathrow Airport and Paddington Station in London can be reached in 25 minutes by rail. All rooms at The Abbey House have a power shower and most have an en suite bathroom. They also feature tea/coffee making facilities, a desk and a hairdryer. Public areas include a bar and a lounge. Cooked English and continental breakfasts are available at the buffet.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Abbey House Hotel is located a 10-minute walk to Reading town center, in a quiet residential area. It offers free WiFi and free parking to all guests. Reading has many restaurants, clubs, cafes and shops to offer, including The Oracle shopping center. The hotel is 20 miles from Heathrow Airport and Paddington Station in London can be reached in 25 minutes by rail.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single Room - Single Room offers one single bed. The 18 tastefully furnished and well appointed en-suite bedrooms are all equipped with remote colour television, direct dial telephone, work desk, tea and coffee making facilities, trouser press hair dryer and also free WI-FI Access from each room. In most of the rooms smoking is not permitted. There is ample parking available in the private car park situated at the rear of the hotel.

Twin Room - Twin Room offers two single beds. The 18 tastefully furnished and well appointed en-suite bedrooms are all equipped with remote colour television, direct dial telephone, work desk, tea and coffee making facilities, trouser press hair dryer and also free WI-FI Access from each room. In most of the rooms smoking is not permitted. There is ample parking available in the private car park situated at the rear of the hotel.

Double Room - Double Room offers one double bed. The 18 tastefully furnished and well appointed en-suite bedrooms are all equipped with remote colour television, direct dial telephone, work desk, tea and coffee making facilities, trouser press hair dryer and also free WI-FI Access from each room. In most of the rooms smoking is not permitted. There is ample parking available in the private car park situated at the rear of the hotel.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>