<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>1086919</Id><Name>Infinity Lifestyle Destination &amp; Spa</Name><Region><Id>18749</Id><Name>Koh Samui</Name><CityId>18749</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>BANG POR, SOI 4, KOH SAMUI, SURATTHANI</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>KO SAMUI</City><State /><Zip>84320</Zip><Country>THAILAND</Country><Tel>6623056609</Tel><Fax>6623056622</Fax><Email>DOSM@INFINITYSAMUI.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>34340</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2783</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>4096</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumbthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2588</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-14.jpg</Url><Width>319</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>24894</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-14</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-14thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1469</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>268</Height><Bytes>27086</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Hotel-Exterior-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>125</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2912</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Recreation-13.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>228</Height><Bytes>16623</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Recreation-13</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Recreation-13thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>147</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2881</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Suite-7.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>162</Height><Bytes>11326</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Suite-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Suite-7thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>207</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3057</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Suite-9.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>302</Height><Bytes>24210</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Suite-9</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Suite-9thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>111</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2297</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-10.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>211</Height><Bytes>14397</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-10</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-10thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>159</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2703</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-11.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>15833</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-11</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-11thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>168</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3121</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-12.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>222</Height><Bytes>14512</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-12</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-12thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>151</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2678</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>279</Height><Bytes>17676</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>120</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2560</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>206</Height><Bytes>12728</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>163</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2716</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>248</Height><Bytes>18073</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-5thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>135</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2842</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>243</Height><Bytes>17398</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-6thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>138</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2940</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-8.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17709</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/39/31/2631759-Infinity-Residences-and-Resort-Koh-Samui-Guest-Room-8thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>112</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1933</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui is trendsetting in its style combining state of the art facilities, outstanding service culture, unique dining concepts, and ultimate spa pampering and breathtaking views. Guaranteeing the utmost level of privacy and security, the property is conceived as an enclosed and private domain with permanent surveillance. Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui is committed to ensure their entire guests feel cared for at all times and they take great pride in providing exclusive properties with luxury and contemporary finishing. Their General Manager has worked in the best resorts worldwide and knows what it takes to bring unique luxury to make your stay one to remember forever. There 65 pool residences with 1, 2, 3 or 4 bedrooms and bathrooms offer dazzling sea and jungle views. Every residence has a fully equipped contemporary open kitchen of excellence next to the dining area, a luxury living room with design furniture and contemporary art, luxury bedrooms and bathrooms with king size beds, a private terrace and plunge or lap pool Don't forget their state of the art restaurant, pool bar, gym, and fitness. Book them for a romantic hideaway, a honeymoon, a wedding, a family vacation, a friend vacation, a golf holiday, a business gathering, a meeting, a holiday get-together or a single retreat: Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui is perfect for those who want security, luxury and privacy with stunning sea views. With easy access to the beach, dining, shopping and nightlife their luxury contemporary private apartments, villas and penthouses will turn your stay into a tropical delight. Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui is one of the most revolutionary destinations in the world combining breathtaking beauty of unspoiled nature with a sophisticated contemporary design. Guest accommodations consist of 65 residences with overwhelming sea views. They represent a contemporary interpretation of modern and tropical living. During construction Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui became the winner of many renowned property awards. All residences have private entrances from their tranquil gardens and are connected by walkways, which are easily accessible with buggies. All residences feature one or more outdoor terraces with sun decks, dining table and a unique blue water element like pool, hot tub or Jacuzzi. The residences are divided into 7 categories with 1 - 2 - 3 - 4 bedrooms and bathrooms: Sovereign Penthouse with 3 or 4 bedrooms, Sovereign Suite with 3 bedrooms, Imperial and Sovereign Penthouse with 3 bedrooms, Imperial Suite and Imperial Villa Penthouse with 2 bedrooms, Executive Suite with 1 or 2 bedrooms, Executive Duplex Villa with 1 or 2 bedrooms and Garden Villa with 2 bedrooms. The interiors offer the very highest standard of luxury and each residence provides guests with the ultimate in residential comfort. All bedrooms have King-size beds and are connected to private bathrooms with unique bathtub, separate showerhead, toilet, double vanity washbasin and amenities. All have walk-in closets and are equipped with LCD TV and DVD player. All residences have a fully equipped contemporary open. Every living room is decorated with design furniture, contemporary art, modern lighting, LCD TV, DVD player and IPod player. You will also find an elegant entrance, a storage room, a separate rest room, build-in air conditioning, a lazy chair and so much more. When you think of Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui, think of open plan, spaciousness, contemporary vibe and stunning views! All residences are inspired by contemporary design and complemented by verdant vistas. Wireless broadband connections are available in all resort accommodations and public areas. All residences have identical stunning views and facilities. The hotel also offers Barbecue area, Dry cleaning, Plunge pool, Reception and Squash court.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Infinity Residences and Resort Koh Samui is redefining global standards for vacationing in an exclusive luxury resort embedded in a high-end holiday destination. Infinity Residences and Infinity Residences and Resort Koh with overlooking the stunning bay of Bang Po and nearby island of Koh Phangan. Koh Samui airport is only 20 Km from Infinity Residences and Resort and a mere one hour flight South of Bangkok or East of Phuket. There are daily flights to Singapore, Hong Kong and Kuala Lumpur. REFERENCE POINTS: Bang Po Beach: 3 minutes down the hill, Na thon harbour: 10 minutes, Chaweng Beach road: 20 minutes, Bophut beach: 15 minutes, Bangrak beach and Big Buddha: 20 minutes, Santibury Country Golf Club: 8 minutes, Fisherman village: 15 minutes, Big C and Tesco Lotus: 15 minutes, Samui International Airport: 20 minutes, Bang Taling Nam District: 15 minutes, Nightlife: 20 minutes. Koh Phangan: 10 minutes drive to the main Ferry pier, and then 30 minutes speed boat ride.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>One bedroom executive duplex - One bedroom executive duplex offers one king bed with sea view with amenities like Alarm clock, Balcony / Terrace, Bathrobe, Bathroom amenities, Cable / Satellite TV, CD player, Ceiling fan, Color TV, Crockery / Cutlery, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Internet access, Jacuzzi / Whirlpool / Spa bath, Laundry service, Microwave oven, Mini bar, Radio, Refrigerator, Room service, Safe, Stove / Oven, Tea and coffee making facilities, Telephone, Toaster, Valet service, Video player, Voicemail and Washing machine. The Executive Duplex is an offer a refreshing plunge pool in front of the Master Bedroom. A fully equipped contemporary open kitchen, an inviting dining and living room, an outdoor terrace, all overlooking the dazzling Gulf of Thailand, decorated with design furniture, contemporary art and modern lighting. You will also find a storage room, safety deposit boxes, rest room, build-in air conditioning, a lazy chair, LCD TV, DVD player, IPod player.

One bedroom executive suite - One bedroom Executive Suite offers one king bed with sea view with amenities like Alarm clock, Balcony / Terrace, Bathrobe, Bathroom amenities, Cable / Satellite TV, CD player, Ceiling fan, Color TV, Crockery / Cutlery, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Internet access, Jacuzzi / Whirlpool / Spa bath, Full Kitchen, Laundry service, Microwave oven, Mini bar, Radio, Refrigerator, Room service, Stove / Oven, Tea and coffee making facilities, Telephone, Toaster, Valet service, Video player, Voicemail and Washing machine. One bedroom Executive Suite with lap pool is equipped with walk-in closets and is equipped with LCD TV and DVD player; bathroom has a big round bathtub, separate shower, toilet, double vanity washbasin, IPod player, and the fully equipped contemporary open. You will also find an elegant entrance, a storage room, and safety deposit boxes, separate rest room, build-in air conditioning, lazy chair.

Two bedroom executive duplex - Two bedroom executive duplex offers two king beds with amenities like Alarm clock, Balcony / Terrace, Bathrobe, Bathroom amenities, Cable / Satellite TV, CD player, Ceiling fan, Color TV, Crockery / Cutlery, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Internet access, Jacuzzi / Whirlpool / Spa bath, Laundry service, Microwave oven, Mini bar, Radio, Refrigerator, Room service, Safe, Stove / Oven, Tea and coffee making facilities, Telephone, Toaster, Valet service, Video player, Voicemail and Washing machine. One Master Bedroom in front of the private plunge pool, a fully equipped contemporary open kitchen, an inviting dining and living room, an outside terrace, all overlooking the dazzling Gulf of Thailand, decorated with design furniture, contemporary art and modern lighting. You will also find a storage room, safety deposit boxes, rest room, build-in air conditioning, a lazy chair, LCD TV, DVD player, IPod player.

Two bedroom executive suite - Two bedroom executive suite offers two king beds with Alarm clock, Balcony / Terrace, Bathrobe, Bathroom amenities, Cable / Satellite TV, CD player, Ceiling fan, Color TV, Crockery / Cutlery, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Internet access, Jacuzzi / Whirlpool / Spa bath, Laundry service, Microwave oven, Mini bar, Radio, Refrigerator, Room service, Stove / Oven, Tea and coffee making facilities, Telephone, Toaster, Valet service, Video player, Voicemail and Washing machine. Executive Suites offers 11 meter private lap pool.The bathrooms are located in the bedrooms with bathtub, separate shower, toilet, double vanity washbasin, amenities and modern blue lighting creating magical effects. The Executive Suites also offers dining room, living room, open kitchen, LCD TV, DVD player, IPod player. You will also find an elegant entrance, a storage room, safety deposit boxes, separate rest room, build-in air conditioning, lazy chair, etc in this two bedroom Executive Suite.

Two bedroom Imperial Suite - Two bedroom Imperial Suite offers two king beds with Alarm clock, Balcony / Terrace, Bathrobe, Cable / Satellite TV, CD player, Ceiling fan, Color TV, Crockery / Cutlery, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Internet access, Jacuzzi / Whirlpool / Spa bath, Laundry service, Microwave oven, Mini bar, Radio, Refrigerator, Room service, Stove / Oven, Tea and coffee making facilities, Telephone, Toaster, Valet service, Video player, Voicemail and Washing machine.The Imperial Suite or Imperial Villa Penthouse offers sea views. There are two types of Imperial Suites: Eight ground floor Imperial Suites with a 15 meter lap or Imperial Villa Penthouses featuring a plunge pool, walk-in closets and are equipped with LCD TV and DVD player. All bathrooms have bathtub, separate shower, toilet, double vanity washbasin, modern lighting, LCD TV and DVD player. It also offers a storage room, safety deposit boxes, rest room, build-in air conditioning, lazy chair, IPod player.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant Smoking Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Massage</Code><Text>Massage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>