<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10874726</Id><Name>Kinmel Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52610</Id><Name>Llandudno</Name><CityId>52610</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Central Promenade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Llandudno, Conwy</City><State /><Zip>LL30 1AR</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01492 876171</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/09/71/2631759-Kinmel-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>24773</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Kinmel-Hotel-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/09/71/2631759-Kinmel-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2088</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/09/71/2631759-Kinmel-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3330</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Kinmel-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/09/71/2631759-Kinmel-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2110</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Occupying a prime seafront position with spectacular views of the sea, offers free Wi-Fi and parking. This family run hotel is the ideal destination for visitors to Llandudno "The Queen of Welsh Resorts". Located just a stone's throw from Venue Cymru (theater and conference center) and numerous shopping facilities and attractions, it offers the perfect combination of convenience, quality and comfort. Originally built in the 19th Century, this Victorian property has been extensively renovated, with great care being taken to preserve the traditional features and charm of the building. This family run Hotel prides itself on cultivating a home-from-home atmosphere, with the emphasis on comfort, relaxation and an exemplary commitment to customer satisfaction. Whether business or leisure, a family holiday or a couples retreat, Kinmel Hotel is ideally suited for all types of traveler. They are also available for conferences, craft fairs, shows, birthdays, and anniversaries.
The hotel also offers free breakfast.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Nestled in the heart of Llandudno, Wales's largest coastal resort, the Kinmel Hotel has long been a welcome feature on the seafront promenade. Boasting not only views of the sea, but from the rear the Snowdonia mountain range, it truly exemplifies all that is great about the Welsh landscape.
Centrally located in the heart of Llandudno the Kinmel Hotel is both convenient and accessible. It's just a 5 minute drive off the A470 by car, or alternatively only a six minute walk from Llandudno Rail Station which offers transport links to most major destinations across the UK. The nearest international airport is Liverpool's John Lennon Airport, which is approximately an hour and a half's drive along the A55.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>CLASSIC - DOUBLE - Classic Double offers one double or two twin beds. When it comes to accommodation, each of the 28 en-suite guest rooms are designed upon the foundations of comfort, relaxation and indulgence. Indeed, the hotel has recently installed a lift, providing access to all the floors. Each room is brightly decorated and equipped with all the necessary amenities needed to ensure a pleasant, stress-free stay, including digital television, free Wi-Fi, telephone, hairdryer and tea &amp; coffee making facilities.Please note a twin room needs to be requested on booking and is subject to availability.

SUPERIOR - DOUBLE - Superior Double offers one double or two twin beds.When it comes to accommodation, each of the 28 en-suite guest rooms are designed upon the foundations of comfort, relaxation and indulgence. Indeed, the hotel has recently installed a lift, providing access to all the floors. Each room is brightly decorated and equipped with all the necessary amenities needed to ensure a pleasant, stress-free stay, including digital television, free Wi-Fi, telephone, hairdryer and tea &amp; coffee making facilities. Please note a twin room needs to be requested on booking and is subject to availability.

FAMILY - ROOM - family Room offers one double and two twin beds.When it comes to accommodation, each of the 28 en-suite guest rooms are designed upon the foundations of comfort, relaxation and indulgence. Indeed, the hotel has recently installed a lift, providing access to all the floors. Each room is brightly decorated and equipped with all the necessary amenities needed to ensure a pleasant, stress-free stay, including digital television, free Wi-Fi, telephone, hairdryer and tea &amp; coffee making facilities.Please can you indicate at time of booking whether it is 4 or 3 occupancy.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>