<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10120674</Id><Name>Delano Marrakech</Name><Region><Id>17562</Id><Name>Marrakech</Name><CityId>17562</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Angle Avenue Echouhada et Rue des Temples</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Marrakech</City><State /><Zip>40000</Zip><Country>Morocco</Country><Tel>00212 (0)524424242</Tel><Fax>00212 (0)524424244</Fax><Email>delanomarrakech-reservations@mhgc.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327001-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1454</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327001-photo-not-available-small.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1454</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Delano Marrakech is a plush 5-star superior hotel offering elegant accommodation in the heart of Marrakech. Highlights include a luxury spa, gym and a choice of restaurants. Marrakech city centre boasts a rich architectural and cultural heritage encompassing an abundance of historical sites and entertainment. Nearby places of interest include the Royal Palace, Rue Bab Agnaou and Djemaa el-Fna, a huge open-air square in the city centre, filled with an eclectic mix of street entertainers, dancers and food stalls. Local bus services provide fast and easy access to other popular Marrakech destinations. The hotel is housed in a contemporary mid-rise building with a metal mesh-look overlay. Facilities include a luxurious spa with an indoor swimming pool, hammams, a beauty salon, Jacuzzi, sauna, relaxation room and treatment rooms. There is also an outdoor swimming pool, gym and an exercise studio. Free Wi-Fi is available throughout the premises. Deluxe rooms are 45sqm and decorated in an opulent style with silk and velvet. They feature a large sitting area and a wrought iron faux balcony with city views. Amenities include a flat-screen satellite/cable TV, mini-bar and an iPod dock. The marble en-suite bathrooms feature a bathtub with integrated shower and Malin &amp; Goetz toiletries. Pomiroeu offers Mediterranean cuisine. Galerie is situated in the circular lobby of the hotel and offers international dishes. The Sky Lounge boasts a relaxed atmosphere courtesy of its comfortable day beds, dipping pool and great views of the city. It serves a variety of Moroccan dishes. Namazake is located on the rooftop and serves Japanese cuisine. Free parking is possible onsite. The hotel provides 24-hour reception, concierge and room service.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>