<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>103213</Id><Name>Mediterranean Suite</Name><Region><Id>21196</Id><Name>Salou</Name><CityId>18374</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>JOANOT MARTORELL S/N</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SALOU</City><State /><Zip>43840</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>977388558</Tel><Fax>977381988</Fax><Email>PODIUM@IBERSOL.ES</Email><Url /></Address><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.0732799</Latitude><Longitude>1.1502207</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/80/28/51/SAOU-MED-1.jpg</Url><Width>270</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>15520</Bytes><Caption>SAOU-MED-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/80/28/51/SAOU-MED-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>52</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1461</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Totally recommended for travellers looking for a nice stay in Salou, without covering the whole budget in accommodation.**If your booking falls over the Easter period (21/04/11 to 24/04/11) please note that we have a very special rate offer, and you could also be accommodated in their sister apartment Salou Suite. This will be informed to you upon arrival. Both apartments provide the similar quality and standards.**  This white-coloured block of flats was built in 1987, but it was completely renovated in 2000. Services offered by the property includes cafeter a, restaurant, Sat TV area, swimming pool, parking (direct pay), 24-hrs reception,money exchange, safebox (direct pay), mini-club for children and more...  Located in the touristic and comercial area of Salou, just 5 minutes walking from the nearest beach, and it takes only 15 minutes by bus to get to Port  Aventura Theme Park. Address: C/Joanot Martorell, s/n, 43840 Salou (Tarragona), Spain. Tel: +34 977 352 401 -From Reus Airport there is one bus line to Salou  (www.empresaplana.es). -From Barcelona Airport there is one bus line to Pineda-Salou-Cambrils (www.empresaplana.es). -From Bcn Train Stations, first  taking any train to Tarragona Rail Station, and there change to Salou-Cambrils rail.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Guest Rooms - Apartments are distributed within a living room with sofa bed, completely equipped kitchen, bathroom, air conditioning and heating, a fantastic balcony and, depending on the capacity, one or two twin-bed rooms.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>