<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10450235</Id><Name>Club I Giardini Di Cala Ginepro</Name><Region><Id>20926</Id><Name>Gulf of Orosei</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Viale Cala Ginepro,97</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>08028</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
The Hotel Club I Giardini di Cala Ginepro, is set in the peaceful bay of Cala Ginepro, in the Gulf of Orosei. The sober and elegant hotel, divided in three different buildings of two or three storeys, set in the green of a big olive grove and beautiful gardens rich in various bright colours of Mediterranean plants, converge towards the Piazzetta del Sole.

Restaurant
The restaurant of the hotel is well known for the excellent cuisine and the faultless service. All our dishes are based on our local traditional cuisine using only the freshest ingredients.
The bars of the hotel are well located and open all day.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
The hotel has three swimming pools (one reserved for children) equipped with sun-beds and beach-umbrellas, children play park, beach volley, bowls, table-tennis, tennis, mini-football, canoes and windsurf.
In some period of the years ,(from 01/06 to 21/09) it is possible to take advantage, with the payment of the club card starting from 4 years age, of beach umbrellas and sunbeds staring from the third row (beach umbrellas and sunbeds located in the first and in the second row are non-reservable and are payable directly at the spot, according to hotel availability), entertainment, mini-club, piano-bar, sport equipments and collective sport courses.
Check - In; From 3.00 pm
Check - out; by 10.00 am</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>