<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10463238</Id><Name>Apostoli Palace</Name><Region><Id>21076</Id><Name>Venice</Name><CityId>17175</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Sestiere Cannaregio, 4702</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>30121</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Dining-4.jpg</Url><Width>401</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>27520</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Dining-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Dining-4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>58</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1754</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>401</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>30169</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Hotel-Exterior-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>58</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1852</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3585</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumbthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2248</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>401</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>35536</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Guest-Room-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>58</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1833</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>401</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>35558</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/31/65/01/2631759-Apostoli-Palace-Venice-Guest-Room-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>58</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1840</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Tucked away in a charming and pictoresque neighborhood of the historic city of Venice, a short, five-minute walk from Saint Mark's Square and the Rialto Bridge, Apostoli Palace offers the possibility to discover an authentic Venice where the Venetians still live out their daily lives amidst shaded alleys, sunlit squares, and centuries-old art and architecture.The structure dates to the mid-fifteenth century and was completely restored in 2002 to ensure maximum comfort and a high standard of quality.  Each room is dedicated to one of the apostles in honor of the nearby Church of the Holy Apostles. All of them are fully equipped with satellite color television, air-conditioning and heating with independent thermostat, direct-dial telephone, Internet WI-FI, safety deposit box, hairdryer, and a private bathroom in mosaic with tub or shower.  The fabrics, the Murano glass chandeliers, the old-style furnishings, and the hand-made Venetian flooring are the creations of some of the more important Venetian artisan workshops and combine to create an inviting and relaxing enviornment immersed in the surrounding magic that is Venice. In addition, the attentive and qualified staff is available at all times to help you plan and enjoy your memorable sojourn in Venice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A tax has been imposed by the city for stays beginning 1 October 2012, and will be collected directly at the property. The tax ranges from EUR 1 to EUR 5 per person, per night. The amount has been determined by the local administration, depends on the star rating of hotel and the season of travel.  This tax does not apply from the 6th consecutive night of stay onwards, to residents of Venice City and children under 10 years of age. Please note that further exemptions may apply.  For additional details on this tax please check with the hotel property at check-in.&lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>From the C D'Oro landing, clients can easily walk to Apostoli Palace in five minutes with no bridges.  At the end of Calle di C D'Oro turn to the right, and continue along Strada Nuova to Campo dei SS Apostoli.  Turn left and follow  Salizada del Pistor, Rio Ter dei Franceschi, Rio Ter dei SS Apostoli, and Rio Ter Barba Frutariol.

From Fondamenta Nuove, guests should turn right from the boat landing and, having crossed over the large bridge, turn left onto Salizada dei Specchieri.  Continue through Campo dei Gesuiti, along Salizada Sheriman, Salizada L. Borgato, and into Rio Ter Barba Frutariol.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>STANDARD - ROOM - Room offers a queen size bed for maximun two people in, with Air conditioning , Cable / Satellite TV, Color TV, Ensuite / Private bathroom with shower, Hairdryer, Heating, Internet access, Mini bar, Non-smoking rooms, Room service and Telephone.

SUPERIOR - ROOM - Room offers a double bed or two twin beds for maximun two people in with Air conditioning , Cable / Satellite TV, Color TV, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Heating, Internet access, Mini bar, Non-smoking rooms, Room service and Telephone.

TRIPLE - ROOM - Room offers a double bed or a twin bed and one extra sofa bed for maximun 3 people in, with Air conditioning , Cable / Satellite TV, Color TV, Ensuite / Private bathroom, Hairdryer, Heating, Internet access, Mini bar, Non-smoking rooms, Room service and Telephone.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>