<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10534030</Id><Name>Holiday Inn Express Hotel &amp; Suites DALLAS WEST</Name><Region><Id>21487</Id><Name>Downtown</Name><CityId>19485</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4321 Communications Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Dallas</City><State /><Zip>75211</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (214) 3310505</Tel><Fax>+1 (214) 3310522</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Experience Dallas Area Hotel's Convenience Situated in a quiet area off I-30 and just minutes from the bustle of downtown is the award-winning Holiday Inn Express® Dallas West hotel. An indoor pool and free Wi-Fi access are just a few of the perks we offer our valued guests when they choose to stay at this state-of-the-art facility. Corporate travelers appreciate the executive boardroom and the spacious meeting room. We also offer a Business Center, which has a copy and print station, so you can stay connected to the office and up-to-date on projects. And if you're doing business with nearby companies, Stewart &amp; Stevenson, Ingersoll Rand, Tandy Brands Accessories and AT&amp;T are close to our hotel's property in Dallas, TX. Because we're near the Cowboys Stadium and the Rangers Ballpark, it's easy for sports fans to catch a game. Downtown Dallas and the West End are also popular attractions among our hotel's patrons. In Dallas, TX, other notable sites such as the Sixth Floor Museum, Fair Park, Lone Star Park and the Verizon Theater are just a short drive from our address. After a day of sightseeing in Dallas, the hotel and its indoor pool and spa can help you unwind. You can keep up your workout routine in the Fitness Center, which has individual TVs on each machine, and then join us for the complimentary, hot Express Start Breakfast Bar. Don't forget that we have special packages, including tours of the Cowboys Stadium, so book today!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Suburban, suburban</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ComplimentaryBreakfast</Code><Text>Complimentary Breakfast</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>