<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10557647</Id><Name>City Club Hotel</Name><Region><Id>64379</Id><Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>55 W 44th Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York City</City><State /><Zip>10036</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>2129215500</Tel><Fax>212.944.5544</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Shaping the future of Hospitality in the spirit of the past, the City Club Hotel combines the scale and tradition of a private club with the first rate services and amenities of a modern luxury hotel. Located near the Theater District on vibrant West 44th Street between Fifth and Sixth Avenue and Avenue of the Americas, it offers the neighborhood and city nothing less than an urban cultural oasis for the refined traveler.&lt;br&gt;Hotelier Jeff Klein has remained ardently committed to preserving the relaxed privacy of the buildings former incarnation as a gentlemens club and private sanctuary for the citys power brokers. Dating from 1904, and nestled on the New York Citys Club Row. The seven-story, 65 room hotels discrete, elegant façade is in harmony with prestigious neighbors like the New York Yacht, Harvard and Penn Clubs. The intimate duplex lobby that incorporates a mezzanine guest lounge furthers the hotels twin themes of discretion and luxury.&lt;br&gt;The hotels interior designer, Jeffrey Bilhuber, regards the City Club as an important step in the evolution of his New American Classicism, a seductive mix of classic materials and simple forms utilized in a refreshing and inspired manner. The blend of familiar and innovative appeals to modernists and traditionalists alike, creating a continuity of style while nurturing a modern tradition.&lt;br&gt;Bilhubers emphasis on comfort and luxury is evident in every facet of the hotel, whose handsome guest rooms feature wall coverings simulating hand drawn plaster, Honduran mahogany, Frette bed linens, and down feather beds. The City Club Hotel also offers three Grand Duplex suites, each with their own private terrace. All accommodations contain voluminous chocolate marble and chrome bathrooms offering CO Bigelow bath products.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located on 44th Street between 5th and 6th Avenue in Midtown, steps fromt the theater district and 5th Avenue shopping.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>PETITE - ROOM - A comfortably spacious room with one full-size bed, smothered in feather down bedding. 195 sq. feet.  Multi-line phone with voice mail, Complimentary wireless high-speed Internet access. CD/DVD/TV speakers, Frette robes, Bathrooms featuring voluminous chocolate-marble, C.O. Bigelow amenities. Minibar stocked with Dean &amp; DeLuca delicacies.

QUEEN LUXE - ROOM - Airy open room with one queen-size feather down bed. Located on front or side of hotel , some with city views and ultra-suede daybed.  295 square feet. Multi-line phone with voice mail. Complimentary wireless high-speed Internet access. CD/DVD/TV speakers, Frette robes, bathrooms featuring voluminous chocolate-marble, C.O. Bigelow amenities. Minibar stocked with Dean &amp; DeLuca delicacies.

KING LUXE - ROOM - Airy open room with ultra-suede daybed, one king-size feather down bed, located at the front or side of the hotel. Some with city views.  365 square feet.   Multi-line phone with voice mail. Complimentary wireless high-speed Internet access. CD/DVD/TV speakers, Frette robes, bathrooms featuring voluminous chocolate-marble, C.O. Bigelow amenities. Minibar stocked with Dean &amp; DeLuca delicacies.

LUXE DOUBLE DOUBLE - ROOM - Airy open room with ultra-suede daybed, two full-size feather down beds, located at the front of the hotel with city views.   365 sq. ft.  Multi-line phone with voice mail. Complimentary wireless high-speed Internet access. CD/DVD/TV speakers, Frette robes, bathrooms featuring voluminous chocolate-marble, C.O. Bigelow amenities. Minibar stocked with Dean &amp; DeLuca delicacies.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>