<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10573892</Id><Name>The Quincy</Name><Region><Id>21948</Id><Name>Capitol Hill - Dupont Circle</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1823 L Street Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20036</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>202-223-4320</Tel><Fax>1-202-293-4977</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Classic comfort. Contemporary atmosphere. Each of the 99 chic studio suites offer the very best in accommodations, with more than a few welcome surprises. Sometimes, it's the little things that make the biggest difference. The morning paper. A crisp, clean shirt. The Quincy believes every day should get off to a great start. That's why, provides the essential amenities needed to kickstart a round of intense meetings or a casual afternoon of sight-seeing. A distinct combination of metropolitan style and understated ambiance is what makes a stay so memorable. Add superlative service and beautiful surroundings-just a few of the ways The Quincy gets it right. Boutique style and superior comfort at an unbeatable location. And it gets better. There are many hotels in Washington, DC. One of them gets it right-inside and out. The Quincy's location is not a few blocks away from, or just around the corner from - but precisely in the middle of. At 18th and L,  at the epicenter of DC's downtown scene. The K Street power brokers, the nightlife on M, the restaurants on 19th and the late-night stroll to Dupont Circle.You will need to walk five minutes for your meeting at the white house.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>While the surroundings at the Quincy are truly enticing a journey into the surrounding city is sure to enhance the guest experience. The hotel is located near the corner of Connecticut and K Street, mere moments away from the best in D.C. offerings: the White House, the Lincoln Memorial, monuments on the National Mall and much more. There are also a variety of unique and tempting eateries nearby. And if travels take beyond the walking distance, The Quincy is convenient to 2 Metro stations; Farragut North-Red Line, and Farragut West- Orange/Blue Lines.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>King Studio - Room with one king bed includes a desk and a kitchenette complete with microwave, refrigerator, coffee maker, wet bar, complimentary  high speed internet in-room, 27-inch flat-screen television and pay-per-play Nintendo games, voice mail, complimentary daily newspaper and same-day dry cleaning service.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>