<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10704736</Id><Name>Blue Star</Name><Region><Id>20782</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>16664</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Katharades</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Crete - Ierapetra</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Islands</Country><Tel>28420 89113</Tel><Fax>2842089114</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Tha hotel has 155 fully furnished rooms which are well equipped with: bath, mini fridge, direct phone line, satellite TV, mini bar, hair-dryer,telephone device in the bathroom, safety deposit box (at a charge) and independently controlled air- conditioning. Most rooms have a view to the pool. Moreover, there are 2 specially equipped rooms for wheelchair access. 24hour Reception Service, internet corner-wifi HotSpot (at a charge), mail service, car rental, taxi, medical care, wireless internet access throughout the communal areas, wake up call service. 
Also, the hotel is surrounded with beautiful gardens and has 2 main pools, active swimming pool with salt water by the sea and relax pool with fresh water in the main building (sunbeds and umbrellas are free of charge in pools and on the private beach), Free parking in hotel, playground, mini market, pool bar, theatre, restaurant with Mediterranean dishes and a large variety of breakfast and dinner choices. Athletic facilities, tennis court, basketball court, ping – pong table, billiard, marine sports on request at 500m, scuba diving at 3km, horse riding at 4km.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel complex is located in the southern coast of Crete directly on the dark sandy/pebbled beach opposite from the island Chrissi where exists the better climate of Mediterranean. It offers pleasant vacations in a beautiful environment, and it is located approximately 4,5 km from the more southern city of Europe Ierapetra.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>