<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10820804</Id><Name>Go Native Mayfair</Name><Region><Id>52927</Id><Name>West End &amp; Marble Arch</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>10 Lees Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W1K 6LL</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 221 2028</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Hotel-Exterior-4.jpg</Url><Width>485</Width><Height>363</Height><Bytes>23930</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Hotel-Exterior-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Hotel-Exterior-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2050</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Hotel-Exterior-4_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3223</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Hotel-Exterior-4_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Hotel-Exterior-4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2077</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>485</Width><Height>363</Height><Bytes>27206</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2207</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>485</Width><Height>363</Height><Bytes>24586</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2059</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>485</Width><Height>363</Height><Bytes>19953</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/35/81/1/2631759-Go-Native-Mayfair-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1771</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Part of the historic Grosvenor Estate, this beautiful Georgian building is Go Natives latest premium property. A 300 year-old mews in Mayfair, it has been sympathetically renovated to provide one and two-bedroom suites - each boasting their own theme and named in honour of a notable architect. Populated with British-built furniture, feature fabrics and artistic flashes of English humour, it is both comforting and comfortable. Perfect for business professionals and discerning city visitors, these new properties offer a luxury haven in London's ultimate postcode. Lees Place is also just a short walk from Marble Arch and Bond Street underground stations making it extremely well connected in the bustling city of London.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Lees Place is also just a short walk from Marble Arch and Bond Street underground stations making it extremely well connected in the bustling city of London.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Classic Apartment - Offering more room, not one room, the Classic one-bed apartments at Mayfair are ideal urban spaces. Consisting of separate living and sleeping quarters for an enhanced city living experience, each provides privacy and comfort in a stylish home-away-from-home apartment. For even more space please book One Bedroom Premium Apartments. Desk Laundry Facilities Lounge Area Telephone Toaster Kitchen Double Bed Microwave Cable/Satellite TV Weekly Room Service Shower - separate Lift/Elevator Access Tea/Coffee Making Fridge - Full size Cots Available Alarm Clock DVD Player Non-Smoking Television Wireless Internet Dishwasher Linen and Towels Provided

Premium Apartment - The premium one-bed apartments are furnished in line with the Classic apartments but benefit from additional floorspace and a separate dining area.. Separate living and sleeping quarters for an enhanced city living experience, each provides privacy and comfort in a stylish home-away-from-home apartment. For two separate bedrooms and a wealth of space please book Two Bedroom Apartments Desk Laundry Facilities Lounge Area Telephone Toaster Kitchen Double Bed Microwave Cable/Satellite TV Weekly Room Service Shower - separate Lift/Elevator Access Tea/Coffee Making Fridge - Full size Cots Available Alarm Clock DVD Player Non-Smoking Television Wireless Internet Dishwasher Linen and Towels Provided

Premium Apartment - As with the studio and family-sized properties, these two-bedroom apartments give generous city space for impressive value. Consisting of two, separate double-bedrooms and additional living quarters, plus a kitchen and a bathroom, they are the ideal solution for families and groups of three or four. Desk Dishwasher Linen and Towels Provided Telephone Views 2nd bathroom Laundry Facilities Lounge Area Cable/Satellite TV Weekly Room Service Kitchen Double Bed Microwave Fridge - Full size Cots Available Shower - separate Lift/Elevator Access Tea/Coffee Making Television Wireless Internet Alarm Clock DVD Player Non-Smoking Toaster</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>