<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10833569</Id><Name>Albion House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>29 Argyle Square</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>WC1H 8AL</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 837 0571</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/LOGO0-20121122-103235-182.jpg</Url><Width>82</Width><Height>40</Height><Bytes>905</Bytes><Caption>LOGO0-20121122-103235-182</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/LOGO0-20121122-103235-182.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>143</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1341</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/PROP0-20121122-103235-174.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>24283</Bytes><Caption>PROP0-20121122-103235-174</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/PROP0-20121122-103235-174.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>116</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3095</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/REST0-20121122-103235-219.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>23017</Bytes><Caption>REST0-20121122-103235-219</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/REST0-20121122-103235-219.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>116</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2930</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/TBNL0-20121122-103235-159.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2675</Bytes><Caption>TBNL0-20121122-103235-159</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/TBNL0-20121122-103235-159.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2264</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/ROOM0-20121122-103235-196.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>24285</Bytes><Caption>ROOM0-20121122-103235-196</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/ROOM0-20121122-103235-196.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>116</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3094</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/ROOM1-20121122-103235-235.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>18646</Bytes><Caption>ROOM1-20121122-103235-235</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/49/09/1/ROOM1-20121122-103235-235.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>116</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2685</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>If you're looking for accommodations in the Kings Cross area, look no further than the rooms at the Albion House B&amp;B Hotel! An ideal solution in London for everyone, couples, groups of friends, and families, in an elegant Victorian townhouse. The Albion House Hotel is on the quiet Argyle Square, just a few minutes away from the St. Pancras station and subway station and offers wi-fi internet access, ironing service and free parking during the week after 6:30 pm until following day 8am. Weekends free parking from Saturday 2:30 pm until Monday 08:00 am. The hotel's 13 rooms are all uniquely decorated to best meet the guests' different needs with simply and comfortably modern furnished interiors. The hotel staff will be happy to provide you with any tourist information you may need to visit London, revealing the most charming sites, countless museums and monuments and best and most exciting events. The Albion House Hotel provides a buffet breakfast - complete with toast, fruit juice, milk, eggs, jam and cereal - included in the room rate.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>One of the most beautiful European capitals, an exciting and cosmopolitan city, rich in history and culture! London awaits you at the Albion House bed &amp; breakfast Hotel with comfortable rooms just minutes from Kings Cross. The Albion House Hotel is centrally located in London zone 1 close to all the fascinating sites of this enchanting city, easily accessed by subway or bus from the nearby stops. The Albion House Hotel is conveniently located near connections to the main airports - Heathrow, Luton and Gatwick - thanks to public transportation and the St. Pancras train station, the terminal for the Eurostar train that connects London with Paris.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>SINGLE - ROOM - Single Room offers one single bed. Recently renovated, the spacious rooms at the Albion House Hotel are comfortable and clean, with private en suite shower and WC and modern services to assure you a pleasant stay in London.

DOUBLE - ROOM - Double Room offers one double bed. Recently renovated, the spacious rooms at the Albion House Hotel are comfortable and clean, with private en suite shower and WC and modern services to assure you a pleasant stay in London.

TRIPPLE - ROOM - Triple Room offers three twin beds. Recently renovated, the spacious rooms at the Albion House Hotel are comfortable and clean, with private en suite shower and WC and modern services to assure you a pleasant stay in London.

TWIN - ROOM - Twin Room offers two twin bed. Recently renovated, the spacious rooms at the Albion House Hotel are comfortable and clean, with private en suite shower and WC and modern services to assure you a pleasant stay in London.

QUAD - ROOM - Quad room offers two double bed.Recently renovated, the spacious rooms at the Albion House Hotel are comfortable and clean, with private en suite shower and WC and modern services to assure you a pleasant stay in London.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>