<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840518</Id><Name>Cleyro Serviced Apartments Bristol Finzels Reach</Name><Region><Id>52850</Id><Name>Bristol</Name><CityId>52416</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Castle Wharf, Finzels Reach</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bristol</City><State /><Zip>BS1 6BX</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>011441173253976</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Finzels Reach serviced apartments are located right in the heart of the city centre, within walking distance of Temple Meads train station, the Bristol Hippodrome and Cabot Circus; there is no more ideal location from which to explore Bristol. Apartments are part of a brand new development of luxury apartments with a high end finish and everything you need from a base to explore the city. Staying with Cleyro offers you so much more, you can expect a fully fitted designer kitchen, including an oven, microwave and fridge freezer, kettle and toaster. Lounge includes a two seat luxurious sofa to relax on; with a flat screen free-view TV and DVD player. The dining area has a dining table with four chairs and all the crockery and cutlery you would need. All bedrooms have wardrobes and plenty of storage space. Soft linens and towels are included for your stay. The bathroom is tiled from floor to ceiling and includes a contemporary glass door shower. All apartments come with a hairdryer, iron and ironing board as well as a washer/dryer. There are double-glazed windows to keep out all the hustle and bustle of the city, security self-locking doors and electronic fob access to enter the building and ensure your safety. At Cleyro work a little differently. They offer a personalized check in service, meeting you at the development to show you around. Therefore we ask you to please contact us after making your booking to arrange your check in time. Please note that operate a minimum stay of 2 nights during weekends.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Throughout the 18th and 19th centuries Finzels Reach developed to become the hub of Bristol's booming sugar industry. The name of the site is in honour of the industrialist and philanthropist called Conrad Finzel, the owner of the refinery where the development is now situated. Sugar being a major ingredient in the brewery industry, the site attracted a number of brewers. Most notably Georges Brewery, where you can still see the branding and insignias on some of the buildings that have been converted into offer  Finzels Reach accommodation, incorporating high quality contemporary architecture within the sites traditional surrounds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Deluxe Apartment - Deluxe Apartments offer contemporary living in the heart of Bristol. All deluxe apartments are fully furnished with everything necessary for a short or long term stay. With a with large open plan living rooms to relax in and free WIFI in all apartments you can feel at home.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>