<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840531</Id><Name>Brighton House</Name><Region><Id>52414</Id><Name>Brighton</Name><CityId>52414</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>52 Regency Square</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brighton</City><State /><Zip>BN1 2FF</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44 (0)1273 32 32 82</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/LOGO0-20121128-084022-383.jpg</Url><Width>82</Width><Height>40</Height><Bytes>1554</Bytes><Caption>LOGO0-20121128-084022-383</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/LOGO0-20121128-084022-383.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>143</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2580</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/PROP0-20121128-084022-388.jpg</Url><Width>579</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>16912</Bytes><Caption>PROP0-20121128-084022-388</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/PROP0-20121128-084022-388.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>115</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2041</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/TBNL0-20121128-084022-398.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2338</Bytes><Caption>TBNL0-20121128-084022-398</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/TBNL0-20121128-084022-398.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1704</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM0-20121128-084022-374.jpg</Url><Width>579</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>16912</Bytes><Caption>ROOM0-20121128-084022-374</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM0-20121128-084022-374.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>115</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2041</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM1-20121128-084022-355.jpg</Url><Width>550</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>13829</Bytes><Caption>ROOM1-20121128-084022-355</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM1-20121128-084022-355.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>110</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2084</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM2-20121128-084022-349.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>15139</Bytes><Caption>ROOM2-20121128-084022-349</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM2-20121128-084022-349.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>116</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2643</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM3-20121128-084022-369.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>12357</Bytes><Caption>ROOM3-20121128-084022-369</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/31/83/1/ROOM3-20121128-084022-369.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>116</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2338</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>In the Heart of Brighton, Christine and Lucho, welcome you to their Brighton House. We are proud to offer; comfortable, clean, fully en-suite guest accomodation in a recently refurbished, historic Regency Townhouse. 

"The Brighton House is a luxurious Regency hotel with Immaculate rooms" - The Lonely Planet Guide.

"Hospitality and comfort high on the agenda" - AA Britain's best B&amp;B quide.

We offer a large organic continental buffet style breakfast with long hours to enjoy it in. Please remember! WE ARE FULLY NON SMOKING, WE CANNOT CATER FOR LARGE GROUPS (i.e. Stag / Hen) NOR SMALL CHILDREN (under 12).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Brighton House is a 4 star guest house in Brighton city-centre. The BNB is conveniently situated close to the Brighton Centre conference venue as well as the city's other major conference centres, Brighton seafront, the historic Lanes and colourful North Laine, and the recently renovated Cultural Quarter.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Twin Room with Bathtub - This room is on the lower ground floor, courtyard, with two large single beds. Fully en-suite with bath and shower. Please note: although with natural light and ventilation this room has no view. Suitable for conference goers / workers. This room is also very cool during the summer months.

Superior Double Queen - This room is a large and comfortable room with queen size four poster bed (5'x6'6" / 150x200cm) on the first floor, with en-suite bath and shower head. This room overlooks the hotel courtyard and is considered very quiet and romantic by the couples who have stayed here.

Budget Single - Our single rooms are at the top of the hotel on the third and fourth floors. With en-suite showers they provide a very practical and economical resting place for our business and single travellers. Rooms on the third and fourth floor may not be suitable for non-ambulant persons (i.e. persons with difficulty climbing and or descending stairs &amp; fire-escapes unaided) Please be sure to advise us should this be a concern.

Triple Room - This room is on the lower ground floor, square-side, but benefits largely from the afternoon sun for natural light. This is one of our larger rooms and with three large single beds and can accommodate three guests very comfortably.

Standard Double - Our standard double rooms on the second, third and fourth floor are spacious ensuite rooms offering all the comforts and room facilities both seasoned travellers and holiday-makers expect. Rooms on the third and fourth floor may not be suitable for non-ambulant persons (i.e. persons with difficulty climbing and or descending stairs &amp; fire-escapes unaided) Please be sure to advise us should this be a concern.

Superior Double with Balcony - Room 36 is one of our most popular hotel rooms, primarily due to the luxurious super-king size bed (6'x6" / 180x200cm) along with the floor to ceiling bay windows, which give access to our balcony over the historic Regency Square and seafront view.

Single Room - Our larger single rooms on the second and third floors are comfortably spacious single rooms with ensuite facilities and the bonus of a small double bed. Rooms on the third and fourth floor may not be suitable for non-ambulant persons (i.e. persons with difficulty climbing and or descending stairs &amp; fire-escapes unaided). Please be sure to advise us should this be a concern. In addition we have a delightful en-suite first floor Single room with a balcony overlooking the Square. Single travellers will find this room offers plenty of space with the added benefit of the shared balcony.

Twin Room - This twin room is on the second floor, city view, with two large single beds .Fully en-suite with shower. We have found these rooms to be popular with friends  and small groups travelling together.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>