<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859033</Id><Name>The Clifton Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52724</Id><Name>Scarborough</Name><CityId>52724</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Queens Parade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Scarborough</City><State /><Zip>YO12 7HX</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>011448712210206</Tel><Fax>0844 873 2942</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>308</Height><Bytes>25736</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>109</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2294</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3311</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2115</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>479</Width><Height>332</Height><Bytes>19544</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>100</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2004</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>277</Height><Bytes>22176</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/91/50/21/2631759-The-Clifton-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>121</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2878</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Set overlooking Scarboroughs beautiful North Bay, the ever-popular Clifton Hotel has been a firm favorite with visitors to Scarborough for many years. Offering some of the most amazing, uninterrupted sea views that Scarborough has to offer and situated just a short distance from many of the towns attractions, this budget Scarborough hotel makes the perfect base when visiting the Yorkshire Coast. Renowned its warm Yorkshire welcome, The Clifton Hotel Scarborough boasts many return guests. The hotel offers a wide range of accommodation types, in both traditional and contemporary styles and a restaurant renowned for good quality food. The Clifton Hotel Scarborough has 70 bedrooms, all with en-suite facilities, direct dial telephone, television and welcome refreshment tray. Many rooms also have spectacular sea views, so you can enjoy watching the local surfers and fisherman in the North Bay from the comfort of your room. At the end of a perfect day where better to relax and watch the world go by, than in the hotel lounge or Tykes Bar  where you can enjoy your favorite tipple whilst watching the large screen TVs.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Youll find plenty to keep you entertained during your stay at The Clifton Hotel including two beautiful award winning clean beaches, North Bay being literally on your doorstep, making the hotel ideally placed for enjoying a seaside break. North Bay is heaven for families with a host of activities all year round including Peasholm Park, offering pedal boats, shows and the famous Navel Warfare and the striking pyramids of Scarborough Sea Life Centre where you can go beneath the sea with even getting the hotel, coming face to face with everthing from shrimps to sharks. As well as excellent walks, the more energetic will enjoy the adjacent indoor bowls center and for those who want to get in the swing, the North Cliff Golf Course is just a shoert walk away, with the South Cliff Golf Course only 3 miles away by car, in addition Filey and Ganton Golf Clubs are close by.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Double - Standard Double offers one double bed. All accommodation at The Clifton Hotel offers en-suite bathrooms, TV, refreshment tray, telephone, hairdryer, shaver point and 24hr room service.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>