<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10867977</Id><Name>The Brandize</Name><Region><Id>52783</Id><Name>Torquay</Name><CityId>52783</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>19 Avenue Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Torquay</City><State /><Zip>TQ2 5LB</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01803 297798</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/94/40/31/2631759-The-Brandize-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>24401</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Brandize-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/94/40/31/2631759-The-Brandize-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2408</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/94/40/31/2631759-The-Brandize-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3281</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Brandize-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/94/40/31/2631759-The-Brandize-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2408</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Welcome to the Brandize - A Quality Torquay B&amp;B that makes a great choice for a Holiday or Short Break on The English Riviera, South Devon. The Brandize is situated within easy walking distance to Torquay town centre, harbour, beaches and leisure centre. With attractive and well equipped guest bedrooms, a private car park,licensed bar, guest lounge, free Internet access and quality home cooked food made from fresh, locally sourced ingredients they hope you'll choose the Brandize B&amp;B for your holiday orshort break in Torquay. On the stunning South Devon coastline, the English Riviera consists of the three towns of Torquay, Paignton and Brixham and makes for the ideal year round holiday destination. The hotel also offers free breakfast.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Brandize is situated within easy walking distance to Torquay town centre, harbour, beaches and leisure centre. With attractive and well equipped guest bedrooms, a private car park,licensed bar, guest lounge, free Internet access and quality home cooked food made from fresh, locally sourced ingredients they hope you'll choose the Brandize B&amp;B for your holiday or short break in Torquay. On the stunning South Devon coastline, the English Riviera consists of the three towns of Torquay, Paignton and Brixham and makes for the ideal year round holiday destination. The Brandize is situated within easy walking distance to Torquay town centre.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Double - Standard Double offers 1 Double bed. All bedrooms are en-suite and tastefully decorated with color TV, beverage making facilities, complimentary toiletries, luxury towels, hair dryers and radio alarms. Standard double offers one double bed.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>