<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10867988</Id><Name>The Hillcroft</Name><Region><Id>52783</Id><Name>Torquay</Name><CityId>52783</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>9 St Lukes Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Torquay</City><State /><Zip>TQ2 5NY</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>011441803297247</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Hillcroft is a small, luxurious boutique hotel situated in a quiet position near the centre of Torquay, just minutes away from the beaches, shops, restaurants and nightlife. The hotel offers a range of accomodation to let including en-suite doubles, a 1 bedroom suite and a top-floor penthouse suite. All rooms are equipped with widescreen TV's that receive a wide selection of digital channels and DVD players. Free WiFi internet connectivity is available in all rooms at The Hillcroft for guests who have wireless capable laptops, and there is a laptop in the bar for guests to browse the Internet or check their Webmail accounts. Start the day with your choice of fresh fruit, cereal and yoghurts, followed by a light Continental or breakfast cooked to your order from the menu. Vegetarian and vegan options are always available. A fully stocked bar is available for the convenience of residents and the sixties jukebox (free-play) will keep you entertained. Therapeutic massage services are available in the treatment room at The Hillcroft (24 hours notice required). A range of treatments are available from their 2 visiting specialists. The Hillcroft has been created for the discerning customer looking for somewhere special. Your resident proprietors look forward to welcoming you.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>If you are travelling by car, the M5 runs to Exeter - from which Torquay is but a short drive. You can plan your journey using the RAC route planner. Great Western Trains operate services from London Paddington to Torquay. Virgin Trains offer services from all major UK destinations to Exeter St Davids and Newton Abbot, from where you can catch connecting trains to Torquay. Virgin Trains also offer direct services to Torquay on Summer Saturdays. National Express operate coach services throughout the year while other coach companies run in the summer.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Double Room - The room offers one double bed with all the basic amenities.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>