<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10874270</Id><Name>Strathness House</Name><Region><Id>52879</Id><Name>Inverness</Name><CityId>52569</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4 Ardross Terrace</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Inverness</City><State /><Zip>IV3 5NQ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01463232765</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Strathness House is a privately and family run guest house with all the facilities that you would expect from a small hotel. Set in a prime area of the city, the emphasis is on personal service with a homely, Highland touch. The services are personally centred around each guest. From small groups to the single business traveller, all are guaranteed a very warm Highland welcome. All guest house rooms en-suite, many rooms with river view Free wireless Internet access Single, Twin, Double and Family Rooms available Ideally situated in the centre of Inverness Strathness House was built in 1874 by Mr Matheson of the Merchant Shipping company Jardine &amp; Matheson, founded in 1843 in China. Alexander Ross (an eminent architect of the day) was commissioned to design and oversee the building of the house. Mr Ross was also the designer of St Andrew's Cathedral that stands next door to Strathness House. Matheson was a highly respected local businessman who invested in the local community - though perhaps today he may have been regarded as something of a shady character due to his involvement in the opium trade! During World War II Strathness House was taken over by the Ministry of Defence as one of their residences, and after the war it remained a guest house until it was renamed the Tower Hotel in 1957. The name Strathness House was reinstated in October 2007 by its present owners Joan and Javed, who will be happy to tell you more about the history of Strathness House on your visit to Inverness.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Strathness House is situated ideally in a prime area of Inverness, one of Scotland's fastest growing cities. Located on the banks of the River Ness and next door to St Andrews Cathedral, it is central to all amenities with the city centre a 5 minute walk away. The Railway and Bus stations are an easy 7-10 minute walk. Inverness Airport is 7 miles (11km) away, with regular shuttle buses from the city centre. Otherwise a taxi will take approximately 10-15 minutes.
All the major local attractions are easily reached with Strathness House as a base; Inverness Castle, Floral Hall, Museum &amp; Art Gallery, Eden Court Theatre and of course the Cathedral and picturesque River Ness sit on their doorstep. From the Caledonian Canal you can take a Boat trip to see Loch Ness where you might just catch a glimpse of the famous monster, "Nessie". Tennis &amp; squash courts, swimming pool, ice rink and 3 golf courses are also walking distance away.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Double En-Suite - The room offers one double bed. Each of the bedrooms is comfortably furnished with attention given to the needs of their guests. All rooms have private en-suite facilities with showers (sorry, no baths available), flat screen TV with "Freeview" viewing, Hostess Tray providing Tea and coffee, direct dial telephone and free internet access to all guests with wireless-enabled laptops or smartphones.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>