<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10910713</Id><Name>Cornwall Hotel Spa and Estate</Name><Region><Id>153609</Id><Name>St Austell</Name><CityId>153609</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Pentewan Road  Tregorrick</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>St Austell</City><State /><Zip>PL26 7AB</Zip><Country>England</Country><Tel>0044 0 1726 874050</Tel><Fax>004401726874056</Fax><Email>reservations@thecornwall.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Opened in February 2010, this stunning four-star country hotel and spa is a luxurious treat and retreat for a stay in Cornwall. In a secluded 43 acre setting between St Austell and the harbour village of Mevagissey, the estate is a true haven yet within touching distance of many popular beaches and tourist attractions including the World famous Eden project and the Lost Gardens of Heligan. The main White House has been tastefully restored and connects with the 56 stylish and contemporary Woodland bedrooms which are nestled into wooded slopes, each with a balcony affording wonderful views of the estate`s sweeping parkland. All Woodland rooms have flat-screen TVs, power-showers in the modern ensuite bathrooms and complimentary Wi-Fi. Guests at The Cornwall can enjoy superb food in The Arboretum Restaurant with a daily changing menu or The Parkland Terrace, overlooking the Pentewan Valley, providing a breath-taking setting for Cornish Afternoon Tea, canapés and cocktails. The Clearing Spa is the hotel`s state of the art centre for beauty, health, fitness and relaxation. Facilities include single and double rooms for luxurious treatments, manicure bar, juice bar, infinity-edge swimming pool, tennis courts, sauna and aroma steam-room, drench showers and a fully equipped fitness suite with personal training and nutritional advisors. You may never want to leave!</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>