<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>111374</Id><Name>Hotel de Londres y de Inglaterra</Name><Region><Id>18446</Id><Name>San Sebastian</Name><CityId>18446</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ZUBIETA, 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SAN SEBASTIAN</City><State /><Zip>20000</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>+34-943-440770</Tel><Fax>+34-943-440491</Fax><Email>reservas@hlondres.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>148</CountRooms><CountFloors>6</CountFloors><Latitude>43.3177835</Latitude><Longitude>-1.9848566</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/B2Zfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/B2Zthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1963</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/B2Zbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/B2Zthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1892</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/B2Zmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/B2Zthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1719</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Hotel de Londres y de Inglaterra is a luxury 4-star property offering beachfront accommodation in the beautiful Spanish town of San Sebastian. It offers an elegant atmosphere right on the shores of La Concha bay. San Sebastian is a small coastal town in northern Spain, located at the mouth of the River Urumea near the French border. It is known for its sandy beaches and charming city centre, which boasts many historic buildings and churches. Nearby places of interest include La Concha and La Zurriola beaches and Monte Igueldo, where travellers can enjoy wonderful panoramic views overlooking the town. Local bus services provide fast and easy access to other popular San Sebastian destinations. The hotel is housed in a 19th-century promenade property with glistening white facade. Onsite facilities include an internet corner, plus there is Wi-Fi (chargeable) throughout the property for convenience. La Brasserie Mari Galant is a fine restaurant that specialises in seasonal vegetables, local meat dishes and grilled fish. Guests can also enjoy a variety of cocktails in the sea view lounge at Bar Swing, plus there is an outdoor terrace open in summer. Standard City View rooms are decorated in a traditional style and offer views of San Sebastian. Amenities include air-conditioning, a flat-screen TV, mini-bar and marble bathroom. Parking is possible nearby.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>