<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10094952</Id><Name>JW Marriott Absheron Baku</Name><Region><Id>15450</Id><Name>Baku</Name><CityId>15450</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>674 Azadliq Square</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Baku</City><State /><Zip>1010</Zip><Country>Azerbaijan</Country><Tel>00994 (0)124998888</Tel><Fax>00994 (0)124998889</Fax><Email>jw.baku.reservations@marriott.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/J8Wfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/J8Wthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2015</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/J8Wbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/J8Wthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1959</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/J8Wmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/J8Wthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1829</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>This stylish hotel offers exceptional comfort and amenities to business and leisure travelers alike. Lavishly appointed guest rooms and suites feature views of the Caspian Sea, luxury bedding and the latest technology, including flat-screen TVs and Wi-Fi. The hotel in Baku is set in the heart of the business, shopping and entertainment district with Azadliq Square, Baku Boulevard and high-end retailers. Make a culinary journey in four dining venues that are exquisite among restaurants in Baku hotels. The spa and 24-hour fitness center feature a rooftop indoor pool overlooking the sea. Our 1,208-square-meter, pillar-less Sharg Zali is graced by high ceilings and panoramic views, while 11 other meeting rooms are flooded with natural light. Discover one of the most enticing hotels in Baku and experience our quiet luxury, personalized service and distinctive decor</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>JW Marriott Hotel Absheron Baku is an upscale Baku hotel ideally located among the city centers futuristic skyline and historic buildings.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Fireworks Oriental Kitchen - Explore the culinary theaters and cultures of Turkey, Azerbaijan, Iran and Punjab. Succulent kebabs, freshly baked breads and an eclectic selection of spice mixes mesmerize you with the exotic flavors of the regions and stimulate your taste buds. OroNero Bar &amp; Ristorante - At the most delectable Italian restaurant Baku has to offer, guests experience a catwalk of tastes from Parma and Milano and Fresco dining. The epitome of style, we offer contemporary Italian cuisine perfectly complemented by warm, luxurious interiors. Razzmatazz Cocktail Bar &amp; Lounge - Engage in the most ebullient bar and restaurant in Baku at Razzmatazz. A destination to meet friends and colleagues for cocktails, conversations and more, we offer an extensive range of hand-crafted martinis and mojitos, specialty coffees and teas. Zest Lifestyle Cafe - Unique among restaurants in Baku, Zest is a one-stop destination for virtually any time of the day. A representation of Baku style, it features a large selection of international, gourmet delicatessen items, such as cheese, cold cuts and home-made salads.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TrouserPress</Code><Text>Trouser press</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>