<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>100941</Id><Name>Minarete</Name><Region><Id>47741</Id><Name>Roquetas de Mar</Name><CityId>18341</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>SIERRA NEVADA</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ROQUETAS DE MAR</City><State /><Zip>04740</Zip><Country>Spain</Country><Tel>950334358</Tel><Fax>950334632</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>1</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountFloors>2</CountFloors><Latitude>36.7291172</Latitude><Longitude>-2.6256476</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1206125-front.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>2434</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1206125-front_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2424</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1206125-front.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>10310</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1206125-front.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2129</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Minarete Apartments are located in the cosmopolitan area of Roquetas de Mar, 4km from the fisherman’s harbor and just a few meters from the resort centre with its many bars, restaurants, shops and vibrant nightlife. The sandy beaches are just 500 meters from the complex and golfers will find a golf course 800 meters away. The Almeria airport is 33 km away. Within the towns` historic centre, several monuments, churches and castles are to be found including the Nuestra Senora del Rosaio and the Castle of Roquetas. The town also boasts a number of golf courses as well as facilities for all kinds of water sports. Typical Spanish tapas bars and restaurants can be found by the small marina. The Minarete offers charming apartments, all equipped with a private bathroom, heating (in winter), air conditioning, satellite TV, direct dial telephone, a living room with a sofa bed, a complete kitchenette with coffee/tea making facilities and a refrigerator, housekeeping services as well as a balcony or terrace with garden. Two-bedroom apartments feature an extra bathroom. Non smoking rooms are available.On site facilities include a swimming pool, reception desk that offers a safe deposit box, room service and a beautiful garden and terrace. The Minarete Apartments provides self-catering style accommodation and a variety of facilities, making it a wonderful place to stay.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>The town of Roquetas de Mar is a popular holiday resort and has many attractions to offer travelers.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Keys</System><Score>10</Score><Description>One key</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>