<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10108940</Id><Name>Poseidonion Grand Hotel</Name><Region><Id>16721</Id><Name>Spetses Island</Name><CityId>16721</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Dapia</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Spetses</City><State /><Zip>18050</Zip><Country>Greece</Country><Tel>0030 2298074553</Tel><Fax>0030 2298074248</Fax><Email>res@poseidonion.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/8DQfront.JPG</Url><Width>401</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/8DQthumbfront.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1977</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/8DQbed.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/8DQthumbbed.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1881</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/8DQmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/8DQthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1389</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The landmark 5-star superior Poseidonion Grand Hotel promises luxury accommodation and elegant facilities right on the seafront. Feel transported to an earlier era while enjoying thoroughly modern comforts. Located on the island of Spetses, just 200m from the main ferry terminal, the hotel affords easy access to the island's many delights, thanks largely to its bike rental service. Guests can experience an island that features lovely beaches, a number of footpaths for hikers (the hotel provides pack lunches) and the chance to do plenty of water sports such as waterskiing, wake-boarding and windsurfing. Guests can also hire a boat for the day and explore secluded areas or dive into the cobalt-blue sea. Completed in 1914, the hotel is a handsome building inspired by the architecture of the Cote d'Azur. Following a five-year renovation project, the hotel is in excellent health, the fresh luminosity of its white walls reflecting the inimitable peace and serenity of the Greek islands. In addition to an outdoor swimming pool, the hotel boasts a spa that offers a range of body and massage treatments. There is also a library, along with Wi-Fi throughout the premises. Benefiting from views across the Argosaronic gulf and the hotel's Mediterranean garden, the Aneton on the Verandah restaurant is open for dinner, preparing delicious traditional dishes using locally sourced ingredients. Open from 10:00-02:00, the library bar serves lighter dishes and salads, as well as a range of beverages including some impressive cocktails. The Deluxe Garden View guestrooms are spacious and elegant, combining the eclectic Belle Epoque style with the high standards of a luxury hotel. The rooms are situated in the historic wing and command views of the pool, palm trees and clutches of lavender. Notable amenities include a mini-bar, satellite TV and an en suite marble bathroom with complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>