<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10436604</Id><Name>Rezia</Name><Region><Id>5031923</Id><Name>Bormio</Name><CityId>5031923</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Milano, 9</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>23032</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
Surrounded by the spectacular Alpine landscape, Hotel Rezia is situated on the peaceful outskirts of the town centre in a pedestrian area full of buildings, churches and towers that confirm a past which is overflowing with history and tradition.

Restaurant
The Hotel’s restaurant has a long history of quality dishes and a prestigious wine list. It offers a cuisine that evokes the famous local traditions yet with an eye to international haute cuisine. 
In the Hotel’s stylish yet informal tavern one can have the chance to sample genuine Valtellina products.

Outside
Hotel Rezia has been the mainstay of the tradi-tional art of hospitality in Alta Valtellina since 1954. A perfectly charming Hotel thanks to its various renovations and extensions.

Lobby
Welcoming and elegant rooms offer a regenerative stay focussed on well-being and comfort all year round.

More Informations
The Hotel offers an oasis of well-being; this area has been specially designed so that you can dedicate time to your body with a sauna, Turkish bath, Finnish shower and gym.
The beauty salon offers massages, sun beds, and body and facial treatments which are all carried out by qualified personnel. Within walking distance are the historic spa facilities offering the philosophy of "SPA" (salus per acquam), using warm water pools with detoxifying, relaxing and rejuvenating and toning. Shuttle service from/to the ski free.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>