<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10450453</Id><Name>Club Cala Ginepro</Name><Region><Id>20926</Id><Name>Gulf of Orosei</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Viale Cala Ginepro,76</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>08028</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
The Hotel Club Cala Ginepro, is located in the beautiful Gulf of Orosei in Cala Ginepro. The harmonious construction in the typical local architecture consists of three separate units, close to each other even if they are located in different areas, all set in the green gardens of special

Restaurant
The restaurant of the hotel is well known for the excellent cuisine and the faultless service. All our dishes are based on our local traditional cuisine using only the freshest ingredients. Buffet breakfast, lunch and dinner are served mixed at the table and / or buffet, at the discretion of the Management. Available gluten-free menu. Drinks always excluded.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
In some period of the years (01/06 - 21/09) it is possible to take advantage, with the payment of the club card starting from 4 years age, of beach umbrellas and sunbeds staring from the third row (beach umbrellas and sunbeds located in the first and in the second row are non-reservable and are payable directly at the spot, according to hotel availability), entertainment, mini-club, disco, sport equipments and collective sport courses.
Check - in; from 3.00 pm
Check - out; by 10.00 am
Small pets allowed with additional charge of € 15 + € 50 for final cleaning.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Entertainment</Code><Text>Entertainment</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>