<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10450305</Id><Name>Porto Pozzo</Name><Region><Id>20924</Id><Name>Costa Esmeralda</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Loc Porto Pozzo S.s 133</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>07028</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
Hotel Porto Pozzo is situated on the north coast of Sardinia, about halfway between Santa Teresa and Palau, in Porto Pozzo. Its location makes the hotel the ideal place for your holidays in Sardinia, having the opportunity to stay in a facility that offers relaxing amenities in its residential units and allows you to easily reach the most beautiful beaches of Northern Sardinia.

Restaurant
The restaurant is located in the center of the hotel, the food in the restaurant for the guests of Hotel Porto Pozzo are varied, from the buffet Italian breakfast, the dinner menu, table service, distinguished specialties typical regional and local. At the bar with TV room, reading and the beautiful veranda overlooking the pool you can relax perhaps tasting a local liquor or a cocktail as the Myrtle particular.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
The Hotel Porto Pozzo, about halfway between Santa Teresa and Palau, offers the possibility to easily reach the most attractive and most interesting of the area, while taking advantage of the peace and quiet of which is surrounded .</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>