<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10455161</Id><Name>Fonzari</Name><Region><Id>5032213</Id><Name>Grado</Name><CityId>5032213</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Piazza Biagio Marin, 6</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>34073</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
Among the sea-facing hotels in Grado, Hotel Fonzari enjoys an enviable position. Near the Grado's beach, Hotel Fonzari is situated in the historic center, in the age-old Piazza Biagio Marin where Roman ruins can be visited. Just outside the hotel there are stores, ice cream parlors and restaurants for shopping and the seafront for pleasant walks.

Restaurant
The restaurant offers Italian, regional and international cuisine with an “a la carte” menu; it is located on the seventh floor of the hotel along with the breakfast room. The rich buffet includes pastries, bread, marmalade, fresh fruit, cereal, yogurt, cheese, deli meats, sausages, etc., to start your day off right. There is a children's game room available for guests of the hotel. There is a children's game room available for guests of the hotel.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
Guests can take advantage of elegant public rooms and countless services at Hotel Fonzari. The wonderful scenic swimming pool with Jacuzzi and sun bathing area with chaise longues and umbrellas awaits you on the seventh floor with its breathtaking view.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>