<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10450241</Id><Name>Cala Di Volpe</Name><Region><Id>20927</Id><Name>Porto Cervo</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Costa Smeralda</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Olbia-Tempio</City><State /><Zip>07021</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
With its design inspired by old fishing villages the Hotel Cala di Volpe and its charming archways, porticoes and turrets is located on the enchanting Costa Smeralda, facing the glittering waters of the Mediterranean.

Restaurant
Guests can enjoy ample buffets and delicious a la carte menus filled with classic Mediterranean and Sardinian cuisine from Hotel Cala di Volpe's award-winning restaurants. Both the Cala Restaurant and the Barbecue Restaurant offer an assortment of international and local dishes, while a menu filled with light local Italian style meals can be found at La Piazzetta Bar, each under the management of Executive Chef Franco Guardone. Half board traitment will be  available in differte restaurants of the resort.

More Informations
Among the wide range of services and luxurious amenities offered by the hotel Cala di Volpe you can find a beautiful swimming pool adjacent to the bay, floodlit tennis courts, a putting green, a beautiful white sand beach and numerous activities acquatiche. Our fitness center is located in a modern environment that provides guests the opportunity to take advantage of the latest Technogym equipment and our qualified personal trainers and pilates instructors.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>