<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10461644</Id><Name>Liberty</Name><Region><Id>20962</Id><Name>Riva del Garda</Name><CityId>17100</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Viale Carducci, 3/5</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>38066</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
On the shores of one of the most beautiful lakes in Europe, in the heart of Riva del Garda, the Grand Hotel Liberty, in a stylish palace built at the beginning of the 20th century, opens its doors into a world of warm refinement and elegance.

Restaurant
It is really very important to start your day with an excellent breakfast, on our buffet you will find a great variety of products, for all tastes and dietary. Breakfast is served in an elegant and very bright dining room or on the terrace which is facing the garden and the outdoor pool. You may relax sitting on the veranda while having your breakfast and start at best your day.


Outside


Lobby


More Informations
The indoor swimming pool (open during all year) is heated on 30° degree, ideal temperature for your total Relax, it includes inside beds for water massage done with air stream, water jet against running water, vertical and horizontal water massage, comfortable stair that make easier the access to the swimming pool.
All around the pool you will find comfortable sunbeds to rest, read a magazine, eat some fruits or only to sip a herbal tea. The outdoor pool (open from April to September) is surrounded by the garden, in a very quiet area, it is accessible throught the Wellness Centre or the Hotel’ terrace. Here as well you can find sunbeds and areas in the shade.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>