<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10461966</Id><Name>Corte Di Nettuno</Name><Region><Id>20974</Id><Name>Otranto</Name><CityId>17105</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Madonna Del Passo</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>73028</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
This historical agricultural cottage in a typical courtyard style situated at the entrance of Otranto’s historic centre overlooking the port, the castle and the Serpe tower, one of the most striking points of Salento, is home to Hotel Corte di Nettuno.

Restaurant
Enclosed in the heart of the historical agricultural cottage that houses the hotel, restaurant Corte di Nettuno is a pleasure that envelops all the senses. Surrounded by a valuable collection of oil amphorae of ancient Roman and portholes that tell the fascinating stories of our seas, the restaurant is a real pleasure for the eyes and especially to the palate, because every day offers delicious dishes of traditional cuisine made with pugliese passion by our chef Martire. A delight of flavors that are accompanied by a rich selection of the best wines of our region. A pleasure that can be transformed into a journey through the flavors and colors of a magical land, which is hard not to fall in love.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
Hotel Corte di Nettuno preserves precious marine objects and tells its guests of its great love for the sea. Compasses and portholes of various sizes, rudders of different workmanship, antique brace blocks, anchors and nautical maps telling of sea routes and landings. These objects collected from all parts of the world enrich this setting.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>