<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10462092</Id><Name>Ai Pozzi Village Spa &amp; Resort</Name><Region><Id>17108</Id><Name>Loano</Name><CityId>17108</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Silvio Amico, 35</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>17010</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
Located about 900/1000 meters from the center and about 1000 from the private beach "Bagni Sirena", located in the center of the promenade of Loano.

Restaurant
Restaurant with international and typical Ligurian cuisine.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
PRICES INCLUDE: electricity, water, bed linen and towels, cot and use of the spa (excluded services to pay). 

COMPULSORY COSTS TO BE PAID ON THE SPOT: Security deposit: € 150.00. ATTENTION: The apartments must be left clean. Otherwise deposit will be retained by the sum of € 30.00 for studios, € 40.00 for the Bilo, € 50.00 for Trilo. 

ADDITIONAL SERVICES: Outdoor swimmingpool open from Easter to the end of the season with 2 single beds + 1 umbrella per double room, with a water slide and children's section. Fitness room. Private beach (located about 1 Km from hotel) included in the price 15/04 to 14/06 and from 06/09 to 11/10 with 2 sunbeds + umbrella + exchange cabin for each apartment. From 14.06 to 06.09.2013 is included only the entry to the beach with the changing booth, Chairs and sun umbrella on supplement(from € 12.00 to € 30.00 per day). SPA of 600 sqm with heated indoor swimming pool with salt water with UVA (without chlorine), whirlpool (6 places), sauna, turkish bath. Pay on the spot: massages, beauty treatments and solarium. Golf about 15 km, riding stables about 10 km, about 1 km sailing, diving center about 1.8 km.
BABY KIT (on supplement): linen - crib - bottle warmer - high chair - pan and changing table.

ARRIVALS: 16:00 to 20:00
CHECK OUT: before 09:30 am.

Cot available paid € 10,00 per day (without linen), only in the type two-apartments maximum 4 pax and types trilocale maximum 7 pax.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>