<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10479112</Id><Name>Borgo Tre Rose</Name><Region><Id>21052</Id><Name>Montepulciano</Name><CityId>17157</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Palazzi, 5</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>53024</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
Hotel Borgo Tre Rose is in the heart of the hills between Montepulciano and Cortona, in the splendid Tuscan countryside. Near Lago Trasimeno and the Terme di Chianciano, the hotel boasts a splendid location compared to the other 3-star hotels near Montepulciano, charming visitors and guests to Borgo Tre Rose and having received praise from the American writer Frances Mayes in her bestsellers Under the Tuscan Sun (which was made into the well-known film) and Bella Tuscany. The surrounding areas are just peace and quiet, vineyards, olive trees and a Medieval landscape to discover and experience with art, history, and architectural tours as well as the must-see wine and culinary tour.

Restaurant
Selecting Hotel Borgo Tre Rose to stay in Montepulciano means having the chance to try typical Tuscan cuisine at the hotel's restaurant.

Simple and genuine ingredients like extra virgin olive oil, cheeses and DOP meats from the area, home-made pasta and desserts and farm-raised and wild meets are offered by our chef in traditional and modern takes on dishes that are always accompanied by DOC wines from the Tre Rose Estate's vineyards.

The restaurant is truly romantic: there is the inside room in the historic setting or the panoramic terrace that, in nice weather, lets you experiences the charming tastes and landscapes of Tuscany.

Outside


Lobby


More Informations
Borgo Tre Rose is near:
Montepulciano, 14 km 
Castiglione del Lago, 16 km 
Cortona, 18 km 
Chianciano Terme, 20 km 
Pienza, 27 km 
Montalcino, 50 km</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>