<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10526791</Id><Name>Casulo Hotel</Name><Region><Id>58462</Id><Name>Austin</Name><CityId>58461</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Casulo Hotel</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Austin</City><State /><Zip>78741</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>(512) 610-1116</Tel><Fax>(512) 441-4477</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Casulo Hotel is a brand new upscale luxury destination for both business and leisure travelers who want to experience something different. We are conveniently located between Austin's vibrant downtown scene and the airport. The hotel is just 12 minutes northwest of the Austin Bergstrom International Airport and 5 minutes south of downtown. Towering above the Interstate Highway 35, our 49-room specialty hotel enjoys a lovely hilltop with panoramic views and our natural topography fends off any noise thus creating an unexpected lovely oasis. &lt;br&gt;Our one of a kind luxurious rooms and unique décor has their roots in Asia, exemplifying the Zen lifestyle. Our 10-foot high ceilings, extra wide hallways, spacious rooms, and luxurious bathrooms are all intended for the utmost comfort of your stay. A large 5 ft × 7 ft glass panel wall between the bathroom and the bedroom highlights the splendor. A waterfall awaits you in our distinctive baths, a rainforest delights you in our showers, or you can soak in our extra long six foot bathtub after a long day, then bask on the Egyptian cotton covered Monogram 600 plush mattress bed while you entertain yourself with the 37 or 47 flat screen TV in the comfort of our state of the art low-noise and environmental friendly central air-conditioning. &lt;br&gt;Whether you are looking for peace of mind during your business travel, or a romantic getaway, we are here to serve you and to make sure your stay with us is one that you will want to keep coming back to.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Address: 3017 S. I35, Austin, TX 78741. Casulo Hotel is located in the east side of South Interstate Highway 35  between Oltorf Street to the north and Woodward Street to the south.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>DELUXE - ROOM - These rooms exemplify the Zen standard. Sumptuous accommodations give way to luxurious linens and sophisticated style with a modern twist. Allow your nights to be as soothing as your day is exciting.

Superior - Suite - A grand understatement. Your home away from home, these 608 square feet rooms are fit for a king, crown not required.

Petite - Suite - This 510 square feet suite embodies our Zen standard with an extra dose of modern mist amenities include a full reading corner and desk adjacent to the sleeping area.

Jacuzzi - Suite - Live like no other. Featuring a heavenly French-modern air-bath centered in the room or an understated deep Japanese bath, your weekend getaway will be unforgettable.

French Bath: The ultimate in comfort, this six-foot hydro-thermal massage for two will even light up your world.

Japanese bath: At nearly three feet deep with room for two, this full Jacuzzi is the consummate de-stresser.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>