<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10529612</Id><Name>Manilow Suites at North Harbor Tower</Name><Region><Id>21467</Id><Name>The Loop</Name><CityId>19455</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>175 North Harbor Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Chicago</City><State /><Zip>60601</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>312/819-0050</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Our North Harbor Tower location offers a magnificent, comfortable short-term experience.  Surrounded by the tranquil beauty of the lake and shoreline parks, removed from the hustle and bustle of the Loop yet so close by, this spacious building offers some of the largest units in the city's luxury high-rise inventory. Guests here enjoy easy access to the business and theatre districts, a short walk to some of the finest restaurants in Chicago, and a peaceful, serene place to kick up their feet at night after a busy day. Your stay in Chicago couldn't be more convenient or comfortable. North Harbor is also an ideal place for guests with children.  The apartment features include a fully equipped kitchen, DVD player, flat screen TVs, king sized bed, indoor swimming pool,  fitness center, a high speed internet connection at no extra charge,  and a playground just outside your door. 

****PETS NOT ALLOWED.******</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>North Harbor Tower is located at the east end of Randolph Drive, just past Michigan Avenue and across the street from Millennium Park and Grant Park. Fabulous views overlooking the lake and Lake Shore Drive.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Junior Apartment - Spread out and relax in a charming, fully-furnished apartment in a luxury high-rise building. With a kitchen stocked with utensils and spacious living room, you get so much more than a simple hotel room without sacrificing hotel services.

One Bedroom Apartment - In addition to a great living room and full kitchen, the bedroom features a king-sized bed. You'll have a luxury experience as our apartments are stocked with the finest linens and towels in corporate housing.

Two Bedroom Apartment - Ideal for families or business travelers in teams: this large two-bedroom apartment features a master bedroom with a king-sized bed and private bathroom. The second bedroom offers plenty of space and has a queen-sized bed. With views of the lake and city, you'll truly be living like a native.

CEO Suite - As one of the most unique apartments in Chicago, this three bedroom suite is the top tier of corporate housing. Traditional English furniture and furnishings lend an elegant feel and sweeping views of the lake and harbor make this stunning location feel more like a manor than an apartment.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>