<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10529617</Id><Name>Manilow Suites at Presidential Towers</Name><Region><Id>21467</Id><Name>The Loop</Name><CityId>19455</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>555 W Madison St</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Chicago</City><State /><Zip>60661</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>312.819.0050</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Don't pay for just a bedroom at a hotel when you can experience a spacious, fully furnished apartment in a luxury high-rise building with better services and amenities FOR LESS! Why settle for crackers from a wet bar when you can have your own fully equipped kitchen, living room with state of the art electronics including a flat screen tv, 24 hr concierge service, and the comforts of feeling like a Chicagoan and not a tourist? Situated in the heart of Chicago and across from Ogilvie Metra train station, Presidential Towers is the closest major residential complex to the financial district. The building contains all the amenities of a small city: An upscale sports bar, Potbelly Sandwich location, convenience store, a flowers shop and more. Corporate offices, brown, purple, and green line stops, the Opera and dining are all accessible in a matter of minutes. With spectacular views, Presidential Towers features spacious studio, convertible, and one bedroom apartments. For convenience and value, Presidential Towers cannot be topped.

****PETS NOT ALLOWED.******</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Chicago's West Loop Neighborhood is home to businesses and residents who enjoy a dynamic and rapidly growing urban environment. The West Loop is one of the fastest growing neighborhoods in Chicago. It is home to thriving restaurants, shops, a burgeoning gallery district, and spacious residential lofts.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Apartment Suite - Spacious one-bedroom apartments offer breathtaking views of the city and so much more space than a traditional hotel room.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>