<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10529711</Id><Name>Manilow Suites at One Superior Place</Name><Region><Id>21466</Id><Name>River North/Magnificent Mile</Name><CityId>19455</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 W Superior St</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Chicago</City><State /><Zip>60654</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>312.819.0050</Tel><Fax>1-312-873-4199</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Don't pay for just a bedroom at a hotel when you can experience a spacious, fully furnished apartment in a luxury high-rise building with better services and amenities! Why settle for crackers from a wet bar when you can have your own fully equipped kitchen, living room with state of the art electronics including a flat screen tv, 24 hr concierge service, a welcome guide with recommendations for the best delivery options in the area including restaurants with 24 hour delivery,and the comforts of feeling like a Chicagoan and not a tourist? 

One Superior Place is the perfect blend of timeless elegance and contemporary style. Ideally situated just a minutes walk from the famous Gold Coast shopping district and Michigan Avenues fabulous dining options, residents have every downtown attraction just outside their door.  One Superior features fabulous views, a 24 hour fitness center, outdoor pool complete with sundeck and bar area, an internet café with a coffee bar, and a private library.   Manilow Suites guests have all of this at their disposal, along with our fully furnished apartment, fully equipped kitchen replete with quality flatware and dishes, and the finest linens, pillows, and towels.

****PETS ARE NOT ALLOWED.******</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The River North and Gold Coast neighborhood is filled with over 100 restaurants, in all genres of food, including American, Brazilian, Chinese, French, Indian, Japanese, Mediterranean, Spanish, Thai and even Vegetarian. Some of these are one of a kind restaurants that one can only find in Chicago, such as the Rockbottom Brewery, Ben Pao, Klay Oven (a South Indian restaurant), Chicagos own Harry Carays Restaurant and House of Blues. Fantastic shopping is right outside your door on Oak Street.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Executive Apartment - This is a two-bedroom apartment with fantastic furniture and furnishings. With your own kitchen (stocked with cooking utensils), living room, and dining area, it's like home only better.

City Apartment - Beautifully furnished apartments in a newly renovated building. Some apartments have queen beds, others have king bed, depending upon layout. You will be getting more than just a hotel room, but without giving up hotel-like services.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>