<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10522863</Id><Name>Lemon Tree Hotel &amp; Kitchen Suites</Name><Region><Id>21399</Id><Name>Disneyland Area</Name><CityId>19324</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1600 East Lincoln Ave.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Anaheim</City><State /><Zip>92805</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-714-772-0200</Tel><Fax>1-714-535-5837</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Unique Spanish Style Boutique Hotel. The Lemon Tree has warm, earthy colors, hand painted accents and saltio tiled floors giving it old world European charm. Many of the rooms have garden patios, set in  a lushly landscaped fountain courtyard with outdoor fireplace and BBQ facilities. Kitchens, feather pillows and hand crafted rustic furniture are just some of the features that were added during a total makeover of the furnished apartments and hotel rooms in 2005. The Lemon Tree has only 30 hotel rooms and 57 furnished apartments so the property has a low key, quiet environment where the staff will help you feel at home for any length of stay.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Hotel is located on the South side of  E Lincoln Avenue between East Street to the west and State College Blvd to the east. Yellow Oaka Buildings next to Martenet Hardware -- Directions -- From Interstate 5 travelling north or south exit Lincoln Ave and travel east about 2 miles. The hotel is on the RHS. From Freeway 91 travelling east or west, exit State College BLVD and head south about 0.5 mile and turn right onto Lincoln Ave to head west. The hotel is on the LHS after about 600 yards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Queen - Rooms with 1 queen bed include Cable/satellite TV, Air conditioning, Access via interior corridors, Free local calls, Refrigerator, Microwave, Housekeeping, Designer toiletries, Hair dryer (on request), Shower/tub combination, Iron/ironing board, Electronic/magnetic keys and unlimited wireless internet for a one time fee of $5.00.

Twin Queen - Rooms with 2 queen beds include Cable/satellite TV, Air conditioning, Access via interior corridors, Free local calls, Refrigerator, Microwave, Housekeeping, Designer toiletries, Hair dryer (on request), Shower/tub combination, Iron/ironing board, Electronic/magnetic keys and unlimited wireless internet for a one time fee of $5.00.

One Bedroom Apartment - Rooms with 1 king bed, sofa bed, and full kitchen include Cable/satellite TV, Air conditioning, Access via interior corridors, Free local calls, Refrigerator, Microwave, Housekeeping, Designer toiletries, Hair dryer (on request), Shower/tub combination, Iron/ironing board, Electronic/magnetic keys and unlimited wireless internet for a one time fee of $5.00.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>