<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10537325</Id><Name>Kuhio Banyan Club</Name><Region><Id>21698</Id><Name>Honolulu - Waikiki</Name><CityId>19807</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2310 Kuhio Ave.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Honolulu</City><State /><Zip>96815</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-808-923-5887</Tel><Fax>+1 (626) 6964510</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Kuhio Banyan Club is an all-kitchenette boutique resort located less than 1-1/2 blocks from spectacular Waikiki Beach, the International Market Place, the Royal Hawaii Shopping Center, many fine restaurants, discos, nightclubs, and exciting shows such as the legendary Society of Seven and The Magic of Polynesia. The Kuhio Banyan Club offers traditional Hawaiian hospitality and customer service, with complimentary flower-lei greeting and chocolates upon check-in. Beach towels, beach chairs, mats, umbrellas, coolers, boogie boards, irons, ironing boards, blow dryers, local calls, and in-room safe are provided free-of-charge. Our friendly staff will help you find all the fun our tropical paradise offers, from exotic out-of-the-way restaurants to the best spots for surfing, skin diving, and watching the sun set on a romantic, deserted beach. Make the Kuhio Banyan Club your home-away-from-home. Please Note- front desk hours are 7am-10pm. Please call before arrival for smoking room availability. A refundable USD 250.00 deposit is required at check-in. A deposit of USD 250.00 is required at the time of check-in. The deposit is refundable at the end of the stay as long as there are no damages in the room.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Waikiki is known for its fabulous weather, average high temperature ranges from 78-85 F., and its legendary beach, with water temperatures ranging from 74 F to 80 F.  Waikiki also boasts world-class shopping, dining, and shows within easy walking distance.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Studio unit - Studio units offer cable TV, stereo, safe, AC, small refrigerator, two burner stove, microwave and breakfast bar. Unit bedding includes a sofa sleeper and a murphy bed.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>