<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10536688</Id><Name>Banyan Harbor</Name><Region><Id>21595</Id><Name>Lihue</Name><CityId>19644</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>3411 Wilcox Rd No 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Lihue</City><State /><Zip>96766</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1 808 2457333</Tel><Fax>1-808 246 3687</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/25/87/12/2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Dining-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>384</Height><Bytes>33171</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Dining-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/25/87/12/2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Dining-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2221</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/25/87/12/2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>384</Height><Bytes>43401</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/25/87/12/2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2478</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/25/87/12/2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Guest-Room-2_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3787</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Guest-Room-2_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/25/87/12/2631759-Banyan-Harbor-Guest-Room-2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2322</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Nestled on a hillside in Nawiliwili, the Banyan Harbor Resort is ideal for your next getaway.  From the moment you set foot in our island-styled lobby, you'll feel the Aloha Spirit that has made Kauai the popular destination it is today. Your "Home away from Home" is a block from Kalapaki Beach, shopping, restaurants, activities and entertainment. Anchor Cove Shopping Village and the Harbor Mall are both within a short walk.   Three golf courses, Kauai's largest shopping center, Kauai's largest movie theatre and world class ocean &amp; air charters are available within two miles.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


All One and Two bedroom condominium suites offer cable TV, DVD/Video players, DVD rentals, WIFI, and ample space for the entire family; Bedrooms include queen- or full-sized beds and a pull out sofa sleeper.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

All Condo suites are equipped with a full kitchen, including all pots and pans; flatware; silverware; glasses; full-sized refrigerator/freezer; full-sized oven; four burner stove top; dishwasher and microwave oven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Gas barbecue grills located next to our heated pool, overlooking beautiful Kalapaki Bay. Pool area also offers Free Tennis, shuffleboard and Basketball court. We also offer Free on a first come first serve basis; mask/snorkels, coolers, boogie boards, beach chairs and beach towels. We look forward to your visit! Mahalo!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Property is located 2 miles west of the Lihue main airport and is centrally located between Princeville and Kokee State park.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>2 Bedroom Condominium - All Two bedroom condominium suites offer a fully equipped kitchen, separate living and dining areas, Private Washer/Dryer, cable TV, DVD/Video players, WIFI and ample space for the entire family; Bedrooms include queen size bed, double bed and a pull out sofa sleeper.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All Condo suites equipped with full kitchen, including all pots and pans; flatware; silverware; glasses; full-sized refrigerator/freezer; full-sized oven; four burner stove top; dishwasher and microwave oven.

1 Bedroom Condominium - All One bedroom condominium suites offer a fully equipped kitchen, separate living and dining areas, Private Washer/Dryer, cable TV, DVD/Video players, WIFI and ample space for the entire family; Bedrooms include queen size bed and a pull out sofa sleeper.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
All Condo suites equipped with full kitchen, including all pots and pans; flatware; silverware; glasses; full-sized refrigerator/freezer; full-sized oven; four burner stove top; dishwasher and microwave oven.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>