<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10546820</Id><Name>Posh South Beach Hotel &amp; Hostel</Name><Region><Id>21648</Id><Name>Miami Beach - South Beach</Name><CityId>19741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>820 Collins Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Miami Beach</City><State /><Zip>33139</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>305-398-7000</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>South Beach Group Hotel's latest concept, Posh South Beach is a luxurious hostel offering affordable accommodations for backpackers and travelers alike! This 5-star hostel invites international guests to engage in a shared-living experience and explore all that South Beach has to offer. Amenities: Spacious Room equipped with bunk beds, that include memory foam mattresses and privacy dividers A unique Rooftop Pool, complete with lounge chairs and outdoor furniture on a sun-bathing deck A self-catering kitchen, equipped with granite counter-tops and a sub-zero appliance Happy Hour every night from 7PM-8PMFree Drinks! On-site concierge, offering tours, attractions, and party buses to the hottest nightclubs. Amenities - Free Breakfast.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Posh South Beach is a fully renovated loft, at the epicenter of South Beach's shopping, attractions, and nightlife. Perfectly nestled on Collins Avenue, Posh South Beach is in the midst of all the action and right across the street from the beach.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Hostel Shared Hostel - Hostel Shared Hostel with twin bed includes secure locker with property provided padlock, reading light and really soft linens! Note, this is a HOSTEL or BACKPACKER hotel. Reservation for this room type is for 1 person in a twin size bed in a shared room.

Hostel Shared Hostel Girls Only - Hostel Shared Hostel with twin bed includes shared dorm-styled room. Dorm features double stacked custom designed twin bunk beds, secure locker with property provided padlock, reading light and really soft linens!</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>