<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10547150</Id><Name>The Loft Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21648</Id><Name>Miami Beach - South Beach</Name><CityId>19741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>952 Collins Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Miami Beach</City><State /><Zip>33139</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>305-534-2244</Tel><Fax>305-538-1509</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The boutique Loft Hotel offers hip and chic accommodations less than one block from the beach in the heart of South Beach in Miami, Florida. Recently renovated and featuring truly distinctive European styling, it is an upscale yet affordable address offering you spacious suites with queen-sized beds, breakfast nooks and kitchens, and separate living areas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Infused with refined warmth, our South Beach Hotel is the ultimate intimate oasis. You can relax and enjoy the lush tropical landscaping and serene garden. Other stylish flourishes include soft white curtains, superb views, laid-back chaise lounges and luxurious down comforters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Valet Parking is $30.00 plus tax per night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


Resort Fee of $15 per night + tax (payable directly to property) includes:&lt;br /&gt;
In-Room Safes&lt;br /&gt;
Wi-Fi Broadband Internet Access&lt;br /&gt;
Beach Towels (Available At Front Desk)&lt;br /&gt;
Beach Umbrellas (1st come 1st serve)&lt;br /&gt;
Coffee &amp; Tea Packs&lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in the heart of South Beach's historic Art Deco district, The Loft Hotel Miami is just one block from famed Ocean Drive --the world's most exciting hotspot and coolest locale. Just steps away from the azure waters of the Atlantic Ocean, The Loft Hotel is nestled beside the center of the city's most renowned shops, best Miami Beach dining establishments and the hottest South Beach nightlife. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience Miami's Cultural Diversity &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unwind and relax on Miami's beautiful South Beach during the day. Embrace the night at the most popular clubs, restaurants and cafes. Discover the fine art, design and architecture of the Art-Deco District. Immerse yourself in the deep cultural roots of communities like Little Havana and the Miccosukee Indian Village and experience exciting Miami special events year around!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>DELUXE - HOTEL - Room Amenities:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cable TV withVCR&lt;br /&gt;Fully Equipped Kitchen &lt;br /&gt;with refrigerator&lt;br /&gt;Complimentary Local Phone Calls&lt;br /&gt;Individual A/C and Heat&lt;br /&gt;Hair Dryer&lt;br /&gt;AM/FM Alarm Clock Radio&lt;br /&gt;Free Wireless Internet&lt;br /&gt;.In room safes&lt;br /&gt;.Daily Newspaper USA Today&lt;br /&gt;.Mini Bar</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>