<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10551968</Id><Name>Melrose Mansion</Name><Region><Id>21680</Id><Name>French Quarter</Name><CityId>19791</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>937 Esplanade Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New Orleans</City><State /><Zip>70116</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>504-944-2255</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>321</Height><Bytes>30732</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2462</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3508</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2303</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-7.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>252</Height><Bytes>34368</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Hotel-Exterior-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>133</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3350</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Pool-5.jpg</Url><Width>319</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>31278</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Pool-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Pool-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1505</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-10.jpg</Url><Width>321</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>21760</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-10</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-10.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1340</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>21918</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1849</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>22995</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2145</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>21387</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2010</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-8.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>26462</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1956</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-9.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>20289</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-9</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Suite-9.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1829</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Bathroom-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>252</Height><Bytes>14538</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Bathroom-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/87/81/2631759-Melrose-Mansion-Bathroom-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>133</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2062</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>For some, it's the mystery of what lies behind those century-old shutters. For others, it's the curiosity to feel what it's like to unwind and enjoy the luxuries of a beautifully restored Victorian Mansion. At the Melrose, the attention to detail will make you feel a part of New Orleans. Upon arriving at the Melrose Mansion, you will experience true southern hospitality from the always friendly staff, available to assist with luggage and ensure that your stay with the hotel is unforgettable. A light continental breakfast can be enjoyed each morning in the breakfast room which features a 75" flat screen television. Wine and cheese are also served each night in the parlor. The newly renovated luxury mansion sits on historic Esplanade Avenue in New Orleans just one block from the world famous French Quarter! The Melrose Mansion features 14 beautifully furnished suites with antiques and all modern amenities including 300 thread-count linens with down comforters, LCD flat screen television, IPod docking station, FACE toiletries, all-marble bathrooms with standing shower or Jacuzzi tub, ebony stained original hardwood floors, original artwork, and Wi-Fi. Hotel also has one of the largest swimming pools in the French Quarter complete with fountains which sits perfectly in the courtyard area of the mansion surrounded by lush trees and landscape. The Melrose is the perfect choice in one of the most historic areas of New Orleans for weddings and bridal parties alike. New to the Melrose Mansion, Salon 937 can provide all of your styling services, hair coloring, and haircuts for your entire bridal party on the big day!
Hotel also offers free breakfast to its guests!&lt;p /&gt;The Melrose Mansion has a mandatory Amenity Package of $12.95 per night which includes welcome amenities upon arrival,  continental breakfast served daily, wine and cheese served nightly, unlimited local and long distance phone calls, WIFI, usage of the in-room safe with safe insurance, and 24hr usage of the fitness center.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>From the Melrose Mansion's convenient location at the corner of Esplanade Avenue and Burgundy Street, you're mere steps to the French Quarter. By day, stroll a few blocks down the avenue in the direction of the Mississippi River to check out the French Market, home of Caf du Monde, and Jackson Square. The Melrose Mansion is also within walking distance to the starting points for several French Quarter Tours. And, if you're coming to experience some of the best in New Orleans nightlife and music, you're two blocks away from the always-lively strip of restaurants and jazz and live music clubs on Frenchmen Street. For those long nights that you don't want to end, drop in at Buffa's located just across the street from the mansion; the neighborhood bar is open 24/7. -adjacent to the French Quarter; located on historic Esplanade Avenue steps away -5 blocks to French Market -2 blocks to Bourbon St. -6 blocks to the Mississippi River -8 blocks to Jackson Square.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Luxury Junior Suite - Each of our 6 Junior Suites feature brand new modern furnishings with custom made headboards, IPOD docking stations, FACE toiletries, one king or queen sized bed, black &amp; white photography of New Orleans musicians, flat screen 40-50" LCD television, 350 thread count linens, ebony stained hardwood floors, cathedral ceilings, wireless internet, and marble bathroom with standing shower or Jacuzzi tub/shower combo. Many of our Junior Suites also feature a mini-fridge.

Luxury Master Suite - Each of our 3 Master Suites feature brand new modern furnishings with custom made headboards, IPOD docking stations, FACE toiletries, one king bed, separate sitting area, black &amp; white photography of New Orleans musicians, flat screen 50" LCD television, 350 thread count linens, ebony stained hardwood floors, cathedral ceilings, marble bathroom with standing shower or Jacuzzi tub/shower combo, mini fridge, wireless internet, and private or shared balconies.

Napolean Suite - Napoleon Suites
Each of our 5 Napoleon Suites are located in the Napoleon House behind the main house. These suites feature beautifully custom made &amp; antique furnishings, one king or queen sized bed, original artwork, IPOD docking stations, FACE toiletries, 350 thread count linens, ebony stained hardwood floors, flat screen 40-50" LCD television, cathedral ceilings, wireless internet, and marble bathroom with standing shower or Jacuzzi tub/shower combo

Marigny Suite - These open concept studio suites are truly your home away from home, giving you 550 square feet complete with a wide variety of amenities which includes 1 queen bed, glass top stove, oven, sub-zero refrigerator and freezer with ice maker, Nespresso coffee maker, Crate &amp; Barrel dining ware and bar ware, washer &amp; dryer, living room complete with contemporary furnishings, bar style dining, 2 flat screen internet ready 40" LCD televisions, 350 thread count linens and duvet covers, Carrera marble bathroom with standing shower and rain shower head, and FACE toiletries.

Esplanade Executive Suites - These newly renovated Executive Suites are truly your home away from home, giving you 1350 square feet complete with a wide variety of amenities which includes 1 king bed, glass top stove, oven, sub-zero refrigerator and freezer with ice maker, Nespresso coffee maker, Crate &amp; Barrel dining ware and bar ware, dishwasher, washer &amp; dryer, full living room complete with contemporary furnishings, dining table with bar stools, 2 flat screen internet ready 40" LCD televisions, 350 thread count linens and duvet covers, Carrera marble bathroom with oversized jacuzzi tub/shower combo with rain shower head, and FACE toiletries.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>