<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10560122</Id><Name>Drury Inn &amp; Suites Orlando</Name><Region><Id>21728</Id><Name>Int'l Drive Sea World</Name><CityId>19827</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>7301 West Sand Lake Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Orlando</City><State /><Zip>32819</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-407-354-1101</Tel><Fax>1-573-331-2887</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Extras Arent Extra at Drury Hotels. Your great rate includes FREE hot food and cold beverages at the 5:30 Kickback, FREE hot breakfast, FREE wireless Internet access and FREE long distance. Theres something for everyone at Drurys 5:30 Kickback.  It's a snack for some, meal for others and free for all.  The daily rotating menu features a variety of hot food, plus, beer, wine, mixed drinks and soft drinks.   Served 5:30-7:00 p.m. nightly.  Dont miss the great QUIKSTART breakfast buffet with scrambled eggs, sausage, biscuits and gravy, fresh fruit, bagels, pastries and more. Take advantage of FREE popcorn and soda every evening from 3-10 p.m. as well as the complimentary exercise room, and 24 hour business center. Recreational amenities at Drury include an indoor pool and a spa tub. Drury Hotels are family owned; you can always expect to receive award winning service during your stay.
The hotel has a smoke-free policy.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Situated in Orlando's Universal Orlando-International Drive North neighborhood, Drury Inn &amp; Suites Orlando is near Wet N' Wild and Ripley's Believe or Not  and just 3 miles from Universal Studios.  Sea World and Discovery Cove are also within 5 miles of the hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Deluxe Queen - 2 Queen Beds, non smoking; microwave and refrigerator; 37 inch LCD television; free wireless internet; free hot breakfast; free hot food and cold drinks every evening.

Deluxe King - 1 King bed; non smoking; microwave and refrigerator; 37 inch LCD television; free wireless internet; free hot breakfast; free hot food and cold drinks every evening</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>