<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10573875</Id><Name>The Jefferson Hotel, Washington DC</Name><Region><Id>21948</Id><Name>Capitol Hill - Dupont Circle</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1200 16th Street, Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington Dc</City><State /><Zip>20036</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-202-448-2300</Tel><Fax>202-448-3262</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Distinguished, sophisticated and discreet, this 99-room luxury boutique hotel exemplifies all that its namesake, Thomas Jefferson, held dear - intricately thought-out design, twenty elegantly appointed suites, the most modern amenities, gastronomic excellence and, of course, exceptional personalized service. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Since its re-opening from a top-to-bottom historic restoration, the hotel has been regularly heralded by leading travel authorities and experts including Travel + Leisure, Cond Nast Traveler, Robb Report and many more. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Visitors to The Jefferson enjoy a sophisticated European ambiance with the residential intimacy of a private home, as well as amenities that are strikingly modern in their technologies and comfort.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Guest also enjoy numerous on-site amenities , including complimentary Wi-Fi, a Monticello-inspired book room, and a fully-equipped fitness center
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The hotel has an ideal location, just four blocks from the White House and within a short walk of the Smithsonian museums, national monuments and the city's many embassies. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dining options include Plume, the city's highest Zagat-rated restaurant, and Quill, a craft cocktail destination
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The hotel features versatile meeting and private events space, including a private board room, bar and wine cellar.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The elegant ambiance of The Jefferson's hotel rooms and suites evokes the hotel namesake's cherished years in Paris as well as his time at Monticello. Extraordinary attention to detail conveys the sense that one is staying in a private residence.  Here, you might find a book on Monticello on your side table, or perhaps a vintage copy of Goode's Best Addresses.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Petite Spa features express and full treatments inspired by the herbs and botanicals grown on Thomas Jefferson's farms.  
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Evoking a stay at a grand private residence, each guest is personally greeted upon arrival and invited to settle into comfortable chairs facing residential-style desks for check-in.  Service that is intuitive, flawless and customized to each guest creates a welcome haven from the bustling world outside, offering a guest experience without parallel at any other Washington DC hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>In the heart of downtown Washington DC, The Jefferson, Washington, DC is located at the northwest corner of 16th and M Streets, NW.  We encourage guests to take advantage of the many historical treasures that our nation's capitol has to offer. Our concierge is happy to make suggestions to seasonal highlights and activities sure to keep you busy in DC. A wide variety of events and festivals are held throughout the year at many of the attractions and in the diverse neighborhoods of the city.
A complimentary house car is available on a first come basis to sites within the DC city limits.  Service is available weekday mornings from 7:30 am to 10:00am and weekday afternoons from 5:30 pm to and weekends from 8:30pm.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Premier King - This hotel room offers a skyline or city view and features one King bed.  The Italian marble bathroom features a large walk-in shower, a lighted, magnified makeup mirror and an in mirror television. 
All hotel room types feature the latest technology for business and entertainment, such as complimentary high-speed Internet and complimentary local and long distance telephone calls.
Found in each room is a large writing desk with data and electrical connections easily accessible within a drawer.
Each room is decorated in one of three elegant color schemes

Deluxe King - This is the most luxurious hotel guest room, affording a skyline or city view of Washington, D.C.  It features one King bed and an Italian marble bathroom.
The bathroom has a large walk-in shower, lighted, magnified makeup mirror and some offer an oversized soaking tub, two sinks and a bathroom window.
All hotel room types feature the latest technology for business and entertainment, such as complimentary high-speed Internet and complimentary local and long distance telephone calls.  Found in each room is a large writing desk with data and electrical connections easily accessible within a drawer.

Each room is decorated in one of three elegant color schemes

Deluxe Suite - The Deluxe Suite affords city views of Washington DC and a choice of gold or platinum color palettes.  The bedroom is furnished with a King bed, while a spacious separate parlor area has a pull-out sofa and small dining table.
The Italian marble bathroom features a separate shower and deep soaking tub, two sinks and a window.  All suites are furnished with the latest technology for business and entertainment, such as complimentary high-speed Internet and complimentary local and long distance telephone calls.
Found in the parlor of each suite is a large writing desk with data and electrical connections easily accessible within a drawer. Each suite has its own unique dcor inspired by Jefferson's loves, such as wine, music, books and horticulture.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>