<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10570595</Id><Name>The Pearl Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21822</Id><Name>Downtown/Airport (SAN)</Name><CityId>19918</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1410 Rosecrans</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Diego</City><State /><Zip>92106</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-619-226-6100</Tel><Fax>1-619-226-6161</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Down to Earth, Up with Style: The Pearl Hotel is San Diego's newest jewel. Welcome to this must-stay destination that looks and feels "alive"-inside and out-and breathes with energy morning, noon and night. The Pearl Hotel sports 23 designer rooms of comfort and distinction, combining a great central location with superior service and an audacious dash of vintage-modern flair. The Pearl Hotel is in historic Point Loma, one block away from beautiful San Diego Bay, two miles from the airport, and 10 minutes from the vibrant Gaslamp Quarter. Also, we're freeway-close, giving easy access to all that America's Finest City has to offer. Whether you're in town for business, for pleasure, or for both. 

&lt;p&gt;The Pearl is where want to be. Every day guest enjoy Affordable sophistication in a boutique hotel environment. Rooms featuring luxury amenities, free wireless internet and LCD TVs. Restaurant serving world-class small plates and entrees. Bar and lounge perfect for rest and relaxation. Proximity to major attractions, major beaches, shopping and business centers.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our facilities do no have rollaways, or cribs. We also cannot accommodate more than 2 people per room, and no one under 18 is permitted to stay at hotel.  We are a completely non-smoking property.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Area Location - The Vibrant Gaslamp Quarter and 2 miles from the Airport.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Jewel - Featuring a king platform bed, extensive casual furnishings, 32-inch LCD television, and superior storage space. Several of these deluxe-size rooms sport outdoor patios, adding more pleasure to the already comfortable and casual accommodations.  Room is approximately 250 square feet.

Strand - Featuring a king platform bed, seating area with casual furnishings, 42-inch LCD television, and a vast assortment of upscale features.  Select units include outdoor patios with dining furniture, making this our largest room and a really big winner among guests.  Room is approximately 250 square feet.

Gem - Featuring a queen platform bed, mirrored ceilings, free standing shower, and a 42 inch LCD television.  This bachelor-class room sports bold and sassy ways to go toe-to-toe with its roomier siblings.  Room is approximately 112 square feet.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>