<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10572357</Id><Name>Mystic Hotel by Charlier Palmer</Name><Region><Id>21827</Id><Name>Union Square - Nob Hill</Name><CityId>19919</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>417 Stockton Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Francisco</City><State /><Zip>94108</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>415-400-0500</Tel><Fax>+1 (415) 4000505</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Mystic Hotel Union Square San Francisco by Charlie Palmer is a smart, sleek retreat situated in the heart of the city's busiest neighborhoods. Conveniently located just one block from the iconic cable car line in the middle of three key destinations - Union Square, Chinatown and the Financial District - Mystic Hotel offers a convenient, comfortable and unique modern boutique hotel experience in a historic location. With a contemporary look and feel, our accommodations are designed to reflect the changing need of today's traveler. Enjoy high-touch service and an ideal Union Square location, perfect for travelers looking to experience all the adventures of San Francisco.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>MYSTIC JUNIOR - 185 sq ft.  Features a double bed, limited city view and exposed brick accent wall with a large encasement window. These rooms are recessed into the hotel and offer a quiet and peaceful sleeping environment.

MYSTIC ROOM - 200 sq ft. Appointed with a queen size bed, Stockton Tunnel or Union Square view with a stylish settee, efficient work surface, adjustable ambient lighting and either a classic bay window or exposed masonry wall.

MYSTIC STUDIO SUITE - 300-400 square feet. With a luxuriously outfitted queen or king size bed &amp; City views, the Crescent Suites offer celebrated San Francisco living with expanded lounge space and studio sleeper sofa. Added comforts feature a selection of wines from some of California's best small house producers, a custom bar with specially created cocktails from the City's most talented mixologists and a curated film, music &amp; book library.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>