<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10574234</Id><Name>The Hay-Adams</Name><Region><Id>21948</Id><Name>Capitol Hill - Dupont Circle</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>800 16th Street Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20006</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>202.638.6600</Tel><Fax>1-202-293-2396</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Originally designed in the 1920s as a residential hotel, the Hay-Adams has always preserved the ambiance of a distinguished private home on Lafayette Square. The 145 room hotel features 21 suites, some with views of Lafayette Park and the White House. All guest rooms combine heritage and luxury with contemporary comfort and technology. Washington's preeminent destination for power dining, The Lafayette serves breakfast, lunch, dinner and Sunday brunch. Overlooking Lafayette Square and the White House, this light-filled dining room offers a unique setting that is certain to complement your fine dining experience.&lt;br /&gt;Selected by Forbes.com as one of the Worlds Best Hotel Bars, Off the Record is well known as Washington's best place to be seen and not heard.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located on Lafayette Square, across from the White House, the Hay-Adams offers guests Washingtons most prestigious address with views overlooking the White House, Lafayette Square and St.Johns Church, the Church of the Presidents. The hotel is just minutes from the Smithsonian, the Washington Monument and the Mall, as well as convenient to Metro stations and the convention center. The Hay-Adams is just walking distance from many of Washington D.C. landmarks, and is the perfect place for both leisure and business travelers alike.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>SUPERIOR - ROOM - Featuring an interior or courtyard view, these accommodations offer one double or one queen-sized bed, and the same luxurious amenities as our special view rooms, including a beautiful marble bathroom, writing desk with high-speed Internet access, CD player, and windows which can be opened for fresh air.

SUPERIOR - ROOM - Featuring an interior or courtyard view, these accommodations offer one double and one twin or two double beds, and the same luxurious amenities as our special view rooms, including a beautiful marble bathroom, writing desk with high-speed Internet access, CD player, and windows which can be opened for fresh air.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>