<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10574118</Id><Name>Capella Washington D C Georgetown</Name><Region><Id>21950</Id><Name>Georgetown</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1050 31 Street, Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20007</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1 202 617 2405</Tel><Fax>+1 (202) 6172499</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/87Rfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/87Rthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1980</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/87Rbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/87Rthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1938</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/87Rmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/87Rthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1759</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Capella Washington, D.C., Georgetown has 49 guest rooms with 12 suites.  All rooms and suites have a central computer system with touch panels in the corridor and next to the bed on both sides, king beds, and rainforest shower-heads.  LCD TVs in the bed and living room(s) as well as the bathroom mirror, HSIA, I-Pod docking station, and refreshment center. The guest rooms will offer bedside control to control lighting, temperature and draperies. Refreshment centers will be customized to the guests needs whether they are low-carb, a special diet,low sodium or stuffed with candy and these items will be at additional charge to the guest.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Georgetown is a historic neighborhood, commercial, and entertainment district located in northwest Washington, D.C., situated along the Potomac River. The Capella Washington, D.C., Georgetown, converted from the former American Trial Lawyers Association building is a five-story building nestled alongside the famous Chesapeake and Ohio Canal.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>SUPERIOR - KING - Superior King Room with king bed includes Accessible facilities, Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) compliance,  Babysitting service,  Banquet facilities,  Bar, Business Center, Concierge,  Conference Facilities, Currency Exchange, Doctor on Call, Gym / Fitness facilities, Health Club, Internet - Free, Internet access - High-Speed, Internet access - Wireless, Internet in room - Free, Laundry Service, Lift / Elevator, Non-smoking rooms, Parking facilities - at cost, Pool, Public areas wheelchair accessible for disabled, Ramp Access to Buildings, Restaurant, Room service - 24 hrs, Safe Deposit Box, Service animals allowed, Service dogs allowed and Spa Services (Massage, Facial, Steam Room, etc.). Each spacious Superior King room features a plush king size bed with sitting area and desk. Enjoy glass enclosed rainfall showers and a fully-stocked complimentary coffee and refreshment station. Several rooms offer canal views. 359 sq ft /34 sqm.

SUPERIOR - DOUBLE - Superior Double Room with queen bed includes Accessible facilities, Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) compliance,  Babysitting service,  Banquet facilities,  Bar, Business Center, Concierge,  Conference Facilities, Currency Exchange, Doctor on Call, Gym / Fitness facilities, Health Club, Internet - Free, Internet access - High-Speed, Internet access - Wireless, Internet in room - Free, Laundry Service, Lift / Elevator, Non-smoking rooms, Parking facilities - at cost, Pool, Public areas wheelchair accessible for disabled, Ramp Access to Buildings, Restaurant, Room service - 24 hrs, Safe Deposit Box, Service animals allowed, Service dogs allowed and Spa Services (Massage, Facial, Steam Room, etc.). Each spacious Superior Double room features two plush queen size beds with sitting area and desk. Enjoy glass enclosed rainfall showers and a fully-stocked complimentary coffee and refreshment station. Several rooms offer canal views. 359 sq ft / 34 sqm.

DELUXE - KING - Deluxe King with king bed includes Accessible facilities, Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) compliance, Babysitting service, Banquet facilities, Bar, Business Center, Concierge, Conference Facilities, Currency Exchange, Doctor on Call, Gym / Fitness facilities, Health Club, Internet - Free, Internet access - High-Speed, Internet access - Wireless, Internet in room - Free, Laundry Service, Lift / Elevator, Non-smoking rooms, Parking facilities - at cost, Pool, Public areas wheelchair accessible for disabled, Ramp Access to Buildings, Restaurant, Room service - 24 hrs, Safe Deposit Box, Service animals allowed, Service dogs allowed and Spa Services (Massage, Facial, Steam Room, etc.). Light and airy, Deluxe rooms feature plush king size beds and a separate sitting area with desk. soak in tubs, separate glass-enclosed rainfall showers and fully-stocked complimentary coffee and refreshment station meet your every need. 480 sq ft /45 sqm.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>