<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>106723</Id><Name>Villa Canaima</Name><Region><Id>21239</Id><Name>Puerto del Carmen</Name><CityId>18407</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>C/ TOMILLO</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PUERTO DEL CARMEN</City><State /><Zip>35510</Zip><Country>Spain</Country><Tel>928.514360</Tel><Fax>928.512369</Fax><Email>villacanaima@villacanaima.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>2</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>31</CountRooms><CountFloors>3</CountFloors><Latitude>28.9214363</Latitude><Longitude>-13.6714934</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/05552hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>238</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/05552hotel1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>94</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2905</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/05552bar1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/05552bar1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2321</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>HotelAmenities</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Reception is open from Monday - Friday between 10am - 1pm.Flight details and arrival times are to be sent to reservation@villacanaima.com.at least 72hrs before arrival.
For arrivals after 21.00hrs and Saturday and Sunday arrivals the key to your apartment will be left in a security box and the code will be given on arrival.
The 24 hr telephone number in case of emergency is  0034 606859451</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>The Apartments Villa Canaima is a small, friendly complex situated in Matagorda in Puerto del Carmen, and located by the main and tranquil beaches of the island.
Nearby facilities include a mini-market, bus stop and taxi rank. The complex is only a stroll away from the beach and shopping centre, with supermarket, bars, restaurants and shops. There are sports facilities, like tennis, windsurfing and much more.
The apartments are fully equipped with kitchenette, television, telephone and safety deposit box (payable locally) and the majority have have pool views.
This is the ideal location for those looking for a relaxing location with full the full amenities of a nearby,bustling holiday resort.
The official rating for these apartments is 2 key however due to the facilities available we have given them our rating of 3 sun.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>5 Minute drive from the main airport in Lanzarote and situated in the quieter area of Matagorda, Puerto del Carmen.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Keys</System><Score>20</Score><Description>Two key</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>