<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10709189</Id><Name>Apollonia Resort &amp; Spa</Name><Region><Id>20763</Id><Name>Amoudara</Name><CityId>16664</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Po Box 32, Gazi</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Crete - Amoudara</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Islands</Country><Tel>2810821602</Tel><Fax>2810821433</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Hotel offers 144 double &amp; twin superior rooms, 57 family rooms, 82 superior bungalows &amp; 52 standard bungalows, 25 Single rooms, 2 presidential suites and 10 rooms specially designed for handicapped people. All with self controlled 24h air-condition, VINGCARD electronic lock, ELSAFE safe box, Sat -TV, hair drier, telephone, fridge, balcony or terrace, wi fi &amp; ADSL available.
Other Facilities:
4 Restaurants, a Greek tavern, one a la carte Italian restaurant and one more ethnic a la carte restaurant, pool snack bar, beach bar, cafeteria, cocktail bar, disco indoors and out doors, 2outdoor pools &amp; 1 paddling pool, 1 indoor pool, water slides, 2 tennis courts (1 floodlighted), children\'s-playground, pedaloes, canoes, wind surfing, scuba diving, waterskiing, card room, billiards, archering, table tennis, beach football, beach volley, shopping arcade, Supermarket, hair-dresser, boutique, jewellery shop, laundry and dry cleaning service, exchange office, beach towel service, beach chairs and umbrellas by the pool and the beach, large gardens and SPA.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hotel is situated on the sandy beach of Amoudara, and is an ideal location offering a variety of guest rooms, restaurants and conference facilities..
Distances from Apollonia Beach Resort &amp; Spa:
Knossos - 7km
Phaistos - 30km
Fodele (El Greco Museum) - 3km
Heraklion Center - 4km
Pankritio Stadium (Footballstadium) - 3km
Golf course - 25km</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>