<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10723057</Id><Name>Armonia</Name><Region><Id>20788</Id><Name>Lefkas</Name><CityId>16691</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Megalo Avlaki</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Lefkada - Nidri</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Islands</Country><Tel>26450 92751</Tel><Fax>2645092752</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The hotel complex is built in a characteristically traditional architectural style. The reception has a comfortable lounge area cocktail bar restaurant with grand views over the pool and sea. The outside bar and swimming pool which includes a safe toddlers section is elevated meeting the middle level of the main building and giving a picturesque view over the bay past the pontoon.
The hotel has 20 rooms, choose from top floor hotel rooms with sea view balcony 2-3 persons.
Spacious first floor side view studios for up to 4persons or garden view studios (also very spacious for up to 4).
All studios possess air-conditioning bath/shower w/c T.V hair dryer light kitchen facilities including fridge kettle balcony veranda, all spaciously designed in a light airy décor.
The hotel also has a magnificent 2-bedroom apartment for up to 6 persons on the upper floor of the main building which enjoys stunning views over Nidri Bay. The very large (80M2) open living/dining/kitchen area is comfortable with sofas T.V DVD player and beautiful pool sea and mountain views from the picture window here. Extra folding beds can be added to this room if required for children. The kitchen area is well equipped and has a full oven and fridge freezer. There is a large and very private balcony boasting magnificent sea and mountain views. The apartment has one double and one twin room, a large private shower room and it is fully air-conditioned. Special attraction is the private jetty for small craft enthusiasts or yachters wishing to combine sailing and hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Armonia Hotel is a family run hotel situated in a quiet area 200m south of the popular village of Nidri, 50m from the water overlooking spectacular views of tranquil bay. Nearest airport Aktio/Preveza is just 37km and Lefkas town 17km away.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>