<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10728604</Id><Name>Archontika Karamarli</Name><Region><Id>16707</Id><Name>Pelion</Name><CityId>16707</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Makrinitsa - Pelion</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Pelion - Makrinitsa</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Mainland</Country><Tel>24280 99570</Tel><Fax>2428099779</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The hotel consists of 18th century stone mansions, fully renovated and equipped with all modern amenities. External preserved all the elements of the old buildings with their original details. Battlements are even kept and preserved!
The hotel was created to offer comfort and service to its customers. The rooms differ considerably and are decorated with antiques from the personal collection of the Karamarlis family. In addition, each room includes lights specially chosen from an Italian gallery, colorful fabrics, mosaic floors, and water massaging bathtubs and fireplaces. Together, these items create a cozy home atmosphere with the scenery of a different era. 
The rooms have the following amenities: 
-Luxury furniture 
-Extra-double built-in beds and mattresses 
-Fireplace -LCD TV &amp; radio
-Central heating 
-Air conditioning 
-Phone 
-Water massage bathtubs (selected rooms only)
-Hair dryer 
-Safe deposit box 
-Panoramic view of the city of Volos and the Pagasitikos Bay.
-Balcony (selected rooms only)
Ηotel also offers parking space and car access</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel consists of 18th-century Pelion-style tower-houses and is centrally located in Makrinitsa, just 3 minutes away on foot from the main square filled offering traditional taverns. It boasts stone-paved courtyards with views of Pagasitikos Gulf and traditional luxury accommodation.
Makrinitsa is the most picturesque village in Pelion and cars are not allowed into the village.
Archontika Karamarlis is the only hotel that has access by two ways, by car from the national road and on foot from the traditional pavement. 
Near the hotel there are shops with traditional herbs, sweets, herbal cosmetics and local products. 
Archontika Karamarlis is 3 km from the charming village of Portaria. Agriolefkes Ski Resort is at a distance of 6 km while the town of Volos is 7 km away.
Splendid numerous  beaches are located 15 km away.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>