<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10729555</Id><Name>Royal Palas Resort</Name><Region><Id>10688398</Id><Name>Platamonas</Name><CityId>10688398</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>K. Karamanli 51</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Platamonas</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Mainland</Country><Tel>23520 42200</Tel><Fax>2352043700</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>GENERAL HOTEL SERVICES
	  	 
Customer services

Customer service;
Swimming pool and spa centre offering sauna, hydromassage, solarium, and steam bath services;
Gym with modern fitness equipment;
Massage facilities;
Roof Garden with views of the Thermaikos Bay, the harbour of
Platamonas and Mount Olympus;
3 lifts;
Direct-dial telephone;
Individual heating and air conditioning;
Underground parking;
Room service;
Laundry service;
Business services - venues;
Small meeting room;
CCTV;
24-hr security
The hotel offers 17 standard rooms and 2 suites.
All rooms have individual heating and air conditioning, cable TV, DVD player, phone, safety box, electric locks, free internet access, mini bar, hairdryer. Suites also have a hydromassage tub, laptop and fax.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>LOCATION
	  	 
The ROYAL PALACE Hotel &amp; SPA is located in the heart of Platamonas opposite the harbour.
Platamonas is a popular tourist resort in South Pieria, offering a range of entertainment and recreation choices and with interesting shops.
Its visitors can enjoy swimming in the blue waters of the Aegean Sea. Several picturesque beaches - some of them more bustling, others more secluded - are located at a distance of only a few kilometres from each other. Most of them are blue flag beaches with a beach bar and sunbeds and parasols for hire.
Mount Olympus and its picturesque villages such as Litochoro, Paleos and Neos Panteleimonas, Palii Pori and Palia Skotina are very close by.
Visitors can enjoy walking in the villages admiring traditional stone houses, hike around the beautiful nearby woods or taste local dishes in traditional village tavernas.
Platamonas Castle is a stone's throw away from the ROYAL PALACE Hotel. This fortress city dates back to the Middle Byzantine period (10th century AD) and occupies a strategic position commanding the route that links Macedonia to Thessaly and Southern Greece. The imposing medieval castle towers above the national motorway.
Platamonas is also close to the particularly interesting archaeological sites of Dion, Pydna and Livithra.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>