<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10735740</Id><Name>Classic</Name><Region><Id>16194</Id><Name>Nicosia</Name><CityId>16194</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>94 Rigenis Street, Po Box 21758</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nicosia</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Cyprus</Country><Tel>00357 22 664006</Tel><Fax>0035722670072</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>THE CLASSIC HOTEL
Located in the old city quarters of Nicosia, right in the heart of the business activity, the recently redesigned Classic Hotel blends perfectly with its environment, offering comfortable accommodation and a multidute of facilities just a few minutes walk from the city's business and commercial centre, as well as many goverment offices.
The 57 spacious rooms are fully equipped, offering air-conditioning, satellite TV channels, FREE-HIGH speed wireless internet and a mini bar with tea and coffee making facilities.
There are five conference rooms with total capacity for up to 400 delegates. All rooms are specially designed and adjusted for today's business needs. A team of events planners offers worry-free organisation, allowing you to concentrate on what's important - the business at hand.
HOTEL FACILITIES
A range of delicious international specialities is served at 59 KNIVES RESTAURANT, which also hosts themed nights with tasty buffets and entertainment. 
The BLUE WINE BAR has a full a la carte menu and over 300 wines from around the world. Live entertainment including jazz nights, piano and acoustic rock can be enjoyed.
The hotel's own Art Gallery showcases various artists from Greece and Cyprus.
The hotel's GYM is equipped with the latest cardio and weight machines and guests can hire personal trainers to work out with.
The newly opened HEALTH CENTRE offers a range of calming and relaxing massages.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Important place or monument close to the hotel: situated in the centre of Business and Trade within the Old Medieval Walls near museums, galleries, theatres,shops, restaurants, tavernas, nightlife, gym and attractions.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>