<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>107372</Id><Name>NH Aravaca</Name><Region><Id>21256</Id><Name>Madrid City Centre</Name><CityId>18417</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>ALSASUA 5</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ARAVACA</City><State /><Zip>28023</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>913571600</Tel><Fax>913570997</Fax><Email>nharavaca@nh-hotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.4641456</Latitude><Longitude>-3.7993909</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>479</Width><Height>401</Height><Bytes>32310</Bytes><Caption>2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Hotel-Exterior-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>83</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2038</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3440</Bytes><Caption>2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumbthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2227</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>479</Width><Height>334</Height><Bytes>23593</Bytes><Caption>2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>100</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2137</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>479</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>18263</Bytes><Caption>2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2037</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>479</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>24631</Bytes><Caption>2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-Guest-Room-5thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2208</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-in-Room-Amenity-3.jpg</Url><Width>479</Width><Height>479</Height><Bytes>24131</Bytes><Caption>2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-in-Room-Amenity-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/46/37/61/2631759-NH-Aravaca-Aparthotel-in-Room-Amenity-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1489</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The NH Aravaca hotel in Madrid provides a comfortable and convenient place for an extended stay while visiting Spain's exciting capital. Located just 10 minutes from the heart of the city, the NH Aravaca hotel enjoys excellent connections to the M-40 and National 6 highways, as well as El Barrial Train Station.
All of the 38 recently renovated rooms at the NH Aravaca hotel are designed to provide a home away from home while staying in Madrid. From the spacious Standard Room to the two-bedroom Apartment, guests can enjoy a full range of facilities and amenities such as a modern kitchen and living room equipped with stylish furnishings and appliances. 

A washing machine, large refrigerator, and wooden dining table, as well as a sofa and armchairs create a relaxing environment, perfect for the needs of business or leisure travelers staying at the NH Aravaca. Guests can make use of air-conditioning, satellite TV, and  free LAN or wireless internet connections, as well as rent extra items, including a microwave, DVD player and second TV.
 
Each morning at the NH Aravaca hotel begins with a healthy, delicious Continental breakfast. Ingredients are chosen for their anti-oxidant properties, ensuring a great start of the day. The breakfast area has also been refurnished to match the smart and welcoming environment of the NH Aravaca hotel in Madrid.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

From July, 13th to September, 9th the front desk timetable will be from 9:00 AM to 5:00 PM.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The NH Aravaca aparthotel is located in a strategic area of Madrid, with easy access to N-VI and M-40 highways, close to Barrial train station, which offers connections to Atocha. 
It is very close to Sexta Avenida and El Corte Ingles shopping centers, with a variety of shops and entertainment facilities. Just 10 minutes by car from Club de Campo Villa de Madrid, 5 minutes away from La Zarzuela hospital and 9 km away from Puerta de Hierro de Mahadahonda hospital. The hotel is surrounded by gardens and is very close to the mountains.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Room - Recently renovated for enhanced comfort and style, the Standard Rooms offer 25 square meters of bright airy space, ideal for business or leisure stays. Guests at the NH Aravaca can choose from a plush queen-size bed or two twin beds. The Standard Room also comes furnished with a table and chairs and a satellite TV. free LAN internet access ensures guests stay connected while visiting Madrid, and the kitchenette comes equipped with utensils, beverages, as well as an option to rent a microwave.

Apartment - The one-bed Apartment is 35 square meters and two-bed is 55 square meters. A modern equipped kitchenette, refrigerator and washing machine make for a comfortable extended stay. The adjacent living room has a table, sofa and armchairs for total relaxation in warmly decorated surroundings. Guests can enjoy satellite TV, free LAN and wireless internet access and individually controlled air-conditioning for all entertainment and connectivity needs. Smoking and non-smoking apartments are available, and guests can add an extra TV, DVD player or microwave to recreate all the comforts of home.

Junior Suite - Ideal for extended stays while in Madrid on business or pleasure, Junior Suites are elegant and comfortable. At 50 square meters the Junior Suite is spacious, with either a queen-size or two twin beds. The Junior Suites at NH Aravaca feature a large living room with stylish furniture, which includes a sofa and wooden dining table. The modern kitchen comes fully equipped with utensils, refrigerator, as well as a washing machine and an option to rent a microwave. Guests can relax in the living room with satellite TV or stay connected with free LAN and wireless internet access.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>