<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10747381</Id><Name>Kozatskyi Stan</Name><Region><Id>19285</Id><Name>Kiev</Name><CityId>19285</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>18th Km Boryspilska Highway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Kiev</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Ukraine</Country><Tel>00380 44 5851165</Tel><Fax>00380445851164</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Expocentre of Ukraine National Complex is located close to the hotel. 
The hotel offers accommodation in 58 rooms of different categories  Standard, Junior Suite, and Apartment. Every room features a hair-dryer, a minibar, air-conditioning, satellite TV, Internet access.
The Getmansky and the Litoral restaurants offer dishes of Ukrainian cuisine. The Wild Forest bar offers a choice of cocktails and live music.
The Kozatsky Stan Hotel has two conference halls, the European and the Capital, and a meeting room. The conference halls accommodate up to 200 people and are equipped with up-to-date facilities.
The following hotel services are also at guests  disposal  a parking lot, laundry and dry-cleaning services, a business centre, taxi call, a sauna.  

 Built   2008 NumberOfBlocks   1 NumberOfRooms   58 NumberOfFloors   4 SpecialRequirements   Cancellation of the bookings without penalty - 2 days prior to arrival. For  EURO 2012  period rates are to be requested. Hotel Category   MODERATE TOURIST Other amenities/ services   Hotel in recreation area Guarded parking Safe deposit box at reception ATM Elevator Bar Laundry service Dry cleaning service Business centre, 24 hours a day Taxi Rent a car Air / railway tickets Baby sitting Newspapers Billiards Pets accepted Change of bed linen daily in all rooms Room-service, 24 hours a day Electronic door locks in all rooms Phone in all rooms Bathrobe available Slippers available Hypoallergenic bed linen in all rooms Shower in all rooms Bathtub available Bathroom floor heating available Kettle available DVD player available</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Kozatsky Stan Hotel is situated at the Kyiv gates, 15 minutes  drive to the downtown, railway and bus stations, and Boryspil International Airport. CityCentre   City centre - 16,5 km Underground   Boryspilska - Syretsko-Pecherska line - 0,8 km Description   Expocentre of Ukraine National Complex Airport   Boryspil-A - 24 km, Boryspil-B - 24 km, Boryspil-C - 24 km, Boryspil-F - 24 km RailwayStation   Kyiv - 20 km RiverPort   River terminal - 18 km</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>