<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10764393</Id><Name>Esteghlal West Old Wing</Name><Region><Id>17008</Id><Name>Tehran</Name><CityId>17008</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Crossroads Of Dr.chamran Expressway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Tehran</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Iran</Country><Tel>0098 21 22660011-25</Tel><Fax>00982122660031</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Parsian Esteghlal consists of two towers, the West (old wing) &amp; the East (new wing) each with 15 floors,with luxurious rooms and suites, not only is the biggest and the most glorious hotel in the capital city, but also from various aspects is exclusive in the Islamic Republic of Iran.
Rooms &amp; suites equipped with luxury , all having safety system of fires extinguishers, private safe boxes , Satellites channels, high speed internet, mini-bar, 24 hours room service are among other facilities of five star Parsina Esteghlal Hotel.
The large suites of hotel West tower are equipped with three separate rooms and vast view of Tehran .The large suites in East tower consists of one room  and a meeting room to hold meetings with a vast view of Tehran northern heights at upper levels are anther reason for exclusiveness of this hotel. It is neccesary to mention that all 42 small suites have been well equipped with modern technologies, communication tools, furniture and decoration of Iranian artists.
Conference &amp; Banquet Halls, Iranian and Foreign Restaurants.
·   Daryay-e- Nour Hall  (Sea of Light ) with a capacity of 1000 people
·   Yas Restaurant No1 ( Jasmine Restaurant ) with a capacity of 300 people
·   Yas Banquet No2   ( Jasmine Banquet) with capacity of 300 people
·   Abshar seasonal restaurant  ( Waterfall seasonal restaurant)  
·   Lobby &amp; Mirage coffee shop
·   Rose , Neauphle le Chateau ,Thai, Italian , French and Arabic restaurants with experienced chefs offering all kinds of Iranian and international meals for all tastes have a remarkable role in registering good memories for the local and foreign guests. 
Recreational &amp; Business Services:
24 hours room service, Health Club, laundry, Business center, High speed internet, luggage room, Safe deposit box, various satellite channels, special TV movie channels, transfer and pickup to city center, airport, Tehran’ sites seeing &amp; recreational sites, currency exchange, shops of handmade rugs- gold &amp; jewelry, paintings, handy crafts &amp; exhibitions ,photography&amp; film services, clothing shops, leathern commodities, various gifts, cigarettes &amp; flower shop and car parking with capacity of 250 cars are other capabilities of five star Parsian Esteghlal Hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The five star Persian Esteghlal International Hotel is situated in the down foot of the Alborz mountain range with 90,000 m2 area, conveniently located in the north of Tehran, 2 kilometres from the Tehran International Fair and 4 kilometres from the Shahid Beheshti University. A golf club and the lovely Mellat-Park is also within easy reach. At a distance of 22 kilometres, the Mehrabad International Airport is located.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>