<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>108143</Id><Name>Balear</Name><Region><Id>21265</Id><Name>Can Pastilla </Name><CityId>18419</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PZ. BARTOLOME RIUTORT 18</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CA'N PASTILLA</City><State /><Zip>07610</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>971261212</Tel><Fax>971260108</Fax><Email>HOTELBALEAR@HOTMAIL.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>39.536037</Latitude><Longitude>2.717453</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/13/75/83/2631759-Balear-Hotel-Mallorca-Island-Other-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>318</Height><Bytes>29772</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Balear-Hotel-Mallorca-Island-Other-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/13/75/83/2631759-Balear-Hotel-Mallorca-Island-Other-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2471</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/13/75/83/2631759-Balear-Hotel-Mallorca-Island-Other-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3463</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Balear-Hotel-Mallorca-Island-Other-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/13/75/83/2631759-Balear-Hotel-Mallorca-Island-Other-1_thumbthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2251</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The hotel is great value for both tourists and business travelers as it is located a mere 50 meters from the beach and only 6 km from downtown Palma. A family-run establishment allowing giving personalized attention to clients. Rooms were recently remodeled in 2009 to enhance the comfort of guests. The Hotel Balear has its own restaurant, serving a generous breakfast buffet daily.  All 54 rooms are equipped with a telephone, air conditioning, central heating and safety deposit box. The majority of rooms have a terrace overlooking the plaza or sea. All rooms offer Internet access via Wi-Fi and cable for guests with laptops. For guests traveling without a laptop, it offers Internet access in reception as well as other business services. Reception is open 24 hours a day. It always offers guests the possibility of a late check-out, availability permitting.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located only 50 meters from the sandy beach of Playa de Palma and 6 kilometers from downtown Palma, the Hotel Balear an unbeatable location both for tourists and business travelers. Central location also facilitates travel to the other main cities of the island. The Playa de Palma offers a wealth of complementary activities that guarantee for a magnificent visit. The beach, 6 kilometres long and some 50 meters wide, was granted the E.C. "blue flag". Thanks to its walkways closed to traffic, one can enjoy the tranquility characteristic of the island or participate in a variety of sporting activities such as cycling, skating, volleyball, soccer, and games for kids, etc. In the area, car, bicycle and scooter rentals are also readily available. The square in front of the hotel hosts a farmer's market with local produce and other products every Tuesday and Thursday morning.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Triple Room - Triple rooms offer three single beds and are ideal for a family or for three friends. Triple rooms are equipped with a telephone, air conditioning, central heating and safety deposit box. The majority of rooms have a terrace overlooking the plaza or sea. All rooms offer Internet access via Wi-Fi and cable for guests with laptops. For guests traveling without a laptop, it offers Internet access in reception as well as other business services.

Standard Room - Rooms offers 1 double/twin beds are equipped with a telephone, air conditioning, central heating and safety deposit box. The majority of rooms have a terrace overlooking the plaza or sea. All rooms offer Internet access via Wi-Fi and cable for guests with laptops. For guests traveling without a laptop, it offers Internet access in reception as well as other business services.

Family Room - Suites offers double/twin beds have two adjoining bedrooms with a shared bathroom. Suites are equipped with a telephone, air conditioning, central heating and safety deposit box. The majority of rooms have a terrace overlooking the plaza or sea. All rooms offer Internet access via Wi-Fi and cable for guests with laptops. For guests traveling without a laptop, it offers Internet access in reception as well as other business services.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant Smoking Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Launderette</Code><Text>Launderette</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>