<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10816795</Id><Name>The W14 Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52887</Id><Name>Kensington &amp; Earls Court</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>16-22 Gunterstone Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W14 9BU</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>02076026600</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-10.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>19849</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-10</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-10.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1982</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-8.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>32306</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2128</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-9.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>21394</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-9</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Dining-9.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1825</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>34932</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2555</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>4129</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2537</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>36266</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2060</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>19197</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2040</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-11.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>33601</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-11</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-11.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2424</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-12.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>37605</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-12</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-12.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2088</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-13.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>30777</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-13</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-13.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2143</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-14.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>23884</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-14</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Property-Amenity-14.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2180</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>16957</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1734</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>13741</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1413</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>14677</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1434</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>377</Height><Bytes>23820</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/65/22/21/2631759-The-W14-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>89</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1912</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The W14 Hotel London is a 3 star Budget Hotel located in trendy Kensington, Central London and sets a new standard for budget accommodation Londonand the UK.
The W14 Hotel spans four beautiful Victorian town houses with original features, mixed in with clean fresh contemporary deco. Situated in a quiet, leafy, residential hotel location conveniently away from all the excitement London can offer, yet close to the prestigious shops of High Street Kensington.

The W14 Hotel not only provides safe and comfortable accommodation, but also a beautifully lit tranquil hotel garden with Hot Tub, Gas Heaters and BBQ. The quiet W14 hotel bar, Internet Room, hotel TV lounge and games room are all part and parcel of this well-loved Kensington budget Hotel.
Accommodation Information
The W14 Hotel has an extensive choice of budget hotel rooms, ranging from double rooms with private patio to en-suite dormitories, with prices from only 12 per bed, including a free continental breakfast!
The W14 Hotel offers unbeatable value and facilities whether you're a family, group or lone traveller. Each hotel room has its own security locker, high quality beds and electronic swipe card access making them comfortable, modern and secure. W14 Hotel London really is an excellent budget London hotel.

We have the following mix of room types.
	Double En-Suite Rooms (1 Double Bed)	
	Twin En-Suite Rooms (2 Single Beds)	
	Triple En-Suite Rooms (1 Double Bed &amp; 1 Single Bed)
	Quad En-Suite Rooms (2 Doubles Or 1 Dbl &amp; 2 Sgls)
	Twin Rooms with Shared Facilities	
	Bed in a 4-Bed Dormitory Room with Shared Facilities
	Bed in a 4-6-Bed FEMALE Dormitory Room with Shared Facilities
	Bed in a 6-Bed Dormitory Room with Shared Facilities


Direction:
From Baron's court tube station - turn left as you leave the station and cross the main road onto Gliddon Road. Continue walking for a few minutes and turn right onto Gunterstone Road. Walk for a further few minutes and W14 Hotel is located on the right hand side, at number 16-22.
From West Kensington tube station - turn right as you leave the station and cross over the main road towards the shops. As you start to walk down North End Road, turn left onto Gunterstone Road. W14 hotel is located a few minutes' walk on the left hand side at number 16-22.


We offer clean and comfortable rooms and dormitories with great facilities:

W14 Hotel
- 24hr reception, no curfew, no lockout
- CCTV &amp; Alarm activated Emergency Exists
- Free Wi-Fi to use on your laptop, phone or pda.
- Free Breakfast (7:30 - 9:30) is served downstairs in the Breakfast Room (Bread/Toasts Butter,        
  Jam, Marmalade, Cereals, Milk, Coffee, Tea, Hot Chocolate &amp; Juice)
- Free Towels
- Free Bed Linen
- Secure Electronic Key Card Access 
- Free lockers and safe for each dorm bed (Bring your own lock or we can sell you one 2.50)
- Fully equipped self-catering kitchen (Cook your own meals.)
- Washing / Drying / Ironing facilities 
- Internet room: write emails, talk via Skype, play games or type your CV.
- Direct links to Heathrow Victoria (from Victoria coach station)

W14 Bar
- Lounge Area with Large screen TV
- Bar with affordable drinks and daily entertainment 
- Bars open from 11am until late every night! (18+ only)
   (Happy Hour is every day between 2.00-5.30pm) 
- Come and play Pool or Table Football in the games room or use slot machines, what a great way   
  to meet people!
- Vending Machine with a variety of Snacks

Reception
- Free Travel and Local Information 
- Tours and Tickets available
- Free Luggage storage before and after your stay
- Check-out time: 10.30 am (yes you can leave your bags @ Reception upon check-out)</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The W14 Hotel London is very close to Royal Albert hall and high street Kensington, near to natural history museum, Hyde park corner, science museum, earl's court exhibition center, Kensington Olympia and Notting hill and close to Chelsea football stadium, near by Harrods, west filed shopping center easy commute by public transport to oxford circus, Piccadilly circus, Big Ben, Westminster parliament and London eye etc.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Double Ensuite - All rooms are non smoking and are comfortably furnished with en-suite facilities offering complimentary toiletries.  Within the room you will find a complimentary hospitality tray, colour television and a hairdryer.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  Additionally all rooms are centrally heated.  Daily maid service is provided.  *** Free Continental breakfast is included for all our guests ***

Twin Private - Shrd Fac - The rate quoted for this room is per bed.  All rooms are non smoking, comfortably furnished with bunk beds (maximum 4 people per dormitory) and are centrally heated.  The shared bathroom facilities are located within a short distance of your room.  You can buy toiletries from the Reception and can also buy or rent towels from the Reception.  Free linen can be collected from Reception 24 hours a day.  There is a television in the common.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  These are mixed dormitories but we try our best to provide same sex dorms.  *** Free breakfast is included for all our guests ***

Bed In Dorm - 4 Bunk Beds - The rate quoted for this room is per bed.  All rooms are non smoking, comfortably furnished with bunk beds (maximum 4 people per dormitory) and are centrally heated.  The shared bathroom facilities are located within a short distance of your room.  You can buy toiletries from the Reception and can also buy or rent towels from the Reception.  Free linen can be collected from Reception 24 hours a day.  There is a television in the common.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  These are mixed dormitories but we try our best to provide same sex dorms.  *** Free breakfast is included for all our guests ***

Bed In Dorm - 6 Bunk Beds - The rate quoted for this room is per bed.  All rooms are non smoking, comfortably furnished with bunk beds (maximum 4 people per dormitory) and are centrally heated.  The shared bathroom facilities are located within a short distance of your room.  You can buy toiletries from the Reception and can also buy or rent towels from the Reception.  Free linen can be collected from Reception 24 hours a day.  There is a television in the common.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  These are mixed dormitories but we try our best to provide same sex dorms.  *** Free breakfast is included for all our guests ***

Triple Ensuite - All rooms are non smoking and are comfortably furnished with en-suite facilities offering complimentary toiletries.  Within the room you will find a complimentary hospitality tray, colour television and a hairdryer.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  Additionally all rooms are centrally heated.  Daily maid service is provided.  *** Free Continental breakfast is included for all our guests ***

Twin Ensuite - All rooms are non smoking and are comfortably furnished with en-suite facilities offering complimentary toiletries.  Within the room you will find a complimentary hospitality tray, colour television and a hairdryer.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  Additionally all rooms are centrally heated.  Daily maid service is provided.  *** Free Continental breakfast is included for all our guests ***

Quad Ensuite - All rooms are non smoking and are comfortably furnished with en-suite facilities offering complimentary toiletries.  Within the room you will find a complimentary hospitality tray, colour television and a hairdryer.  For your added security all rooms can only be accessed with a key card and there are individual lockers within rooms for which you must use your own padlock.  Additionally all rooms are centrally heated.  Daily maid service is provided.  *** Free Continental breakfast is included for all our guests ***</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>