<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10817156</Id><Name>13 Half Moon Street Apartment</Name><Region><Id>52927</Id><Name>West End &amp; Marble Arch</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>Half Moon Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W1J 7BH</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-207-016-5626</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>15009</Bytes><Caption>2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2623</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3673</Bytes><Caption>2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2323</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>27551</Bytes><Caption>2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1975</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>16578</Bytes><Caption>2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2855</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>25727</Bytes><Caption>2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/73/43/31/2631759-13-Half-Moon-Street-Apartment-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2326</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>No 13 Half Moon Street Mayfair is situated adjacent to its sister property, The Flemings Hotel, in the heart of London's fashionable Mayfair. 10 fully serviced, spacious and luxurious apartments ensure a relaxing and comfortable stay. Located in the heart of central London, No 13 Half Moon Street Apartments are ideally located for business and pleasure. Situated adjacent to its sister property, Flemings Hotel, 10 apartments and 119 hotel bedrooms are located just a stone's throw from Buckingham Palace, Bond Street, Piccadilly Circus and London's Theatre District. Dating back to the 1730's this luxurious four-star deluxe Georgian property is a clever fusion between the 18th century's traditional charm and elegance and today's modern amenities and features suitable for both families of the business traveler.  The luxury apartments feature their own private entrance and ensure privacy and peace in the centre of London. Each spacious apartment is perfect for long term stays; families or guests who would like to hold small meetings throughout their stay.  Apartments boast air conditioning, full kitchen facilities, LCD television with pay movies and cable channels, high speed internet access, in room safe, CD player and radio with selection of CDs, iron and ironing board, trouser press, hairdryer, bathrobes, DDI and voicemail telephone, first aid box and secured entrance. One, two, three bedroom and penthouse apartments can be booked for a minimum one-night stay or longer periods, which can be discussed upon request. Each apartment benefits from the full service facilities extended by Flemings Mayfair hotel and a Guest Relations Manager will personally show each guest to their apartment to clarify the services and amenities on offer.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>No 13 Half Moon Apartments are ideally located in London's exclusive Mayfair, just a stone's throw from Green Park and Buckingham Palace and a short walk from Bond Street. Green Park underground station has easy links to Heathrow Airport, Victoria Station for Gatwick Airport and Kings Cross St Pancras for the Eurostar.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>One Bedroom apartment - Room offers a double bed with air conditioning, alarm clock, bathrobe, cable/satellite TV, CD player, color TV, crockery/cutlery, disabled facilities, DVD player, ensuite/private bathroom, hairdryer, heating, internet access, Iron/Ironing board, kettle, full kitchen, laundry service, microwave oven, non smoking rooms, pay-per-view-movies, radio, refrigerator, room service, safe in room, shaver in bathroom, stove/oven, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone, toaster, voicemail and washing machine.

Two Bedroom Apartment - Room offers two double beds with air conditioning, alarm clock, bathrobe, cable/satellite TV, CD player, color TV, crockery/cutlery, disabled facilities, DVD player, ensuite/private bathroom, hairdryer, heating, internet access, iron/ironing board, kettle, full kitchen, laundry service, microwave oven, non smoking rooms, pay-per-view-movies, radio, refrigerator, room service, safe in room, shaver in bathroom, stove/oven, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone, toaster, voicemail and washing machine.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>