<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10816027</Id><Name>High Street Kensington Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52887</Id><Name>Kensington &amp; Earls Court</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>5 Prince Of Wales Terrace</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W8 5PG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 587 3010</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Set just a stone's throw from Hyde Park and a short walk from Kensington High Street these London apartments offer an ideal location in the capital. A wealth of famous sights and popular attractions are just a short distance away and you'll be spoilt for choice by the many shops, bars and restaurants located close by. They offer variety of apartment types: - Studio Apartment - One Bedroom Apartment for 3 people - One Bedroom Apartment for 4 people its Services Comfortable and convenient the High Street Kensington Apartments are an excellent choice for a business trip or short break. Providing you with the service of a hotel but with the space, comfort and flexibility of home, these Kensington apartments are the perfect base. They provide serviced accommodation for short term in the heart of London. For example some of the general facilities are: - Airport Transfers - Linen Change - Luggage Room - Maid Service/Housekeeping - Secure Entry System - Security.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Kensington is one of the most attractive locations in the capital offering visitors a great selection of famous sights, fabulous shopping and more. The apartments are just a stone's throw from Hyde Park and within easy walking distance of Kensington Palace, Kensington High Street and the Royal Albert Hall.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Residential Apartment Studio - Studio Apartment Maximum Occupancy: 3 This studio apartment offers a combined living and sleeping area with a double bed and a sofa bed suitable for one person, there is also a kitchenette and a bathroom with shower only. Floor: First &amp; Second Floor.

Residential apartment Apartment - One Bedroom Apartment for 3 people Maximum Occupancy: 3 This one bedroom apartment comes equipped with a double bed in a spacious room and a sofa bed in the living room suitable for one person, kitchenette and a bathroom. Floor: First &amp; Third Floor

Residential apartment Apartment - Large One Bedroom Apartment Maximum Occupancy: 4 This spacious one bedroom apartment comes equipped with a double bed in large room as well as a double sofa bed in the living room, kitchenette and a bathroom Floor: Lower Ground Floor, Ground Floor, First Floor, Second Floor &amp; Third Floor.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>