<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10828437</Id><Name>Georgian House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52923</Id><Name>Southbank</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>37 Saint Georges Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW1V 4DG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44- 207-8341438</Tel><Fax>44-207-9766085</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>20957</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>50</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1355</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2655</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1850</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>17294</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2089</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>19503</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2102</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>18247</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2107</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>18016</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2053</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>23265</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2301</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>19073</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2105</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-8.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>23112</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/30/15/42/2631759-Georgian-House-Hotel-Guest-Room-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2240</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Georgian House Hotel is a charming hotel located in the centre of London. Built in 1851, it is still run by the original family. This independent hotel offers a high standard of central London accommodation, with an emphasis on comfort and warm service at a cheap and affordable price. The Georgian House Hotel complex consists of two buildings with a Reception located in the Main Building.

The Georgian House Apartments are a perfect home from home in the heart of London. They are situated in a quiet residential street, just a short walk from the hotel. They are contemporary and stylish. The rooms are beautifully proportioned and full of light and space, with lots of the original features of the house, which was built in 1851. They are fully fitted and are ideal for a longer stay, or for a family group. 

Beds: the apartments are available with :

2 single beds (3ft x 6ft 3in 90 x 190cm) 
1 double bed (4ft 6in x 6ft 3in 135 x 190cm) 
1 super king size bed (6ft x 6ft 6in 180 x 200cm) 

All the apartments have 1 sofa bed, and some have 2 sofa beds available (4ft x 6ft 3in 120cm x 190cm) so the maximum capacity is 6 guests. For booking for 5 guests or more please contact the hotel for assistance by telephone or email.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel, close to Victoria Station, is ideally situated for access to all of London. All the main attractions of the city are within easy reach; a short walk to the King's Road, the Chelsea Flower Show, and the Hard Rock Cafe. The hotel is near Big Ben and Buckingham Palace, and very convenient for shopping in Oxford Street or Knightsbridge and Harrods.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Single Ensuite - Standard single room with 1 single bed and ensuite bathroom. Amenities in the room: TV, hairdryer, radio, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone.

Standard Double Ensuite - Standard double room with 1 double bed and ensuite bathroom. Amenities in the room: TV, hairdryer, radio, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone.

Standard Triple Ensuite - Standard triple room with 3 twin bed or 1 double bed and 1 single bed and ensuite bathroom. Amenities in the room: TV, hairdryer, radio, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone.

Standard Quad Ensuite - Standard family room with 1 double bed and 2 single beds (bedding may vary) and ensuite bathroom. Amenities in the room: TV, hairdryer, radio, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone.

Classic Double Room - Classic double room with 1 double bed and ensuite bathroom. 
Amenities in the room: TV, hairdryer, radio, tea and coffee making facilities, telephone. 
Classic rooms are located in both - The Main and Adjacent Buildings - rooms will be allocated upon availability. The Adjacent Building is within 2 minute walking distance.

One Bedroom Apartment - All the apartments have 1 sofa bed, and some have 2
Bathrooms: all of the apartments are equipped with shower and toilet. 
Kitchens: all kitchens are fitted with fridge, oven, hob, toaster, kettle, cooking implements, crockery, cutlery, ironing facilities, washing facilities.
Seating: desk, chair and stool, dining table and chairs.
Other: the apartments have flat screen digital TV, DVD and freeview, and clock radios.
Internet: wireless 24 hour broadband connection available for free. If you are travelling without a PC then they are available to use at reception for a small fee.
Breakfast: complimentary full English breakfast
Service: there is a daily cleaning service including making the beds, cleaning the bathroom and changing the bins.

Economy Double Room wth Shared Bathroom - Basic room with Double bed. These basic rooms are on the fourth floor. The rooms here are very sweet. They have telephone, television, safes, tea and coffee facilities and are offered at good value prices. They also have hand wash basin. However, they do not have private bathroom. There are shared bathrooms and shower rooms on the landing. No Lift access to the fourth Floor.

Economy Single Room with Shared Bathroom - Basic room with a Single bed. These basic rooms are on the fourth floor. The rooms here are very sweet. They have telephone, television, safes, tea and coffee facilities and are offered at good value prices. They also have hand wash basin. However, they do not have private bathroom. There are shared bathrooms and shower rooms on the landing. No Lift access to the fourth Floor.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>