<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10828959</Id><Name>Churchill House Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>40 Laystall Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>EC1R 4PQ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 751 006 2715</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Hotel-Exterior-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>21081</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Hotel-Exterior-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Hotel-Exterior-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1934</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Hotel-Exterior-3_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2876</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Hotel-Exterior-3_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Hotel-Exterior-3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1943</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>13809</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1800</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>12278</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1711</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>11261</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1427</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>12166</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/03/41/2631759-Churchill-House-Apartments-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1729</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>These luxury apartments have a stylish decor, free Wi-Fi and a modern, equipped kitchen. Farringdon Tube Station is an 8-minute walk away, and bus stops and eating places are close by. The 1 and 2-bedroom apartments at Churchill House Residence have a separate seating area, flat-screen TV and dining area. The kitchen has an oven, microwave and fridge. Bedrooms have unique, modern furnishings. Some apartments have a balcony and terrace area. Keys must be collected from an address in Camden, 3 miles away. Please see the Important Information section for further details. The Eurostar service at St Pancras International Station, and Kings Cross Train Station, are just 1 Tube stop from Farringdon Station. The famous Smithfields Meat Market is 15 minutes' walk from Churchill House Residence. 

Check-In Information:
To check in, go to the following address:
Ground Floor, 47 Kentish Town Road, Waterside House, London NW1 8NX. Here you will receive the keys and pay for the stay. Please notice that your apartment is at a different address. Please telephone the local office at least 1 hour before your arrival (using the contact number provided in your booking confirmation). If you do not do this, you may have to wait much longer to check in. Check-in after 21:00 will be at an additional cost.


IMPORTANT CHECK IN INFORMATION:
Check In for this apartment is located at:
Ground Floor, 47 Kentish Town Road, Waterside House, London NW1 8NX

How to get to our office: 
The closest underground station is Camden Town on the Northern Line (black line). Take the exit on the LEFT hand side, when exiting the station turn left and walk straight up on Kentish Town Road. The office building is on the left hand side after crossing the Canal (brick building with blue entrance doors), about 3 minutes walking time from the station. Please ring the bell labelled ApartmentsApart, Ground Floor office - Right side.

CHECK IN AND CHECK OUT: 
Check-in from: 15:00
Check-out: 11:00 am 
LATE CHECK IN FEE: 
Between 9 PM and 12 PM - 20 GBP 
From 12 PM - 30 GBP and check in after 21.00 only upon earlier arrangements.

Arrivals between 21:00 and midnight will be subject to a late check-in fee of GBP 20.00 and GBP30.00 from 00:00

During your check in you:
A) fILL IN OUR GUEST FORM
B) Facilitate the outstanding payment
C) Provide us with your credit card details OR leave a cash deposit of GBP150.00 to cover any possible damage that might be incurred to the apartment or its contents, during your stay. In case you choose to leave a deposit, it is refunded after check-out, once the apartment has been proved free of damage.
D) Only upon payment you receive the keys to your apartment.

Groups of 6 or more will be charged a security deposit of GBP50.00 per person.

Accepted payment methods:
Preferred method of payment: CASH
Visa, Mastercard, Visa Electronare subject to a surcharge of 1.7%
Other cards are subject to a surcharge of 4.2% Amex or Maestro cards are not accepted. Please bring a photocopy of a picture ID of the person in whose name the reservation was made and a of any person paying by credit card.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Formerly known for its watchmaking industry and Italian population, Clerkenwell is now packed with modern restaurants and bars, including the Michelin-starred Club Gascon and the traditional, award-winning St John restaurant. Numerous gastropubs populate the area, and the bustling 800-year-old Smithfield Meat Market sells a huge variety of fresh meat within grand, Victorian surroundings. Camden In the heart of North London, this trendy district is home to rock stars and artists. Known for its vibrant music scene, colorful Camden boasts quirky shops, bohemian cafes and the famous Camden Market. The area is just north of Kings Cross and Regents Park.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>1BR Apartment - The 1 and 2-bedroom apartments at Churchill House Residence have a separate seating area, flat-screen TV and dining area. The kitchen has an oven, microwave and fridge.

2BR Apartment - The 1 and 2-bedroom apartments at Churchill House Residence have a separate seating area, flat-screen TV and dining area. The kitchen has an oven, microwave and fridge.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>