<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10823077</Id><Name>Dreamhouse London City</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>3 Cyrus Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>EC1V 0BE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-845-226-0232</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>London City apartments offer a comfortable, stylish and conveniently located accommodation ranging from 1 &amp; 2 bedroom apartments to magnificent 3 bedroom penthouse apartment which boasts impressive views of the city. The apartments are extremely well equipped and well designed to be a home away from home. With fully equipped kitchens, high tech appliances (including ipod dock), spacious living area, balcony and under-floor heating in each apartment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The property is located a short walk from Barbican Underground Station and the local area provides a broad selection of bars, restaurants, shops and supermarkets. St Pauls Catherdal is 15-20 minute walk with easy access to the tourist area on the South-bank.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Luxury 1 bedroom apartment - Luxury 1 bedroom apartment with one double bed includes designed to be a home from home with open plan lounge/dining/kitchen.  Full Kitchen facility.  One double bedroom and bathroom with shower over bath. Balcony and under-floor heating.

Luxury 2 bedroom apartment - Luxury 2 bedroom apartment with two double beds includes designed to be a home from home. With open plan lounge/dining/kitchen.  Full kitchen facility.  2 double bedrooms, master bedroom with en suite shower and separate bathroom (with shower over bath)

Two Bedroom Penthouse Apartment - Luxury 2 bedroom penthouse apartment, designed to be a home from home.  With open plan lounge/dining/kitchen.  Full kitchen facility.  2 double bedrooms and bathroom with shower over bath. Balcony and under-floor heating.

Three Bedroom Penthouse Apartment - Luxury 3 bedroom penthouse apartment, designed to be a home from home.  With open plan lounge/dining/kitchen.  Full kitchen facility.  3 double bedrooms master en suite and bathroom with shower over bath.  Balcony, city views and under-floor heating.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>