<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10822181</Id><Name>44 Curzon Street</Name><Region><Id>52927</Id><Name>West End &amp; Marble Arch</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>44 Curzon Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W1J 7</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44 (0)20 7373 6265</Tel><Fax>+44 (020) 749-1702</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>418</Width><Height>317</Height><Bytes>21011</Bytes><Caption>2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1945</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2942</Bytes><Caption>2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1940</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>456</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>27471</Bytes><Caption>2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>99</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2307</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>450</Width><Height>312</Height><Bytes>16517</Bytes><Caption>2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>100</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2002</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>450</Width><Height>315</Height><Bytes>16188</Bytes><Caption>2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/21/2631759-44-Curzon-Street-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>100</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2130</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>44 Curzon Street offers a wide selection of serviced apartments designed to provide comfort, privacy and excellent value for money. Whether you are traveling on business or leisure the apartment aim is to provide you with the feeling that you have your very own home in the heart of London. The apartment have been the owners of No.44 Curzon Street serviced apartments, the name given to the 3 properties comprising the Mayfair accommodation, for over fifty years. No.44 Curzon Street was the first property of its kind, built in 1908 as a gentlemens' pied-a-terre. The apartment have two further properties close by enabling to offer a greater selection of apartments to choose from. To enhance your stay with the apartment, offers a complimentary chauffeur airport transfer from Heathrow for stays of 5 days or more (incoming only)*. You will be met at the airport and your luggage taken care of, then a comfortable drive direct to your apartment. Transfers both to and from other airports are easy to arrange on your behalf when required. Reception staff at the front desk will be able to arrange your personal laundry and dry cleaning and purchase any provisions you may need. They can also book tickets for the theater, sporting events or concerts, make restaurant reservations, book tours or car hire and offer assistance with other requirements you may have. Freedom and flexibility go hand in hand at No.44 Curzon Street - looking forward to see you.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Situated in the center of Mayfair, close to Shepherd Market, you will be located in one of the most prestigious areas of this fabulous city.Public transport is close at hand with Green Park underground station and numerous bus routes, on Piccadilly and Park Lane, just a 5 minute walk away. Taxis are easy to hail at all times of day. You will be very close to both royal parks, Buckingham Palace, the best of London's shopping and of course Theatreland. Many of the outstanding art collections and galleries are within easy reach, as are most of London's main tourist attractions.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Residential apartment Studio - All apartments have satellite television (with most apartments having more than one TV), FREE BROADBAND, voice mail, hi-fi system, beds can either be Twin, Queen or King, welcome packs in both kitchens and bathrooms, full cooking facilities, plus all the usual attributes you would expect in a top quality serviced apartment. In addition, larger apartments have washer/dryers and dishwashers. Maid service is provided every day except Sundays and Bank Holidays, with extra service available upon request.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>