<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10821941</Id><Name>No 1 The Mansions Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52887</Id><Name>Kensington &amp; Earls Court</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>219 Earls Court Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW5 9BN</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-(0)-207-373-6265</Tel><Fax>+44 (020) 737-3626</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>9744</Bytes><Caption>No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1398</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2314</Bytes><Caption>No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1604</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>14810</Bytes><Caption>No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1848</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>450</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>24973</Bytes><Caption>No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2482</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>10789</Bytes><Caption>No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/67/27/41/No-1-The-Mansions-Apartments-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1607</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>No.1 the Mansions is an elegant property built at the end of the nineteenth century, offering a superb selection of extremely comfortable apartments. They provide a high standard of accommodation with each spacious apartment individually designed and decorated, with different layouts to suit varied needs. For stays of 5 nights or more - will provide a FREE chauffeur transfer from Heathrow airport (incoming only). There are numerous cafes and restaurants in this lively and cosmopolitan part of London, suiting all budgets. The superb shopping of West-field Cent-re, Europe's largest urban shopping mall, King's Road Chelsea and High Street Kensington are a short distance away, with Harrods and Knights-bridge also close by. London's major attractions are easily reached, with three of the finest museums only ten minutes away. Ideal for both the corporate and leisure traveler, attending exhibitions (Earls Court and Olympia are close by) and formal entertaining for large family get-together s, budget holidays, shopping breaks and theater trips - a serviced apartment brings so many advantages to everyone. The luxury of privacy, peace and quiet, meals and snacks when you want, without exorbitant room service charges and just being free to do exactly what you want, when you want.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located within a 5 minutes walk of Earls Court underground station, on the Piccadilly and District lines, serving the whole of London, also with bus stops close by, traveling in and around London is so easy from Earls Court. The Earls Court Exhibition Cent-re is 7 minutes walk away and it is just one stop by underground to Olympia's Exhibition Halls. National History Museum Located in South West London a museum where you can discover the natural world under one building. Open everyday with free entry. Kensington Palace One of the historic Palaces it is located a 10 minute walk from High street Kensington tube station. Once home to Princes Diana it is now full of exhibitions and glorious sights. Harrods - The department store opened its doors in 1849 as a store that prides itself on reputation for excellence. Still today it is one of London's leading department stores with exclusive fashion and food.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Apartment Apartment - Every apartment provides a high standard of accommodation individually designed and decorated, with different layouts to suit varied needs. The apartments include a fully fitted kitchen, washer/dryer (and dishwashers in 3 and larger 2 bedroom apartments), FREE BROADBAND WIFI, satellite TV, direct line telephone and hi-fi music system. The larger apartments are very spacious with many having separate dining rooms for entertaining and meeting purposes. 5-day maid service is included. Baby cots and high chairs are available for small children.

Apartment Studio - Every apartment provides a high standard of accommodation individually designed and decorated, with different layouts to suit varied needs. The apartments include a fully fitted kitchen, washer/dryer (and dishwashers in 3 and larger 2 bedroom apartments), FREE BROADBAND WIFI, satellite TV, direct line telephone and hi-fi music system. The larger apartments are very spacious with many having separate dining rooms for entertaining and meeting purposes. 5-day maid service is included. Baby cots and high chairs are available for small children.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Security24Hour</Code><Text>24-hour security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>