<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10829933</Id><Name>The Victoria Inn</Name><Region><Id>52923</Id><Name>Southbank</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>65-67 Belgrave Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW1V 2BG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 834 6721</Tel><Fax>+44 (207) 9310201</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Dining-4.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>16956</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Dining-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Dining-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1931</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17407</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1771</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3463</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2204</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>14538</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1768</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Other-6.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17230</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Other-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Other-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1896</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>452</Width><Height>282</Height><Bytes>24485</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>112</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2129</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Bar-Lounge-3.jpg</Url><Width>339</Width><Height>282</Height><Bytes>18218</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Bar-Lounge-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/22/08/2631759-The-Victoria-Inn-Bar-Lounge-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>84</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2141</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Welcome to Victoria Inn London. Whether you are looking for a bed and breakfast in London for business or holiday travel, the cheap accommodation in Central London is conveniently located near business centers and London's most popular attractions. Hotels near Victoria Station are convenient for travel throughout London and beyond. Victoria Inn is situated within walking distance from Victoria Station for easy access to British Airways Terminal and Gatwick Express. When choosing London hotels for holiday travel, most visitors want to be near popular tourist attractions. Whether you are searching for cheap hotels near Buckingham palace, hotels near Houses of parliament, cheap hotels near London eye, or hotels near Royal Albert hall, the hotel is near these attractions and many others in Central London, as well as museums, restaurants and shopping. If you plan to spend time shopping in London, hotels near Harrods London and hotels near Oxford street, such as Victoria Inn, is the perfect choice. Other attractions close by Victoria are Westminster abbey, Big Ben, Piccadilly, Sloane Square, Tate Gallery, Victoria Palace Theatre, Apollo Victoria Theatre, Trafalgar Square, Victoria and Albert Museum, the Queen Elizabeth II Conference Center, and the Passport office. With 43 well-appointed rooms, the hotel offers more options and amenities than many budget hotels in Central London. The hotel offers accommodation that includes cheap rooms and comfortable luxury rooms to fit every budget. This recently refurbished hotel has a lift to all floors and provides essential amenities, such as digital flat television, bathroom, tea and coffee, hair dryer, and more. When choosing cheap hotels in Central London, you can save money with hotels that offer breakfast each morning! In addition, the hotel are near many restaurants with reasonable charges for lunch and dinner, as well as entertainment places for the day and night. Whether you are looking for cheap hotels near Victoria station or hotels in Paddington for business or leisure travel, Victoria Inn London offers affordable rates every season. Check the special offers section of the website to learn more about current seasonal discounts. Victoria Inn enables booking hotels in London Victoria easy and convenient with the secure online reservation system. If you have questions or need assistance, please contact us by telephone. The friendly staff at Victoria Inn is committed to offering the best service of any cheap accommodation in Central London. Contact the hotel for assistance in booking your reservation at the bed and breakfast in London Victoria, or with any questions or enquirers. The hotel look forward to welcoming you to London and helping you have a memorable stay with the hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When choosing London hotels for holiday travel, most visitors want to be near popular tourist attractions. Whether you are searching for cheap hotels near Buckingham palace, hotels near Houses of parliament, cheap hotels near London eye, or hotels near Royal Albert hall, the hotel is near these attractions and many others in Central London, as well as museums, restaurants and shopping.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>DOUBLE - ROOM - Double Room offers one double bed with basic amenities.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>