<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10839419</Id><Name>Hotel La Tour Birmingham</Name><Region><Id>52391</Id><Name>Birmingham (and vicinity)</Name><CityId>52391</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Albert Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Birmingham</City><State /><Zip>B5 5JE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+441217188000</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Opened in March 2012, this 4-star hotel is just a 5-minute walk from the Bullring Shopping Centre. It serves modern food in its stylish restaurant. Bespoke cocktails are made by expert mixologists in the bar and there is also an on-site fitness centre. CONTEMPORARY, LUXURIOUS AND COMFORTABLE. IT'S ALL IN THE DETAIL. RICH WOODS AND LEATHER FINISHES COMBINE WITH SEXY, SOFT FURNISHINGS: Elegant blinds and curtains dress the full height windows. There's a neat desk area if you want to work (free wi-fi of course) - it's also a great place to put your ipad! Frosted glass gives an intriguing glimpse into the bathrooms, which hotel is particularly proud of: you'll get well and truly drenched under that walk-in shower. At Hotel La Tour, you're always in control: self check-in, set your room temperature, record TV and watch films on demand. Plug your mp3 player into the system, select your pillow from the comfort menu. It's all there waiting, just for you.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hotel La Tour is located near to the centre of Birmingham and is easily walkable from New Street Station although Moor Street Station is the nearest to the Hotel. Car parking is available in 3 local car parks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>STANDARD - ROOM - A 24 square metre room with full height windows and city views. Fully air conditioned. Touch screen controls for lighting and temperature. Large armchair with footstool, desk and chair. 32inch flat screen TV with live record. Media hub with full connectivity to laptops, smart phones and MP3 players. Listen to your own music and watch your own movie through the system. Fully interactive telephone with touch screen: order room service, dim lights and adjust heating. High quality bed with luxury topper, pillows and duvet for a dreamy night's sleep. Sparkling bathroom with anti-steam mirrors, large walk-in rain shower, audio speakers. Coffee and tea making, safe, iron and ironing board, hairdryer Proximity door locks: one swipe and you're in, with digital control for Do Not Disturb and Please Service signs.

EXECUTIVE - ROOM - A 26 square metre room with full height windows and city views. Fully air conditioned. Coffee and tea making, safe, iron and ironing board, hairdryer. Proximity door locks: one swipe and you're in, with digital control for Do Not Disturb and Please Service signs. Touch screen controls for lighting and temperature. Large armchair with footstool, desk and chair. 40inch flat screen TV with live record. Media hub with full connectivity to laptops, smart phones and MP3 players. Listen to your own music and watch your own movie through the system. Fully interactive telephone with touch screen: order room service, dim lights and adjust heating. High quality bed with luxury topper, pillows and duvet for a dreamy night's sleep. Sparkling bathroom with anti-steam mirrors, large walk-in rain shower, audio speakers. Park and roof terrace views. A stylish designer chaise for you to relax.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>