<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10833577</Id><Name>Dreamhouse Vauxhall Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52923</Id><Name>Southbank</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>St George Wharf</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>Sw8 2LE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 845 2260232</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Dreamhouse is proud to present the new apartments in St George Wharf situated in Vauxhall, South Bank, one of Londond most central riverside locations. The property is set in an apartment complex which has its own internal gardens and access to the embankment and pier.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The apartments are situated in a luxury apartment complex in Vauxhall. A 20 minute  walk to Westminster, Victoria Station and Embankment. The closest Tube station is Vauxhall on the Victoria Line which is less than a 5 minute walk. The property is a short distance from Londons Southbank which is a popular area for tourism and includes landmarks such as the London Eye, The Tate Modern and Tower Bridge.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Luxury 1 Bedroom apartment - Residential  apartment apartment offers one double bed with basic amenities. Luxury 1 bedroom apartment, designed to be a home from home with open plan lounge/dining/kitchen.  Full Kitchen facility.  One double bedroom and bathroom with shower over bath.

Luxury 2 Bedroom Apartment - Residential  apartment apartment offers two double beds with basic amenities. Luxury 2 bedroom apartment, designed to be a home from home.  With open plan lounge/dining/kitchen.  Full kitchen facility. 2 double bedrooms, master bedroom with en suite shower and separate bathroom (with shower over bath).</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>