<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10833793</Id><Name>Melville Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>38/39 Argyle Square</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>WC1H</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 837 0571</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/LOGO0-20121119-080540-652.jpg</Url><Width>82</Width><Height>40</Height><Bytes>1136</Bytes><Caption>LOGO0-20121119-080540-652</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/LOGO0-20121119-080540-652.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>143</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1578</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/PROP0-20121119-080540-634.jpg</Url><Width>600</Width><Height>392</Height><Bytes>29166</Bytes><Caption>PROP0-20121119-080540-634</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/PROP0-20121119-080540-634.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2481</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/TBNL0-20121119-080540-656.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2919</Bytes><Caption>TBNL0-20121119-080540-656</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/TBNL0-20121119-080540-656.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2111</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/ROOM0-20121119-080540-640.jpg</Url><Width>600</Width><Height>392</Height><Bytes>29166</Bytes><Caption>ROOM0-20121119-080540-640</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/ROOM0-20121119-080540-640.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2481</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/ROOM1-20121119-080540-645.jpg</Url><Width>420</Width><Height>600</Height><Bytes>29599</Bytes><Caption>ROOM1-20121119-080540-645</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/46/61/1/ROOM1-20121119-080540-645.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>49</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1615</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Hotel Melville in Argyle Square, where attention is paid to the smallest details, is an accommodating budget bed and breakfast with all the most modern comforts, perfect for young people on holiday in London and appreciated by business customers. Its soberly decorated interiors, finished with warm woodwork and soundprofed floors of real wood, make this low cost hotel in Kings Cross an inviting place to stay. It is spotlessly clean and complete with LCD TV, free WI-Fi and pay car park for those travelling by car. All information about getting around the city and discovering the events taking place in London will be provided by the staff in reception, which is open 24 hours a day and at your complete service. Your stay at Hotel Melville includes an abundant buffet breakfast and rest in a comfortable Scandinavian bed with orthopaedic pocket sprung mattresses. The hotel also offers amenities such as free breakfast.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hotel Melville, in London's zone 1, is a low-cost hotel for those who wish to discover the wonders of a simply fantastic city, one of the capitals of the world, with a wealth of history, culture and glamour. Peaceful Argyle Square, just a short walk from the underground station, is the location of Hotel Melville, the low-cost B&amp;B in Kings Cross, within easy reach of Regent's Park and Camden. Hotel Melville is just two minutes' walk from Kings Cross, and has good underground and bus links to Heathrow, Luton and Gatwick airports. The Eurostar to Paris departs from the nearby Saint Pancras international station, as well as various trains bound for the north of England and Scotland.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Quad Room - Quad Room offers one king size bed and one double bed with basic amenities. Quadruple (1 king size bed + 1 standard double bed), Non-smoking, Hypoallergenic room With view, Radio alarm clock, Hairdryer, Hair styling iron, Electronic safe for valuables and Bathroom.

Guest Suite - Guest Suite Room offers one double size bed and one sofa bed with basic amenities. suite (1 double bed + 1 double sofa bed), Non-smoking, Hypoallergenic room  With view, Radio alarm clock,  Hairdryer, Hair styling iron,  Electronic safe for valuable and  Bathroom.

Double Room - Double Room offers one double bed with basic amenities. Double  Non-smoking, Hypoallergenic room With view, Radio alarm clock, Hairdryer, Hair styling iron Electronic safe for valuables and  Bathroom.

Double Twin for sole use - Double Twin for sole use offers one double bed with basic amenities. Double Room For Single Use, Non-smoking, Hypoallergenic room With view, Radio alarm clock, Hairdryer, Hair styling iron, Electronic safe for valuables and  Bathroom.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>