<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>108353</Id><Name>Playa Garden</Name><Region><Id>21276</Id><Name>Playa De Muro</Name><CityId>18419</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ALCUDIA - ARTA KM.29,5</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PLAYA DE MURO</City><State /><Zip>07408</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>971892115</Tel><Fax>971891477</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>39.790039</Latitude><Longitude>3.124795</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/LOGO0-20090624-105359-489.gif</Url><Width>1</Width><Height>1</Height><Bytes>43</Bytes><Caption>LOGO0-20090624-105359-489</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/LOGO0-20090624-105359-489thumb.gif</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>917</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/PROP0-20090624-105359-414.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>15335</Bytes><Caption>PROP0-20090624-105359-414</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/PROP0-20090624-105359-414thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2283</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/TBNL0-20090624-105359-500.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3609</Bytes><Caption>TBNL0-20090624-105359-500</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/TBNL0-20090624-105359-500thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2492</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/ROOM0-20090624-105359-481.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>13135</Bytes><Caption>ROOM0-20090624-105359-481</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/92/47/31/ROOM0-20090624-105359-481thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2117</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Aparthotel Playa Garden invites you to experience an exceptional ocean front hotel built right on the beach. Whether you are looking for a romantic getaway, a family reunion or coming simply to relax and rejuvenate, the Aparthotel Playa Garden is truly the best place to stay with breathtaking well maintained natural beauty. The Aparthotel offers many sport and leisure activities such as an indoor pool, jacuzzi, sauna and gymnasium enabling you to stay in shape and take good care of yourself, even when you are travelling. 

We also offer a reception service, with free wifi access, lounge, lounge-bar, air-conditioned buffet restaurant and a poolside bar where guests can chill out. Guests can enjoy serene comfort with over 8,000m of lush landscaped garden. 

Here you can enjoy the sea and the pure sea breeze, and swim in the sparkling large outdoor swimming pool, which is the perfect option for those seeking life's simple pleasures. 

Guests staying in its 225 apartments, built on the Playa de Muro will be immersed in the atmosphere, in the perfect surroundings for a memorable vacation. 

No sooner than coming down from your room, you will be able to enjoy an extensive, delicious, and varied breakfast buffet, and those who reserve their accommodation with half-board, which includes both the breakfast and dinner buffets, will be able to combine flavour and health at night with the delicious, extensive and varied buffet of hot and cold dishes that the Aparthotel Playa Garden has to offer. 

At mid-day, there is a snack bar available at the swimming pool for lunch, or if you like, you will have a grill and  la carte restaurant (charged separately) available in the evening. 

The Aparthotel Playa Garden is also the ideal option for family vacations with children and offers a range of services specially designed for them including: miniclub from 4 to 7 years old, children's pool, a playground, games, competitions and much more, as well as a separate special Kid's Club operated by First Choice. 
In front of The Aparthotel Playa Garden is a supermarket and a steakhouse restaurant which provides your holiday with more freedom and variety. 

Our entertainments team put together a large programme of activities throughout the day and night and aim to make your holiday as fun and entertaining as possible. For this reason they have planned an entertainments program full of different activities including live music shows, aerobic classes, games and many childrens activities to keep the whole family busy. 

On May 18th we opened a new Italian restaurant at the Hotel, the Giardino. It has a varied menu that includes salads, pizzas, meats, fish, snacks and the corner of Children "for children. Also offers special meals for vegetarians and celiacs. 

Will also offer delivery to the area of Playa de Muro and Ca'n Picafort. 
Guests can also enjoy free wifi in the restaurant. Guests with Gold IT service enjoy a 50% discount.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Apartment - 2 twin (single) beds or 1 double bed or 1 sofa bed - The Standard Apartment in Playa Garden have a bathroom and a balcony. All of them are equipped with air conditioning, telephone, Satellite Tv, and a safe (additional charge).</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>