<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10842375</Id><Name>Victoria Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52435</Id><Name>Canterbury</Name><CityId>52435</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>59 London Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Canterbury</City><State /><Zip>CT2 8TY</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 1227 459 333</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>267</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>29231</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1623</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>4008</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2496</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>23708</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2506</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-6.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>16145</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2187</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-9.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>28821</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-9</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-9.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2985</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Interior-10.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>28264</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Interior-10</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Hotel-Interior-10.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2786</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Lobby-3.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>18896</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Lobby-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Lobby-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2363</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>14556</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2192</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>15722</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2265</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>14540</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2157</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-8.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>267</Height><Bytes>26433</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/89/15/41/2631759-Victoria-Hotel-Bar-Lounge-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2853</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The recently refurbished family run Canterbury hotel is set in lovely well maintained gardens and escapes the noise and traffic/parking problems in the city center. All of the 34 rooms are en-suite, non smoking and have new flat screen digital TV's. Free wifi (wireless broadband) is also available for the guests. Just a 10 minute walk brings you to The Westgate Towers, the ancient monument which is the only remaining original gate to the city. Friendly service and hospitality from professional staff is the key to why many visitors - whether tourists or business people - return and become 'old friends'. Whether you are dining in the restaurant or having drinks with a light meal in their cosy bar; organizing a conference, attending a wedding reception or simply indulging in 'getting away from it all', the hotel is always available to help make your visit a really enjoyable occasion.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>For the traveller, Canterbury is an ideal base for exploring the South East England region, or a very convenient stopping off point for breaking a journey en route to your final destination. Canterbury appeals to younger and mature visitors alike, and the labyrinthine Medieval streets are perfect for discovering the city centre on foot. Canterbury's many attractions include: Canterbury Cathedral Fascinating and historic architecture Theatres &amp; Cinemas Excellent shopping facilities Museums &amp; Galleries Canterbury Festival (October) Kent County Cricket Ground Superb selection of restaurants &amp; cafes Romantic river boat trips Attractive parks &amp; riverside walks A little further afield in the beautiful surrounding countryside of "The Garden of England" hide numerous charming villages, country pubs and inns and famous Country houses, gardens and Royal retreats open to the public.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single Room - Following recent refurbishment to the highest standard, The Victoria Hotel offers comfort and style with 33 individually decorated bedrooms to suite every taste. The selection of single, double, twin, triple, family and the superior four poster room are all ensuite with flat screen digital TVs, autodial telephones, personal toiletries and complimentary tea and coffee making facilities. Free wifi (wireless broadband) is also available for their guests. All this is to ensure that you have a great experience from one of Canterbury's best hotels.

Double Room - The room offers one double bed. Following recent refurbishment to the highest standard, The Victoria Hotel offers comfort and style with 33 individually decorated bedrooms to suite every taste. The selection of single, double, twin, triple, family and the superior four poster room are all en-suite with flat screen digital TVs, autodial telephones, personal toiletries and complimentary tea and coffee making facilities. Free wifi (wireless broadband) is also available for the guests. All this is to ensure that you have a great experience from one of Canterbury's best hotels.

Twin Room - The room offers two twin beds. Following recent refurbishment to the highest standard, The Victoria Hotel offers comfort and style with 33 individually decorated bedrooms to suite every taste. The selection of single, double, twin, triple, family and the superior four poster room are all ensuite with flat screen digital TVs, autodial telephones, personal toiletries and complimentary tea and coffee making facilities. Free wifi (wireless broadband) is also available for the guests. All this is to ensure that you have a great experience from one of Canterbury's best hotels.

Triple Room - The room offers three twin beds. Following recent refurbishment to the highest standard, The Victoria Hotel offers comfort and style with 33 individually decorated bedrooms to suite every taste. The selection of single, double, twin, triple, family and the superior four poster room are all ensuite with flat screen digital TVs, autodial telephones, personal toiletries and complimentary tea and coffee making facilities. Free wifi (wireless broadband) is also available for the guests. All this is to ensure that you have a great experience from one of Canterbury's best hotels.

Family - Quad Room - The room offers one king bed and two twin beds. Following recent refurbishment to the highest standard, The Victoria Hotel offers comfort and style with 33 individually decorated bedrooms to suite every taste. The selection of single, double, twin, triple, family and the superior four poster room are all ensuite with flat screen digital TVs, autodial telephones, personal toiletries and complimentary tea and coffee making facilities. Free wifi (wireless broadband) is also available for the guests. All this is to ensure that you have a great experience from one of Canterbury's best hotels.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>