<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840515</Id><Name>Cleyro Serviced Apartments Bristol Harbourside</Name><Region><Id>52850</Id><Name>Bristol</Name><CityId>52416</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Caledonian Road, Bedminster</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bristol</City><State /><Zip>BS1 6JR</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>011441173253976</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Harbourside Apartments boast a superb accommodation in an idyllic waterside location; whilst being only a 10 minute stroll to the city centre. These serviced apartments offer peace and quiet, away from all the hustle and bustle of the city centre with the convenience of being so close to the all the action. The design of the apartments are striking, winning numerous architectural wards since conception by Feilden Clegg Bradley. Staying with Cleyro offers you so much more, you can expect a fully fitted designer kitchen, including an oven, microwave and fridge freezer, kettle and toaster. Our lounge includes a two seat luxurious sofa to relax on; with a flat screen freeview TV and DVD player. The dining area has a dining table with four chairs and all the crockery and cutlery you would need. All bedrooms have wardrobes and plenty of storage space. Soft linens and towels are included for your stay. The bathroom is tiled from floor to ceiling and includes a contemporary glass door shower. All apartments come with a hairdryer, iron and ironing board as well as a washer/dryer. There are double-glazed windows to keep out all the hustle and bustle of the city, security self-locking doors and electronic fob access to enter the building and ensure your safety. At Cleyro we work a little differently. We offer a personalised check in service, meeting you at the development to show you around. Therefore we ask you to please contact us after making your booking to arrange your check in time. Please note that we operate a minimum stay of 2 nights during weekends.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Bristol has a long history as a port, dating back to 1051 and has been an important city for the sea trade for hundreds of years. As the port grew in size, so to did the need to develop the harbourside. As you walk along the harbourside, next to the apartments, you can imagine the magnificent ships with their huge sails flapping in the wind. As the wealth of Bristol increased, through the trade of slavery and tobacco, piracy became prevalent. Bristol's most infamous pirate was known as Blackbeard, terrorized the Caribbean waters for many years. Just next door you will find The SS Great Britain and the @ Bristol Science Centre, with so much to explore at just a stones throw you will have plenty to do right on your doorstep.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Deluxe Apartment - Deluxe Apartments offer contemporary living in the heart of Bristol. All our deluxe apartments are fully furnished with everything necessary for a short or long term stay. With a with large open plan living rooms to relax in and free WIFI in all apartments you can feel at home.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>