<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840545</Id><Name>Artist Residence Brighton Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52414</Id><Name>Brighton</Name><CityId>52414</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>33 Regency Square</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brighton</City><State /><Zip>BN1 2GG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>011 4412 7332 4302</Tel><Fax>+44 (1273) 376879</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>33181</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1558</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3775</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2358</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Interior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>20507</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Interior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Hotel-Interior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2159</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>451</Width><Height>301</Height><Bytes>37601</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2613</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>17937</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2096</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>318</Height><Bytes>19980</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2161</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>38523</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2743</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>45588</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/90/07/11/2631759-Artist-Residence-Brighton-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2839</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Artist Residence is a small boutique style hotel in a beautiful grade 2 listed Regency Townhouse with stunning sea views over the West Pier and art at its core. The perfect place to stay if you're seeking a relaxing and informal break. Hotel has 3 different types of bedrooms - doubles, micro sea views and superior sea views. Each one is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration and all the rooms have digital flat screen TVs and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers. Your comfort is the main concern and all the beds and mattresses are pocket sprung with mattress toppers. Each room has a desk and chair for those of you that will be working. All the guests have access to the Wi-Fi cafe which has stunning sea views and high ceilings where you can enjoy the view with a nice cup of tea. Hotel has put a lot of thought into food and in the downstairs cafe, you'll be able to enjoy a cooked breakfast or continental all prepared by the home cook Trish. Hotel has a small but perfectly formed breakfast menu. If you imagine an atom, Artist Residence has art at its core. Its not just the art rooms. Hotel also has an art gallery downstairs, which shows monthly exhibitions of emerging artists. 
The hotel has no smoking policy.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Artist Residence Hotel is in the very centre of Brighton where many of the city's bars and shops are located. You are only 10 minutes for the North and South Laines as well as the usual historic places such as the Royal Pavilion and the tourist attractions such the Brighton Palace Pier.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard - Double - Standard Double offers one double bed, each room is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration. All the rooms have digital flat screen TV's and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers for your comfort.

Standard - Twin - Standard Twin offers two twin beds, each room is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration. All the rooms have digital flat screen TV's and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers for your comfort.

Standard - Triple - Standard Triple offers 1 double bed and 1 Single bed, each room is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration. All the rooms have digital flat screen TV's and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers for your comfort.

Family - Room - Family Room offers 1 double bed and 2 Single beds, each room is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration. All the rooms have digital flat screen TV's and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers for your comfort.

Double - Room - Double Room offers 1 double bed, each room is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration. All the rooms have digital flat screen TV's and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers for your comfort.

Superior - Double - Superior Double offers 1 double bed, each room is individually decorated by artists in a variety of styles from urban street art to contemporary illustration. All the rooms have digital flat screen TV's and the en-suite bathrooms have power showers and hairdryers for your comfort.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>