<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846424</Id><Name>Fox and Hounds Country Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52516</Id><Name>Exeter</Name><CityId>52516</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Eggesford</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Exeter</City><State /><Zip>EX18 7JZ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-0176-9580-345</Tel><Fax>011-44-1271410200</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/LOGO0-20120210-094641-060.gif</Url><Width>82</Width><Height>40</Height><Bytes>967</Bytes><Caption>LOGO0-20120210-094641-060</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/LOGO0-20120210-094641-060.gif</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>143</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>4129</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/PROP0-20120210-094640-981.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>49040</Bytes><Caption>PROP0-20120210-094640-981</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/PROP0-20120210-094640-981.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2311</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/REST0-20120210-094641-022.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>29985</Bytes><Caption>REST0-20120210-094641-022</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/REST0-20120210-094641-022.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2397</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/TBNL0-20120210-094641-043.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3089</Bytes><Caption>TBNL0-20120210-094641-043</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/TBNL0-20120210-094641-043.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2160</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/ROOM0-20120210-094640-903.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>27744</Bytes><Caption>ROOM0-20120210-094640-903</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/ROOM0-20120210-094640-903.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2362</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/ROOM1-20120210-094640-944.jpg</Url><Width>500</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>26627</Bytes><Caption>ROOM1-20120210-094640-944</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/87/92/71/ROOM1-20120210-094640-944.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2073</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Fox and Hounds Country Hotel is located in the glorious North Devon Countryside, perched on the River Taw amongst the scenic landscape of the Tarka Trail. The hotel offers a comfortable retreat to nature where you can enjoy the outdoor life amongst the surrounding natural beauty. Fox and Hounds boasts access to some of the best sports in the country and boasts rolling gardens that meet the riverbank, where on a lucky day you can find salmon leaping and otters frolicking. The hotel is one of the very few in the country that offers their own in-house Fly Fishing school, with full time AAPGAI instructors on hand for experienced fly fishing tutorials. For the more advanced angler, the lake is the perfect spot to perfect your casting and perhaps add a few more techniques. The Fox &amp; Hounds Country Hotel has rooms with en-suite baths/showers and are all individually styled with antique furnishings. We are proud to be part of the AA, Essential Exeter and Devon Tourism Scheme and Visit Devon who only offer quality accommodation on their sites. There is WiFi access throughout the hotel. Our beauty room is owned and run by Prana Holistic Health and all the latest relaxation therapies are available to book direct with them. We have a croquet area in the summer months and our practice lake is suitable for all the family to try their hand at fishing. We have DVD players &amp; PlayStation available to hire and irons are available to borrow when required. We offer fishing equipment for hire (pre booking advised) and bicycles can be rented at Barnstaple station.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The local area boasts many sites of interest and country pursuits, including the famous national parks of Dartmoor and Exmoor. There is an amazing array of activities on offer at the hotel or in the nearby countryside. The hotel is famous for its fishing with a rich history associated with trout and salmon fishing and currently has over five miles of fishing available on the River Taw with concessions at a number of other local rivers. If you fancy something more energetic there is great riding, seasonal shooting, walking and numerous golf courses within a few minutes drive. Slightly further afield are the beaches of North Devon with Saunton Sands and Croyde, rightly famous for its surfing, about 35 minutes drive.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Standard Room - Rooms offer the traditionally comfortable furnishings and decor one would expect of a country hotel, allowing guests to truly relax after an exhilarating day spent enjoying the delights of the countryside. In addition, rooms boast an excellent range of modernised features to enhance your enjoyment, including flat screen television and free wireless internet access. For an extra sense of grandeur in your stay, the hotel's four poster bedrooms complete with antique furnishings are the perfect treat for those special weekends away.

Superior and Family Rooms - Our largest rooms feature flat screen TV &amp; radios, hot drink making facilities with the 'good' biscuits, hairdryer, fluffy bathrobes and luxury toiletries. With either four poster or canopy kingsize beds all are furnished to a high standard. Our largest family suite has a separate lounge area with bunk beds and space for cots as required. One superior room on the ground floor has two double beds, bath with over shower, separate sitting area and own private patio overlooking the garden.

Standard Family and Twin Rooms - Our family twins have a double and single bed with additional space for a cot if required and feature all the amenities of our double rooms. Suitable for a maximum of 2 children.

Single Rooms - Compact and cosy with 4 foot beds our singles have full en-suite facilities, TV, tea &amp; coffee facilities and hairdryer. Recommended only for 1 guest.

Disabled Friendly Rooms - We have 3 ground floor rooms in total which all face the garden. The superior Garden Room with its' own terrace has a normal bath with over shower and is dog friendly. The standard room number 20 with its' own patio area can be double or twin with a walk-in shower and is also dog friendly (N.B shower width is 70cm so suited to partially mobile guests). We also have our new standard twin number 21 with fully adapted wet room and low level units as the most suited to wheelchair users.

Please note in high season the Garden Room (as our most popular room) is subject to a minimum stay of 2 nights.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>