<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10855205</Id><Name>City Warehouse Apartment Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52895</Id><Name>Manchester City</Name><CityId>52631</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>6-14 Great Ancoats Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Manchester</City><State /><Zip>M4 5AZ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0161 236 3066</Tel><Fax>011441612286773</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/LOGO0-20121113-063932-482.gif</Url><Width>1</Width><Height>1</Height><Bytes>43</Bytes><Caption>LOGO0-20121113-063932-482</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/LOGO0-20121113-063932-482.gif</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>1</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>1</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>43</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/PROP0-20121113-063932-505.jpg</Url><Width>450</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>22617</Bytes><Caption>PROP0-20121113-063932-505</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/PROP0-20121113-063932-505.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>450</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>350</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>22617</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/TBNL0-20121113-063932-490.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2607</Bytes><Caption>TBNL0-20121113-063932-490</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/TBNL0-20121113-063932-490.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>120</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>90</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2607</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/ROOM0-20121113-063932-522.jpg</Url><Width>450</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>23719</Bytes><Caption>ROOM0-20121113-063932-522</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/ROOM0-20121113-063932-522.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>450</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>350</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>23719</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/ROOM1-20121113-063932-473.jpg</Url><Width>450</Width><Height>350</Height><Bytes>21699</Bytes><Caption>ROOM1-20121113-063932-473</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/29/22/1/ROOM1-20121113-063932-473.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>450</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>350</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>21699</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located just a few minutes' walk from Piccadilly Gardens, in the heart of Manchester City Centre, the City Warehouse Apartment Hotel offers a superb alternative to traditional Hotel accommodation. All 28 spacious and stylishly decorated apartments are designed with comfort, privacy and subtle elegance in mind, with options to sleep up to 8 people. All apartments are fitted with modern kitchens and beautifully designed bathrooms, and come equipped with 32 inch plasma-screen televisions. CD and DVD players are available on request, and WIFI is free as standard throughout the building. There is even a shopping service provided for those of you who really want to put your feet up! All fresh linen, towels and toiletries are included and there is a complimentary welcome pack provided on arrival, including tea, coffee and milk. Our reception is open 24 hours a day and check-in is from 3pm onwards. We may be able to arrange an early check-in where required. Please note that this would be subject to availability and must be confirmed directly with the hotel prior to your check in date. Check out is at 12noon. Secure car parking is also available at a small charge. Guests may also be required to pay a security deposit on check-in of between 50GBP-300GBP, depending on the type of apartment booked. This is taken as a pre-authorisation on a valid debit or credit card and is fully refundable on check-out, provided keys are returned safely and the hotel's terms and conditions have been adhered to.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Enjoy the boutique vintage shops, tea rooms and stylish bars and restaurants of Manchester's fashionable Northern Quarter, and with the Arndale Shopping Centre and both Piccadilly and Victoria train stations just a ten minute walk away in either direction, you would find it hard to be better located for a visit to this vibrant city. Ideally situated next to the famous Frog and Bucket Comedy Club, we are also one of the city's best located hotels near Manchester Arena. Manchester City Centre offers a wealth of entertainment and cultural destinations for visitors. The former European Capital of Culture boasts a generous number of theatres, museums, art galleries and some of the most iconic music venues in the country. It is also home to one of world sport's oldest and biggest rivalries, between Manchester United and Manchester City football clubs.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>One Bedroom Apartment - One bedroom apartment with one double bed and one bathroom. One bedroom apartments are also available with 2 Single Sofa beds sleeping a maximum of 4 persons. All apartments are fitted with modern kitchens and beautifully designed bathrooms, and come equipped with 32 inch plasma-screen TV's.  All fresh linen, towels and toiletries are included and a complimentary welcome pack is provided on arrival, including tea, coffee, milk etc. PLEASE NOTE: Guests may be required to pay a security deposit on check-in of between 50GBP-300GBP, depending on the type of apartment booked. This is taken as a pre-authorisation on a valid debit or credit card and is fully refundable on check-out, provided keys are returned safely and the hotel's terms and conditions have been adhered to.

Two Bedroom Apartment - Two bedroom apartment with two double beds and one bathroom. Two bedroom apartments are also available with 2 Single Sofa beds sleeping a maximum of 6 persons. All apartments are fitted with modern kitchens and beautifully designed bathrooms, and come equipped with 32 inch plasma-screen TV's.  All fresh linen, towels and toiletries are included and a complimentary welcome pack is provided on arrival, including tea, coffee, milk etc. PLEASE NOTE: Guests may be required to pay a security deposit on check-in of between 50GBP-300GBP, depending on the type of apartment booked. This is taken as a pre-authorisation on a valid debit or credit card and is fully refundable on check-out, provided keys are returned safely and the hotel's terms and conditions have been adhered to.

Two Bedroom Penthouse Apartment - Our Penthouse Apartments feature exceptional City views and each has two bedrooms with a double bed in each and two bathrooms. In addition, there is an option of either 2 Single Sofa beds or 2 Double Sofa beds sleeping a maximum of 6 or 8 persons dependent on your selection when booking. All apartments are fitted with modern kitchens and beautifully designed bathrooms, and come equipped with 32 inch plasma-screen TV's.  All fresh linen, towels and toiletries are included and a complimentary welcome pack is provided on arrival, including tea, coffee, milk etc. PLEASE NOTE: Guests may be required to pay a security deposit on check-in of between 50GBP-300GBP, depending on the type of apartment booked. This is taken as a pre-authorisation on a valid debit or credit card and is fully refundable on check-out, provided keys are returned safely and the hotel's terms and conditions have been adhered to.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>