<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856472</Id><Name>Invicta Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52683</Id><Name>Plymouth</Name><CityId>52683</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>11/12 Osborne Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Plymouth</City><State /><Zip>PL1 2PU</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>00442072244405</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/17/27/1/2631759-Invicta-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>395</Width><Height>297</Height><Bytes>21931</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Invicta-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/17/27/1/2631759-Invicta-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2291</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/10/17/27/1/2631759-Invicta-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3799</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Invicta-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/10/17/27/1/2631759-Invicta-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2333</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Invicta Hotel is a friendly family run 3 Star Hotel. Situated on the famous Plymouth Hoe  commanding views across The Hoe Park and Bowling Green. Sea views to the right and on a clear day into Dartmoor.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Invicta Hotel is a friendly family run 3 Star Hotel. Situated on the famous Plymouth Hoe commanding views across The Hoe Park and Bowling Green. For those of you travelling to France or Spain the Brittany ferry port is 2 minutes by car. Recently refurbished the hotel accommodation offers twenty-three fully en-suite rooms comprising of single double twin and family rooms with executive "Classic" rooms located on the first floor. Each room includes tea and coffee making facilities complimentary toiletries a hairdryer colour television and radio direct dial telephone and BT Broadband internet access. Please be aware that being a grade II listed building the hotel do not have a lift third floor rooms are reduced in price to compensate for this but may not be suitable for guests with mobility problems.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>CLASSIC - DOUBLE - Classic Double Room offers one double bed with basic amenities.Classic Double En-suite.

CLASSIC - TWIN - Classic Twin Room offers two twin beds with basic amenities.Classic Twin En-suite.

DOUBLE - EN_SUITE - Double En-suite Room offers one double bed with basic amenities. Double En-suite.

TWIN - EN_SUITE - Twin En-suite Room offers two twin beds with basic amenities.  Twin Ensuite.

FAMILY - EN_SUITE - Family En-suite Room offers one double bed or two twin beds with basic amenities. Family En-suite - 2 Adults &amp; 2 Children.

CLASSIC - ROOM - Classic Room offers one double bed and two twin beds with basic amenities. Classic Double/Twin.

SINGLE - EN_SUITE - Single En-suite Room offers one twin bed with basic amenities. Single En-suite.

STANDARD - ROOM - Standard Room offers one double bed and two twin beds with basic amenities. Double/Twin En-Suite.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>