<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856231</Id><Name>Swans Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52666</Id><Name>Nottingham</Name><CityId>52666</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>84-90 Radcliffe Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nottingham</City><State /><Zip>NG2 5HH</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01159814042</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>At Swans Hotel they provide quality en suite accommodation in comfortable surroundings at competitive rates. Whether on business or pleasure, you will find that Swans Hotel offers a friendly and informal atmosphere while at the same time provides all the facilities you require for your stay away from home. Indeed, the hotel try very hard to make you feel at home. The hotel also offers free breakfast, free parking &amp; free WiFi to all its guests.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Nottingham - Ideal location for all sporting events, close to Cricket, Nottingham Forest and Notts County grounds</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single Room - The room offers one single bed. This elegant hotel offers 30 tastefully decorated bedrooms, each with it's own en-suite bathroom facilities, direct dial telephone, remote control colour television with satellite and freeview channels, radio, trouser press, hair dryer and tea/coffee making facilities.

Double Room - The room offers one double bed. This elegant hotel offers 30 tastefully decorated bedrooms, each with it's own en-suite bathroom facilities, direct dial telephone, remote control colour television with satellite and freeview channels, radio, trouser press, hair dryer and tea/coffee making facilities.

Twin Room - The room offers two single beds. This elegant hotel offers 30 tastefully decorated bedrooms, each with it's own en-suite bathroom facilities, direct dial telephone, remote control colour television with satellite and freeview channels, radio, trouser press, hair dryer and tea/coffee making facilities.

Family Room - The room offers one double beds and one single bed. This elegant hotel offers 30 tastefully decorated bedrooms, each with it's own en-suite bathroom facilities, direct dial telephone, remote control colour television with satellite and freeview channels, radio, trouser press, hair dryer and tea/coffee making facilities.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>