<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10868013</Id><Name>Meadfoot Bay Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52783</Id><Name>Torquay</Name><CityId>52783</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Meadfoot Sea Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Torquay</City><State /><Zip>TQ1 2LQ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>011441803294722</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>21794</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2200</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3292</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2197</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-10.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>12086</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-10</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-10.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2225</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-11.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>16956</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-11</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-11.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2186</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-12.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>299</Height><Bytes>23358</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-12</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-12.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2338</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-13.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>28206</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-13</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-13.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2345</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-14.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>31345</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-14</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-14.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2445</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-15.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17548</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-15</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-15.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1858</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-16.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>36233</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-16</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-16.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2613</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>14041</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2322</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-3.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>19545</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2537</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-4.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>18678</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2525</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-5.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17227</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2175</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-6.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>12516</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1903</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>13861</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2038</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-8.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>17665</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2529</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-9.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>266</Height><Bytes>18267</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-9</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/59/04/01/2631759-Meadfoot-Bay-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-9.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2577</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Meadfoot Bay is a Victorian residence transformed into an award-winning guest house. It is located just 200 meters from Meadfoot Bay Beach, one of Torbays stunning Blue Flag beaches, and a 15-minute walk from Torquay town center. The Meadfoot Bay is a family-run luxury bed and breakfast with facilities including a bar, 2 beautiful lounges, stylish rooms, outside terraces, free on-site car parking and free Wi-Fi. Breakfast is available every morning, and is home-cooked using fresh, local produce. The bar is open throughout the day serving carefully selected wines and specialty coffees. The Meadfoot Bay provides rooms to suit a wide range of requirements. Hotel has room types to suit any budget and these include Standard rooms, Superior rooms, Superior Deluxe rooms and The St Andrews Suite. All bedrooms are individually furnished and tastefully decorated, have en-suite bathrooms with either a bath or shower and have a range of complimentary toiletries. All are equipped with new HD Ready LCD Televisions with Free-view, radio alarm clocks and tea and coffee making facilities and all rooms are maintained to a high standard. If you are here on business or would like to bring your laptop you have free access to the Wi-Fi (laptop dependent) that runs throughout the hotel. Hotel can also supply hairdryers, irons and ironing boards should these be required in the Standard rooms as they are already present in all Superior, Superior Deluxe and The St Andrews Suite. Please note that The Meadfoot Bay does not accept Group Bookings or Stag/Hen Parties. Children over the age of 14 years are welcome.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Meadfoot Bay hotel is just 15 minutes' walk from Torquay harbour and the Living Coasts wildlife experience. Kents Cavern, Babbacombe Model Village and Torre Abbey are all within 2 miles of the guest house.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single Room - All standard bedrooms are individually furnished and tastefully decorated, have en-suite bathrooms with either a bath or shower and have a range of complimentary toiletries. All are equipped with HD Ready LCD Televisions with freeview, radio alarm clocks and tea and coffee making facilities and all are maintained to a high standard. If you are here on business or would like to bring your laptop you have free access to the Wi-Fi (laptop dependant) that runs throughout the hotel. We can also supply hairdryers, irons and ironing boards should these be required in the Standard rooms as they are already present in all Superior, Superior Deluxe and The St Andrews Suite.

Small Double - All standard bedrooms are individually furnished and tastefully decorated, have en-suite bathrooms with either a bath or shower and have a range of complimentary toiletries. All are equipped with HD Ready LCD Televisions with freeview, radio alarm clocks and tea and coffee making facilities and all are maintained to a high standard. If you are here on business or would like to bring your laptop you have free access to the Wi-Fi (laptop dependant) that runs throughout the hotel. We can also supply hairdryers, irons and ironing boards should these be required in the Standard rooms as they are already present in all Superior, Superior Deluxe and The St Andrews Suite. Please note this is a small double and is reduced in price as smaller than hotel's other double rooms.

Superior Double Room - The Superior rooms have been decorated to the highest standard with the finest fittings. We have 3 available, Pebble Beach, Carnoustie and Muirfield. The rooms feature contemporary furniture, sumptuous carpets and Egyptian silk curtains. The luxury bathrooms feature Gilchrist &amp; Soames Spa therapy toiletries, large Turkish bath towels and your own bathrobe and slippers to use during your stay. We have sourced the finest linen available so we can promise that the beds are prepared with Egyptian cotton frette bed linen and for your room entertainment the superior rooms have LCD Televisions with Freeview; the Muirfield room also offers a DVD player, radio alarm clock, trouser press, ironing centre and safe. In addition, when you book a Superior Room you receive a welcome drink in the room compliments from Gary's Bar. There is also complimentary mineral water and a hospitality tray with teas, coffee and hot chocolate.

Superior Deluxe Double Room - We have 2 individually designed rooms, the Wentworth and the Valderrama. The Wentworth is the largest and features luxury seating for your relaxation. The Valderrama is a dual aspect room, located at the front of the guest house, with decked balcony and views of the gardens. Both rooms feature contemporary furniture, sumptuous carpets and Egyptian silk curtains. The beautiful bathrooms boasts power showers, large spa baths, twin sinks, Spa therapy toiletries and large Turkish bath towels. In the rooms you will find your own bathrobe and slippers to use during your stay and the bed is prepared with Egyptian cotton bed linen. For your room entertainment there are LCD Televisions with Freeview, free Wi-Fi, radio alarm clock, trouser press, ironing Centre and safe. In addition, when you book a Superior Deluxe Room you receive a welcome drink in the room compliments from Gary's Bar. There is also complimentary mineral water and a hospitality tray with teas, coffee and hot chocolate.

St Andrews Suite - The superb St. Andrews Suite is ideal if you are planning a romantic trip away with its spacious open plan layout and views of the garden. Designed with contemporary furniture, sumptuous carpets and Egyptian silk curtains, the room also has a 2-seater leather sofa to relax on. The elegant bathroom boasts power shower, large spa bath, twin sinks, Spa therapy toiletries and large Turkish bath towels. In the room you will find your own bathrobe and slippers to use during your stay and the bed is prepared with Egyptian cotton frette bed linen. For your room entertainment there is a 37 inch wall hung HD Ready LCD Television with Freeview and DVD player, free access to the Wi-Fi that runs throughout the hotel, Radio alarm clock, trouser press, ironing centre and safe. In addition, when you book the St. Andrews Suite you receive a welcome drink in the room compliments from Gary's Bar. There is also complimentary mineral water and a hospitality tray with teas, coffee and hot chocolate.

Double Room - All standard bedrooms are individually furnished and tastefully decorated, have en-suite bathrooms with either a bath or shower and have a range of complimentary toiletries. All are equipped with HD Ready LCD Televisions with freeview, radio alarm clocks and tea and coffee making facilities and all are maintained to a high standard. If you are here on business or would like to bring your laptop you have free access to the Wi-Fi (laptop dependant) that runs throughout the hotel. We can also supply hairdryers, irons and ironing boards should these be required in the Standard rooms as they are already present in all Superior, Superior Deluxe and The St Andrews Suite.

Twin Room - All standard bedrooms are individually furnished and tastefully decorated, have en-suite bathrooms with either a bath or shower and have a range of complimentary toiletries. All are equipped with HD Ready LCD Televisions with freeview, radio alarm clocks and tea and coffee making facilities and all are maintained to a high standard. If you are here on business or would like to bring your laptop you have free access to the Wi-Fi (laptop dependant) that runs throughout the hotel. We can also supply hairdryers, irons and ironing boards should these be required in the Standard rooms as they are already present in all Superior, Superior Deluxe and The St Andrews Suite.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>