<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10871938</Id><Name>Bauhaus Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52841</Id><Name>Aberdeen City</Name><CityId>52342</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>52 - 60 Langstane Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Aberdeen</City><State /><Zip>AB11 6EN</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>012-242-121-22</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Dining-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>28809</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Dining-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Dining-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2290</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>29012</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2608</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3757</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Hotel-Exterior-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2376</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>24134</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2017</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>27861</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/85/27/41/2631759-Bauhaus-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1898</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Set in the heart of Aberdeen City Center, contemporary, iconic building opened its doors in November 2009. located very close to union street, the hotel provides easy access to the city's shops, nightlife and Theaters. Bauhaus is an urban boutique hotel. All of the stylish rooms have 32-inch flat-screen HD TVs and king-size beds. free Wi-Fi, The luxurious en suite bathrooms have double power showers and Aveda bathroom products. Relax in a contemporary lounge bar with a 60-inch flat-screen TV. Ideal to meet for a drink or a coffee. Rail and bus stations are within walking distance.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Bauhaus is situated in the heart of Aberdeen, just seconds from Union Street. With a rich history, great shopping, and exceptional cultural attractions on its doorstep bauhaus provides an ideal base for exploring Aberdeen and the surrounding area. Aberdeen is the perfect place for a Scottish getaway. Whether you are salmon fishing on the Don and the Dee rivers, touring Balm-oral Castle, catching a game at Aberdeen Football Club, hitting a golf ball around some of stunning local golf courses or exploring Union Square, it is little wonder why visitors return again and again to Aberdeen and the surrounding area.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single Room - Our smallest rooms offer the same comforts as our largest suites but are, well, smaller! Each has en suite showers with luxurious aveda toiletries, free wifi, 32" LCD TV, complimentary bottled water, fridge and safe. there is even an iron and ironing board to help you look your sharpest for the day or night ahead.

Double Room - Double Room with one double bed includes Safety Deposit Box, Iron, Work Desk, Ironing Facilities, Seating Area, Heating, Shower, Hairdryer, Bathroom Amenities, Toilet, Bathroom, TV, Telephone, Tea/Coffee Maker, Minibar, Refrigerator and Wake Up Service/Alarm Clock.

Superior Room - These rooms offer even greater floor space than our executive rooms. We have superior rooms with twin beds for sharing with friends and rooms with king size beds for couples. Each room comes with luxurious aveda toiletries, free wifi, 32" LCD TV, complimentary bottled water, fridge and safe. Just throw your clothes on the floor at night because you can take away the creases in the morning with the iron and ironing board provided in every room.

Executive Rooms - All our executive rooms have king size beds and en suite facilities with walk in showers. All have a work desk and angle lamp so you can work a little bit late if you are not out on the town. Each room comes with luxurious aveda toiletries, free wifi, 32" LCD TV, complimentary bottled water, fridge and safe. there is even an iron and ironing board so there is no excuse not to look your best for that morning meeting.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>