<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10872756</Id><Name>Nicolson Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52867</Id><Name>Edinburgh City</Name><CityId>52507</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>28 West Nicolson Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Edinburgh</City><State /><Zip>EH8 9DD</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+441314773680</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/33/09/46/2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Property-Amenity-2.jpg</Url><Width>485</Width><Height>363</Height><Bytes>18015</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Property-Amenity-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/33/09/46/2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Property-Amenity-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1568</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/33/09/46/2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>485</Width><Height>361</Height><Bytes>22254</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/33/09/46/2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>94</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2213</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/33/09/46/2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>3345</Bytes><Caption>2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/33/09/46/2631759-Nicolson-Apartments-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2228</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located in Edinburgh's Old Town, these modern 4 star apartments are the perfect stylish and convenient choice for your visit to Edinburgh. Well situated for Edinburgh University, Surgeons Hall and the Old Town.  You are only 10 minutes walk from the Royal Mile and Edinburgh Castle. The apartments are fully equipped and include a TV, DVD Player, oven and stove top, microwave, dishwasher and washing machine with dryer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 
PLEASE NOTE:  Check in is at our office at 1 Byres Close, 375 High Street, just beside the retail shop Marchbrae, to collect the keys to your apartment. If you are arriving after 8pm, please contact us for late Check-in instructions.  &lt;br /&gt;WE ASK YOU PLEASE CHECK THE APARTMENTS DESCRIPTIONS FOR THE EXACT ADDRESS OF EACH APARTMENT.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Edinburghs old town, we are only minutes away from the Royal Mile and situated conveniently for all of Edinburghs attractions, making our apartments and ideal base while visiting this historic city.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Quartermile One bedroom Apartment - These contemporary one bedroom apartments are within the striking Norman Building, a seven minute-walk to the Royal Mile and a two minute-walk to Edinburgh University. Each ground floor property has a living room/kitchen, luxury bathroom and one double bedroom. NO WIFI available. A Welcome Pack is offered.

Nicolson - Two Bed Apartment for 4 guests - This apartment has two Double bedrooms. There is a separate living and dining room, a bathroom and a modern fully fitted kitchen that includes a range of integrated appliances. Free Wifi is available and a Welcome Pack is offered.

Nicolson - Studio Apartment - Charming Studio apartment for two people, with fully fitted kitchen and shower room. This top floor apartment (no lift) is fully equipped, very well furnished and a perfect hideaway for your visit to Edinburgh. Free Wifi is available and a Welcome Pack is offered.

Nicolson - Two Bed Apartment for 3 Guests - This apartment has one double bedroom and a single bedroom. There is a separate living/dining room and a modern fully-fitted kitchen that includes a range of integrated appliances. Free Wifi is available and a Welcome Pack is offered.

Nicolson - Two Bed Apartment for 4 Guests - This apartment has two double bedrooms. There is a separate living and dining room, a bathroom and a modern fully fitted kitchen that includes a range of integrated appliances. Free Wifi is available and a Welcome Pack is offered.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>