<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10872939</Id><Name>The Salisbury Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52867</Id><Name>Edinburgh City</Name><CityId>52507</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>43-45 Salisbury Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Edinburgh</City><State /><Zip>EH16 5AA</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 01316671264</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Dining-8.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>316</Height><Bytes>21607</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Dining-8</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Dining-8.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>106</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2390</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>317</Height><Bytes>16453</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2144</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</Url><Width>120</Width><Height>90</Height><Bytes>2642</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1874</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</Url><Width>315</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>18402</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>45</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1333</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>316</Height><Bytes>13620</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-3</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>106</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2045</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>318</Height><Bytes>21372</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2077</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>314</Height><Bytes>18210</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1901</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>317</Height><Bytes>18000</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1723</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>313</Height><Bytes>14129</Bytes><Caption>2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-7</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1116/66/87/21/2631759-The-Salisbury-Hotel-Guest-Room-7.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1722</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The Salisbury Hotel is a luxury contemporary styled georgian townhouse hotel in the cosmopolitan Southside and close to the Old Town, Royal Mile, Edinburgh Castle and Edinburgh University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A range of room types are available from single, double, superior doubles and twins, family and four poster. Ground floor rooms are available, whilst many have lovely views to the magnificent walled gardens. All guestrooms feature crisp white linen, fluffy towels, plasma-televisions, iPod docking stations, hairdryers and welcome trays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is private parking and the Salisbury is easily accessible by car from all the main routes in the City and is located just 1.5 miles from Waverley Train Station; the main bus route is a mere 2 minutes walk from the Salisbury making it convenient to get around the entire city. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gabbro restaurant is located at garden level with direct access to the beautiful walled gardens - featuring an excellent array of dishes and always featuring local and Scottish produce - popular with locals and very family friendly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many interesting shops and bars and the Queens Hall and Festival Theatre are 10 minutes away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests can enjoy the lounge area to relax in after a day exploring the City or to retire to after the children are sleeping in bed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A hearty breakfast can be enjoyed in the Breakfast Room after a good nights rest - a full choice of juices, fruits, cereals, cheeses, as well as a Full Scottish Grill, French toast with grilled bacon and passion fruit syrup or poached eggs with watercress and Hollandaise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most importantly, a warm Scottish friendly welcome awaits you at the Salisbury where you can expect the highest levels of service and comfort. Relax and enjoy the comfort and elegant ambiance of this beautiful Georgian townhouse hotel the ideal base for you to explore the vibrant Edinburgh city.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Edinburgh is one of Scotland's most exciting, vibrant cities, offering many things to see and do. The Salisbury Hotel nestled in the leafy suburb of Newington, and set within the desirable Blacket conservation area  quietly located, yet convenient for a stroll into Edinburghs fashionable George Street shopping district or alternatively, enjoy the fresh air with a gentle hike up Arthurs Seat  it truly is a unique blend of town meets country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Salisbury Hotel is located close enough to reach out into the city in a moment; far enough out to afford space to unwind and drift away in luxury.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Single - Room - Single room offers one single bed. The room is small, but cozy, offering stylish and comfortable accommodation for one.

Standard Double - Room - Standard Double Room for 2 people - are located at the front of the building enjoying a bright and sunny view all day long.  These are budget rooms with comfortable double beds and compact bathrooms; small, but cosy.

Superior Double Room - Superior Double/Twin
Each of these rooms retains the classic ambience of the Georgian era, utilizing rich colours of the period to decorate individual and contemporary designs.  They each offer a suede-upholstered king-size bed or two single beds assuring you of a very restful night's sleep. All feature tall windows with working shutters giving a light and airy ambience, many of which offer spectacular views over the well-tended walled gardens.

Family Room - These junior suites are perfect for family and group accommodation, sporting a suede-upholstered king-size bed or two single beds, as well as a comfortable queen-size sofa bed; if occupied by two persons, it offers a relaxing seating area instead.  Each boasting a distinctive, contemporary design these lovely rooms still capture the classic ambience of the Georgian era.  Further features include full-height windows with working shutters, a marble fireplace, and a bath.

Deluxe Suite - Our deluxe suites are perfectly suited for relaxation and celebration.  They boast a king-size four-poster bed assuring you of a luxuriously comforting night's rest.  Both feature a marble fireplace, full-height windows with working shutters, a wet room complete with a large bath, and views to the front of the building.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>