<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10871313</Id><Name>Glen Lui Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52367</Id><Name>Ballater</Name><CityId>52367</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>14 Invercauld Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Aberdeen</City><State /><Zip>AB35 5PP</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>013397 55402</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Nestled in two acres of peaceful, private woodland, just 20 minutes from Balmoral Castle, offering free WI-FI and Parking, this family-run Hotel offers spectacular views, log fires, delightful dining, and cosy accommodation. Surrounded by the awe-inspiring beauty of Cairngorm National Park, the Hotel is a haven of tranquillity and relaxation. Guests can enjoy magnificent panoramic views of the Cairngorm mountains and the majestic Lochnagar, or perhaps simply watch as red squirrels frolic in the surrounding pine trees. Originally built in 1896, every effort has been taken to ensure that the building still retains many of its original features and traditional charm. Offering a warm, friendly welcome and the best in highland hospitality, the Glen Lui Hotel is sure to inspire a wealth of wonderful memories. Each of the 19 en-suite rooms are tastefully decorated and furnished, perfectly complementing the welcoming appeal of the rest of the building. There is also additional accommodation in the Pine Terrace annexe located within the grounds. As one would expect from a hotel of this calibre, all of the rooms come fully equipped with all the necessary conveniences and comforts, including free Wi-Fi, flat screen TV, Egyptian cotton linen, hairdryer and tea &amp; coffee facilities. There are a range of room types available, with Single, Double, Twin and Superior options. There are also two Suites, one with a splendid four-poster bed and the other a luxurious king-size, whilst both offer south-facing sitting rooms with magnificent views. Pets are welcome by prior arrangement in some Pine Terrace rooms. The hotel also offers free breakfast.

Please note: Pets only permitted in some pine terrace Rooms (annex)</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Hotel is located in the Cairngorm National Park home to Britain's highest mountain range, its biggest native forests, spectacular rivers and lochs, rolling hills and farmland and a natural habitat for much of Britain's wildlife. Visitors can expect immediate access to fantastic outdoor activities, including walking, cycling, fishing, skiing, rock climbing and much more. The Hotel also lies in the famous Royal Deeside valley, one of the most beautiful areas of Scotland and home to some of its most popular attractions. Perhaps most distinguished of all is Balmoral Castle, the Scottish home of the British Royal Family. Visitors can look forward to exploring the acres of scenic grounds, marvellous gardens and wonderful exhibitions and galleries. There are further castles to discover including Braemar, Crathes (with its world-famous gardens) and Drum, the latter two being National Trust for Scotland properties.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Classic Double - Each of the 19 en-suite rooms are tastefully decorated and furnished, perfectly complementing the welcoming appeal of the rest of the building. As one would expect from a hotel of this calibre, all of the rooms come fully equipped with all the necessary conveniences and comforts, including free Wi-Fi, flat screen TV, Egyptian cotton linen, hairdryer and tea &amp; coffee facilities. Classic Double offers one double or two twin beds.

Courtyard Twin - This is additional accommodation in the Pine Terrace annexe located within the grounds. As one would expect from a hotel of this calibre, all of the rooms come fully equipped with all the necessary conveniences and comforts, including free Wi-Fi, flat screen TV, Egyptian cotton linen, hairdryer and tea &amp; coffee facilities.Pets are welcome by prior arrangement in some Pine Terrace rooms. Courtyard Twin offers two twin beds.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>