<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11174751</Id><Name>Signum</Name><Region><Id>157913</Id><Name>Aeolian Islands</Name><CityId>17070</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Scalo, 15</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Messina</City><State /><Zip>98050</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
The Signum, a charming Boutique Hotel in Malfa on the Island of Salina, in the Aeolian archipelago, was born of the painstaking renovation of an old country hamlet surrounded by greenery, just a few steps from the sea for a property that extends for more than five thousand meters. Here the perfumes of the land and sea greet guests as they are welcomed with the authentic Aeolian hospitality of Casa Signum.

Restaurant
The Signum Restaurant is located inside the welcoming Signum hotel, with the covered terrace with views of Stromboli and Panarea and the winter garden veranda housing the dining rooms. The cuisine of Patron Michele and his daughter Martina Caruso offers Mediterranean dishes that merge tradition and innovation. An elegant restaurant which a passionate and attentive service.

More Informations
At Signum guests' disposal large terraces and gardens with relaxing open spaces and intimate hidden corners. The hotel also offers infinity pool with Jacuzzi, reading room and library, free Wi-Fi, a bar, room service and laundry, Spa. 

The concierge will arrange your travel and other activities on the island, such as renting a car or a private boat, organizing a hike in the mountains, a wine tasting at one of the wineries or excursions to the other islands of the Aeolian archipelago.

Check in from 3.00 p.m. 
Check out till 11.00 p.m.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>