<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11175921</Id><Name>Cristina</Name><Region><Id>116530</Id><Name>Limone Sul Garda</Name><CityId>17100</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Tamas, 20</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>25010</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Position
The Cristina Hotel offers comfortable accommodation in Limone sul Garda, a splendid town in Northern Italy, situated on the shores of the famous Lake Garda. This stunning tourist destination offers a diverse choice of beaches, where guests can sunbathe and relax.

Restaurant
Hotel amenities include the Benaco restaurant serving delicious Italian and international dishes, a bar with a wide selection of drinks and snacks.
Drinks during dinner are included (water, red and white wine, orange juice and coke).

Outside
This hotel complex consists of 5 villas (Cristina, Orchidea, Oasi, Calipso and the main building), surrounded by lush gardens from where you can enjoy breathtaking views of Lake Garda. Limone center is reachable with a 15 minutes stroll - there is a hotel shuttlebus at a small charge.

Lobby


More Informations
Among the various activities: pool table, playground, bike hire, excursions, baby sitting, outdoor pool. Services: bike rental, breakfast room, car rental, currency exchange, laundry and ironing service, internet point, room service, Fax / Photocopying.

Check in: rooms are available from approx. 3pm

Dogs allowed small max 10 Kg not in common areas.
Air conditioning from 15/06 to 15/09</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bike Rental</Code><Text>Bike Rental</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>